<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 12:47:28 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Help me name my kitten!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Sorry this isn’t a book suggestion, but I thought it’d be kinda fun - I have a
tradition of giving my pets punny writer names. Currently I have F. Scott
Fishgerald and Margaret Catwood (Maggie for short). I’m getting a new kitten, a
boy, and he doesn’t have a name yet! Best ideas I’ve had so far are…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r4xyn8/help_me_name_my_kitten/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r4xyn8/help_me_name_my_kitten/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 02:51:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry this isn’t a book suggestion, but I thought it’d be kinda fun - I have a tradition of giving my pets punny writer names. Currently I have F. Scott Fishgerald and Margaret Catwood (Maggie for short). I’m getting a new kitten, a boy, and he doesn’t have a name yet! Best ideas I’ve had so far are Kurt Vonnecat and Nathaniel Pawthorn lol. Have a favorite author or poet whose name you can turn into a cat pun? Help me come up with a name for my new kitty! :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Giver is a great book. It should never be seen as just a childrens book.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Giver is an excellent book and yes, while I was introduced to it as a child
and its perfectly acceptable book for kids to read, the messages and lessons in
the book go far beyond that of a child or teenager will understand.

Looking back it is a profound book that should be read and understood…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r59ca6/the_giver_is_a_great_book_it_should_never_be_seen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r59ca6/the_giver_is_a_great_book_it_should_never_be_seen/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2021 01:58:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Giver is an excellent book and yes, while I was introduced to it as a child and its perfectly acceptable book for kids to read, the messages and lessons in the book go far beyond that of a child or teenager will understand.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Looking back it is a profound book that should be read and understood as an adult.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It gives a much better way to question your reality and society and I find it to be much more thought provoking than major works such as 1984 or Animal Farm with regards to potentially dystopian societies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Wheel of Time series has made me mad (no spoilers)]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I watched Wheel of Time on Amazon and I was hooked immediately. Then Amazon
had 50% off the collected box sets this weekend and I bought all of them for
super cheap.

I started reading it last night and before I knew it I was at page 178. I
couldn't put it down. And this is just me reading what…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r54uwy/the_wheel_of_time_series_has_made_me_mad_no/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r54uwy/the_wheel_of_time_series_has_made_me_mad_no/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 22:53:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I watched Wheel of Time on Amazon and I was hooked immediately. Then Amazon had 50% off the collected box sets this weekend and I bought all of them for super cheap. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started reading it last night and before I knew it I was at page 178. I couldn&amp;#39;t put it down. And this is just me reading what the show already mostly covered. I&amp;#39;m so excited for this series. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I&amp;#39;m mad that I didn&amp;#39;t read these sooner. I&amp;#39;m mad that I broke my &amp;quot;no Amazon&amp;quot; goal this Holiday season. Mostly though I&amp;#39;m mad that George Martin and Patrick Rothfuss can&amp;#39;t write a single book in a decade when I currently have 14 books in a single series that I&amp;#39;m VERY excited to read and it only took 2 decades for the entire series. These two can eat a whole bag of dicks. Use a ghost writer at a certain point or I don&amp;#39;t know but figure it out you cock-bites.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Instances in your life where you mispronounced a word you learned via reading a book]]></title><description><![CDATA[I want y'all to tell me a situation where you said a word out loud and learned
later (or immediately, to your embarrassment, if someone corrected you on the
spot) that it is actually pronounced differently. And of course you must have
learned this word from a book.

I'll start: So back when I was…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r513zz/instances_in_your_life_where_you_mispronounced_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r513zz/instances_in_your_life_where_you_mispronounced_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 22:41:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want y&amp;#39;all to tell  me a situation where you said a word out loud and learned later (or immediately, to your embarrassment, if someone corrected you on the spot) that it is actually pronounced differently. And of course you must have learned this word from a book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll start:
So back when I was 16, I learned this fancy new word while reading a book (i forget the book it was) : RENDEZVOUS. I thought it was really cool and looked up the meaning. It means a meeting or if you want to use it as a verb to meet at a certain time and place. A few days later, I was with a group of my friends and we were discussing coming together for  an event. So we needed to meetup. Enter perfect time to use the word RENDEZVOUS. Me being the prententious 16 year old brat I was said, &amp;quot;Let&amp;#39;s rendezvous at this particular place&amp;quot; and you can guess how I pronounced it. I said it how it is written but the actual pronounciation is: RON-DI-VOO. crazy! Annnnnd  I only found out how it was pronounced two years later while listening to a random non-fiction audiobook.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mel Brooks’ memoir, All About Me! The best stories, trivia and tidbits]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r54ccp/mel_brooks_memoir_all_about_me_the_best_stories/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r54ccp/mel_brooks_memoir_all_about_me_the_best_stories/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 22:41:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Danny Trejo's autobiography "Trejo" is amazing.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Just listened to the audio version of Danny Trejo's autobiography "Trejo". He
self narrates the audio book which is really cool. He's not the greatest
narrator, but one you get used to the way he talks, it's overall better that
he's telling his own story.

He lived a crazy violent life in the…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r52rhw/danny_trejos_autobiography_trejo_is_amazing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r52rhw/danny_trejos_autobiography_trejo_is_amazing/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 21:34:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just listened to the audio version of Danny Trejo&amp;#39;s autobiography &amp;quot;Trejo&amp;quot;. He self narrates the audio book which  is really cool. He&amp;#39;s not the greatest narrator, but one you get used to the way he talks, it&amp;#39;s overall better that he&amp;#39;s telling his own story. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He lived a crazy violent life in the beginning, but its ultimately a story about redemption, recovery and giving back. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best biographies I&amp;#39;ve come across.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Overdue book returned anonymously to Idaho library 111 years later]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r52c3x/overdue_book_returned_anonymously_to_idaho/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r52c3x/overdue_book_returned_anonymously_to_idaho/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:57:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Goodreads provide any value to you?]]></title><description><![CDATA[As a user of Goodreads for years, I have very mixed feelings on the platform. It
should be a goldmine of information (millions of ratings and reviews, book
recommendations, interactions with authors), but I often find it underwhelming
in practice.

A few things that stand out to me:

Most books have…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r513zy/does_goodreads_provide_any_value_to_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r513zy/does_goodreads_provide_any_value_to_you/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:32:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a user of Goodreads for years, I have very mixed feelings on the platform.  It &lt;em&gt;should&lt;/em&gt; be a goldmine of information (millions of ratings and reviews, book recommendations, interactions with authors), but I often find it underwhelming in practice.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few things that stand out to me:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most books have a very similar rating.  It&amp;#39;s as if the law of large numbers ends up normalizing most books to be rated between 3.9 and 4.1 stars.  A few regular exceptions to the rule are: Long books almost always rated highly (presumably because one wouldn&amp;#39;t read a 1000 page book if they weren&amp;#39;t really enjoying it, or because one feels the need to justify spending that much time reading a single book) and YA books - often rated abnormally high (possibly due to the large presence of young adults usually social media in general)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Reviews usually consist of generic 5 star reviews &amp;quot;OMG, this book was amazing!&amp;quot; and generic 1 star reviews &amp;quot;This book was boring, poorly written, and stupid!&amp;quot;  I rarely see anything of use in reviews that would help me decide whether or not it&amp;#39;s worth reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The same 10 reviewers seem to consistently bubble up to the top.  (You know the ones I&amp;#39;m referring to:  The reviewers with glamor shots for profile pictures, who write as though they are B- students in AP English required to write a 1000 word essay, when all they have to say is &amp;quot;I liked the book&amp;quot;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Goodreads Choice Award winners are not the best books of the year, even by their own rating system.  They just end up being the books that people have heard of.  For example, &lt;em&gt;Go Set a Watchman&lt;/em&gt; is rated at 3.32 stars (which is abysmally low for Goodreads), but it ended up winning the 2015 Best Fiction award.  What???&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being owned by Amazon, I&amp;#39;m inherently skeptical of any recommendations they give, as they may just be trying to promote a certain publisher or author who they have a special contract with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the same time, I have found the site is very useful for finding potential books to read, getting a quick look into an author&amp;#39;s works and getting updates, seeing what other books people liked who gave my favorite book 5 stars.  And honestly, the Genres listing is one of the most useful sections for me, so I can quickly get a sense of what type of book I&amp;#39;m dealing with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you use Goodreads for?  What value does it provide to you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A note of appreciation for Charles Dickens]]></title><description><![CDATA[Tl;dr Charles Dickens made me smart

Ever since David Copperfield was assigned as reading in my first year of high
school, I have devoured his works and revisited them on an annual basis.

His style of writing has elevated my language, speech, and vocabulary to such
degrees that colleagues and…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4y0pb/a_note_of_appreciation_for_charles_dickens/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4y0pb/a_note_of_appreciation_for_charles_dickens/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 20:11:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tl;dr Charles Dickens made me smart&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ever since David Copperfield was assigned as reading in my first year of high school, I have devoured his works and revisited them on an annual basis. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His style of writing has elevated my language, speech, and vocabulary to such degrees that colleagues and friends often comment on how well I speak, and how refined and clear my writing is. I wholly attribute this to his works, since there is a notable elevation in my powers of expression while I am reading (or recently finished) one of his works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No sarcasm at all, just wanted to publicly share my gratitude. I hope others out there have felt the same, with Dickens or otherwise!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What word do you personally use for getting a book out of the library?]]></title><description><![CDATA[This sounds weird, but online I keep seeing people say that they “rented” a book
from the library, and this feels weird to me. I’d usually say “borrowed” or
maybe “checked out.” In my mind renting implies payment, but I think more so
it’s just weird because I feel like I’ve never heard “rented” used…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4ns2v/what_word_do_you_personally_use_for_getting_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4ns2v/what_word_do_you_personally_use_for_getting_a/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 19:14:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sounds weird, but online I keep seeing people say that they “rented” a book from the library, and this feels weird to me. I’d usually say “borrowed” or maybe “checked out.” In my mind renting implies payment, but I think more so it’s just weird because I feel like I’ve never heard “rented” used in-person in reference to books gotten from a library. What word do you guys use?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books about a mans perspective of divorce]]></title><description><![CDATA[My wife and I got married young, and over time we have grown apart as people
quite a bit. I love her very much and accepted the differences between us but
she doesn't love me anymore, and is no longer happy, so we're splitting up. I've
moved out already. The whole thing is very sad for me but we are…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r4vmhc/books_about_a_mans_perspective_of_divorce/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r4vmhc/books_about_a_mans_perspective_of_divorce/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 17:40:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My wife and I got married young, and over time we have grown apart as people quite a bit. I love her very much and accepted the differences between us but she doesn&amp;#39;t love me anymore, and is no longer happy, so we&amp;#39;re splitting up. I&amp;#39;ve moved out already. The whole thing is very sad for me but we are still friends and there&amp;#39;s no resentment or blame or anything like that. This is the friendliest and most gentle break up/divorce that I&amp;#39;ve ever heard of. There&amp;#39;s nothing that can be changed to make our relationship work, we&amp;#39;re simply just different people with different priorities. But my heart is broken and I was just wondering if you lot could suggest any good novels that are somehow relevant to my situation at all?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to heal, and move on with my life. Maybe reading a relatable story and having a big cry will help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would prefer suggestions of novels, not self care/self help type books. I&amp;#39;m already quite well connected to myself and I&amp;#39;ve done a lot of healing over the years, but this divorce just blindsided me, so I want fictional stories of men in a similar situation...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for the suggestions and kind words, it&amp;#39;s much appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why have I just discovered the Libby app?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Let me tell you, the Libby app has been a total game changer for me! But perhaps
maybe I am just late to the game!

Before moving overseas, I was always at the library borrowing books, I could go
through multiple books a week. Once I moved, books, especially English ones are
just not as available,…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4qqak/why_have_i_just_discovered_the_libby_app/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4qqak/why_have_i_just_discovered_the_libby_app/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 12:37:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let me tell you, the Libby app has been a total game changer for me! But perhaps maybe I am just late to the game!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before moving overseas, I was always at the library borrowing books, I could go through multiple books a week. Once I moved, books, especially English ones are just not as available, or terribly expensive, cue using my Kindle more, but that gets pricy too. Basically, I had to throttle the amount of books I was reading due to cost. And I always tried to use my library&amp;#39;s ebook rental portal, but it gave me nothing but problems that I stopped trying. I have been devouring books since I got it, and rediscovered all the joy I have while reading! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any book suggestions to add to my list are more than welcome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just finished Mexican Gothic and I’ve never loved a book more]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just wanted to gush a bit. The writing is beautiful, the characters are
amazing, and the ending was satisfying. I can count on one hand how many times
I’ve read a book that left me satisfied on the last page. I love the sweet blend
of fantasy and realism and man oh man the suspense!! I was on the…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4lnbq/just_finished_mexican_gothic_and_ive_never_loved/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4lnbq/just_finished_mexican_gothic_and_ive_never_loved/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 04:49:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to gush a bit. The writing is beautiful, the characters are amazing, and the ending was &lt;em&gt;satisfying&lt;/em&gt;. I can count on one hand how many times I’ve read a book that left me satisfied on the last page. I love the sweet blend of fantasy and realism and man oh man the suspense!! I was on the edge of my seat! I could hardly put the book down. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone here read any other works by Silvia Moreno-Garcia? Are they just as good? I can’t decide if I want to read another of hers next or move on.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A fantasy book that isn't set in a medieval world. I want fantasy that resembles our present world.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bonus points if it portrays late 90s/early 2000s.]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r4dszc/a_fantasy_book_that_isnt_set_in_a_medieval_world/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r4dszc/a_fantasy_book_that_isnt_set_in_a_medieval_world/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:08:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bonus points if it portrays late 90s/early 2000s.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just Finished Reading "This Is How You Lose the Time War" by Amal El-Mohtar and Max Gladstone]]></title><description><![CDATA[just WOW what a good read. Reasonably short but absolutely full to the brim with
story, the descriptions were intricate and poetic, the letters were so fun it
was really like reading correspondence between two soldiers/lovers, I've never
been one for time travel story with how confusing things can…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4ellv/just_finished_reading_this_is_how_you_lose_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4ellv/just_finished_reading_this_is_how_you_lose_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 01:08:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;just WOW what a good read. Reasonably short but absolutely full to the brim with story, the descriptions were intricate and poetic, the letters were so fun it was really like reading correspondence between two soldiers/lovers, I&amp;#39;ve never been one for time travel story with how confusing things can get but I feel like the time travel aspect was handled quite smoothly. Red and Blue&amp;#39;s relationship was sooo goood they way they were intricately woven into eachothers lives ;;w;; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The dystopian aspect of their respective lives was also so interesting, Garden made me think of the eco cult in Margaret Atwoods Oryx and Crake series and Commandment made me think of big brother in 1984, it was interesting to see how they contrasted and yet were quite similar. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just feel like the whole book was reading a work of poetry. Anyways totally a 5/5&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just finished Murder On The Orient Express. Is this representative of Agatha Christie? Is this representation of mystery in general?]]></title><description><![CDATA[As audiobooks have allowed me to greatly increase the number of books I consume,
I've been branching out into new areas and a gave Murder On The Orient Express a
try. I didn't love the narrator but I can get past that and enjoy the story for
it's merits.

The set up was good and the ending was…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4aye4/i_just_finished_murder_on_the_orient_express_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r4aye4/i_just_finished_murder_on_the_orient_express_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 20:54:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As audiobooks have allowed me to greatly increase the number of books I consume, I&amp;#39;ve been branching out into new areas and a gave Murder On The Orient Express a try. I didn&amp;#39;t love the narrator but I can get past that and enjoy the story for it&amp;#39;s merits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The set up was good and the ending was absolutely unpredictably but overall I found the book to be only okay. Would I find other Agatha Christie books the same? Does this represent mystery books in general?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are some good books about Assassins?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ive been meaning to read something related to assassins, but im unsure what’s
good and what’s not. (Action/Fantasy whatever comes up)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r41dab/what_are_some_good_books_about_assassins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r41dab/what_are_some_good_books_about_assassins/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 18:18:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ive been meaning to read something related to assassins, but im unsure what’s good and what’s not. (Action/Fantasy whatever comes up)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Foundation is the first book I've read in almost 30 years]]></title><description><![CDATA[Back when I was in jr high, I used to read a lot of books. Mostly Science
Fiction and some random Stephen King. But sometime during high school I got out
of the habit, and literally haven't read an actual book since then. Got into
computers and programming in college, so I ended up filing my free…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r46iml/foundation_is_the_first_book_ive_read_in_almost/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r46iml/foundation_is_the_first_book_ive_read_in_almost/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 17:41:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back when I was in jr high, I used to read a lot of books.  Mostly Science Fiction and some random Stephen King. But sometime during high school I got out of the habit, and literally haven&amp;#39;t read an actual book since then.  Got into computers and programming in college, so I ended up filing my free time with computer stuff and books just fell by the wayside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flash forward to today (I&amp;#39;m 47) and I&amp;#39;m trying to detach myself from my cell phone somewhat.  Uninstalled Facebook, instagram, and a few others. We caught a couple episodes of Foundation on AppleTV, and I&amp;#39;m not sure what it was about that show, but I found it fascinating.   Got it into my head that it would be good for me to start reading books again. And I&amp;#39;ll be damned if I didn&amp;#39;t read the whole thing last night.  What a quick read! And I have to say it felt really good!  Just the process of sitting on the couch with a book, and getting caught up in some other world was such a nice change of pace from the normal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not sure what exactly the point of this post is, except that I&amp;#39;m kind of excited about reading again, and wanted to tell someone...😆 As far as the book goes, I was a little surprised that there wasn&amp;#39;t a little more happening at the end, but I suppose it IS just the beginning of a very long story.  Amazon has a &amp;quot;buy 2 get 1 free&amp;quot; sale on those books, so I just ordered the next 3 in the series.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just finished reading In Cold Blood by Truman Capote]]></title><description><![CDATA[So, I’m in shock. This was a rough experience. It was the first true crime book
that I’ve read, but I was totally immersed in the story. Yes, the whole thing is
distressing and unpleasant, but following the story from so many different
angles is an interesting reading experience. There’s no way to…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r45gbm/just_finished_reading_in_cold_blood_by_truman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r45gbm/just_finished_reading_in_cold_blood_by_truman/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 17:22:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I’m in shock. This was a rough experience. It was the first true crime book that I’ve read, but I was totally immersed in the story. Yes, the whole thing is distressing and unpleasant, but following the story from so many different angles is an interesting reading experience. There’s no way to deny or justify the atrocity of the crime committed by Dick and Perry. But while I was reading it, I couldn&amp;#39;t help but develop a terrible sense of pity for Perry. 
The proximity that Truman brings the reader to the characters is frightening.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do you find it hard to understand surroundings/locations being described in books?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The thought just hit me that I'm probably impaired in this regard, for lack of a
kinder word. Whenever a book starts going into describing how a city is
structured, to the left of the church is a river that runs through x y and z. On
the other side is a hill that towers over... And etc and etc. I…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r42lll/do_you_find_it_hard_to_understand/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r42lll/do_you_find_it_hard_to_understand/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:54:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The thought just hit me that I&amp;#39;m probably impaired in this regard, for lack of a kinder word. Whenever a book starts going into describing how a city is structured, to the left of the church is a river that runs through x y and z. On the other side is a hill that towers over... And etc and etc. I just sigh and hope it&amp;#39;s over soon and that it won&amp;#39;t mess up my understanding of the plot. This is probably not the case for everyone right? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can understand a map very good and all, but whenever someone describes a route for me, I just tell them to stop and instead give me an address that I can gps instead. I&amp;#39;m equally bad at giving other people directions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would be fun to hear how it&amp;#39;s like for you guys!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do you try to figure out the ending of the book as you read?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am often blindsided by twist endings in books. So often, especially with
popular books, people ask "oh, did you figure out the twist?" and almost always,
I did not. The thing is, unless it's a legit "whodunit" type mystery (ie, The
Hunting Party), I don't even really try. Literally three times…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r44d3o/do_you_try_to_figure_out_the_ending_of_the_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r44d3o/do_you_try_to_figure_out_the_ending_of_the_book/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 16:18:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am often blindsided by twist endings in books. So often, especially with popular books, people ask &amp;quot;oh, did you figure out the twist?&amp;quot; and almost always, I did not. The thing is, unless it&amp;#39;s a legit &amp;quot;whodunit&amp;quot; type mystery (ie, The Hunting Party), I don&amp;#39;t even really try. Literally three times this year, I was like &amp;quot;OMG they were dead!?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was feeling like it makes me dumb or unobservant for not picking up certain clues, but I think I just focus on what is happening and enjoy the ride. I don&amp;#39;t necessarily treat a book like a puzzle to solve, but I&amp;#39;m wondering how others approach it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Advice for becoming an adult]]></title><description><![CDATA[Look, I’m 24 years old and I pretty much think I have problems with ,growing
old’ and would like to read a book which gives me advice how to handle that time
between childhood and adulthood. Like for example preparing me, that my parents
will actually die in a couple of years. Or giving me advice,…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r3qowk/advice_for_becoming_an_adult/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r3qowk/advice_for_becoming_an_adult/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 14:15:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Look, I’m 24 years old and I pretty much think I have problems with ,growing old’ and would like to read a book which gives me advice how to handle that time between childhood and adulthood. Like for example preparing me, that my parents will actually die in a couple of years. Or giving me advice, how to handle all the possibilities and issues of getting older. Any book suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Acclaimed Spanish writer Almudena Grandes dies]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3vp5x/acclaimed_spanish_writer_almudena_grandes_dies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3vp5x/acclaimed_spanish_writer_almudena_grandes_dies/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 11:29:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Xeelee Sequence helped me enjoy reading again]]></title><description><![CDATA[Over the past year (probably longer), I've been struggling with depression and
enjoying a lot of things I previously enjoyed. Video games, movies, music,
reading. I was getting back into reading after getting my kindle around 2 years
ago and was able to read some older sci-fi I enjoyed, and new…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3kzfx/the_xeelee_sequence_helped_me_enjoy_reading_again/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3kzfx/the_xeelee_sequence_helped_me_enjoy_reading_again/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:41:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past year (probably longer), I&amp;#39;ve been struggling with depression and enjoying a lot of things I previously enjoyed. Video games, movies, music, reading. I was getting back into reading after getting my kindle around 2 years ago and was able to read some older sci-fi I enjoyed, and new stuff I hadn&amp;#39;t read. Around a year ago or more though depression started hitting me harder than normal and I found it hard to read as much, or enjoy what I was reading. I know I made a previous post a while back about new sci-fi vs old sci-fi and their differences as I wasn&amp;#39;t a fan of what I was reading much. I dropped a few books in a row. I started reading some older stuff as well, and was not getting much out of it either. I believe part of this may have been due to just a string of bad luck of picking things I ended up not enjoying (sad as one of these was by Asimov and I love his Foundation Trilogy).   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently got a new job and have been able to listen to audiobooks which really help to pass the time. I was really excited but having listened to about 5 books now I was surprised that I really wasn&amp;#39;t super into any of them. I felt bad as I thought I was just incapable of enjoying stories as much anymore, or my standards somehow randomly shot through the roof and now *everything* was just so cliche, or many plot points felt so childish and dumb for any reason. I was getting pretty upset by this. I&amp;#39;ve always wanted to try newer sci-fi, and find some sort of large scale series that I could get into. Epic sci-fi always seemed so appealing to me but the few series I tried that were modern I just couldn&amp;#39;t get into. Finally I listened to the audiobook of Raft.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not going to say this is some milestone of literature, or some incredible feat of writing. I will simply say that I found a lot of joy in listening to this book. I enjoyed the strange world they were in, and the simple adventure story it followed. Something about it broke open my shell and allowed me to actually enjoy what I was listening to. I followed it up just this weekend by reading Timelike Infinity and I enjoyed it even more than Raft. I now definitely plan to read the rest of the series and feel like, even if I don&amp;#39;t find it the highest literature or the best writing I&amp;#39;ve read, it has had fun stories and an interesting universe that has been extremely pleasurable to read.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mainly wanted to write this to get this out because I&amp;#39;m just very happy at the moment that I finally found a (somewhat) modern sci-fi, large scale series that I&amp;#39;m actually finally interested in following through with reading and getting me out of my reading rut. Has anyone else had these types of moments where for some reason you just felt like you could not enjoy reading for some reason or another until some book helped you out of that rut, whether it was one of your favorites or not? What do you normally do when you do find yourself in one of these ruts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kindred Film Adaptation?]]></title><description><![CDATA[A few months back, I read Kindred by Octavia E. Butler. I first picked it up
because I was intrigued by the time travel aspect. As I read it, it definitely
got me thinking about aspects of racism and slavery that I never considered
before.

I really wonder why this hasn't been adapted into a film…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3qavl/kindred_film_adaptation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3qavl/kindred_film_adaptation/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 07:09:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few months back, I read Kindred by Octavia E. Butler. I first picked it up because I was intrigued by the time travel aspect. As I read it, it definitely got me thinking about aspects of racism and slavery that I never considered before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really wonder why this hasn&amp;#39;t been adapted into a film yet. I know adapting books to films is hard enough, and with this one especially, you&amp;#39;d really need the right team of people. But it was first published in the 70&amp;#39;s, and it&amp;#39;s still such a timely story. So why no adaptation? Does Octavia E. Butler&amp;#39;s estate not want that, that&amp;#39;s the only reason I can think of. I&amp;#39;m positive that in the right hands, this could make for an excellent film, or even a miniseries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you all think? Do you want to see this book on the big/small screen?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: I&amp;#39;m looking more into it, and I see that as of March 2021, a pilot has been ordered by FX. So if all goes well, looks like this will be happening after all. 🙂&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[George Orwell: how romantic walks with girlfriends inspired Nineteen Eighty-Four]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3udbw/george_orwell_how_romantic_walks_with_girlfriends/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3udbw/george_orwell_how_romantic_walks_with_girlfriends/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 05:35:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Brontës, the Shelleys, Kingsley and Martin Amis: new research suggests literary relatives share similar writing styles]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3hjtz/the_brontës_the_shelleys_kingsley_and_martin_amis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3hjtz/the_brontës_the_shelleys_kingsley_and_martin_amis/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 03:23:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Favorite Novel Written by a Poet?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've read On Earth We're Briefly Gorgeous by Ocean Vuong, and since then I have
become amazed by the prose poets are able to write. The way they convey their
thoughts and feelings is, to me, out of this world. Don't mind me, I love
poetry, but seeing these artists take on a novel length project…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3hmr3/favorite_novel_written_by_a_poet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3hmr3/favorite_novel_written_by_a_poet/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 02:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve read On Earth We&amp;#39;re Briefly Gorgeous by Ocean Vuong, and since then I have become amazed by the prose poets are able to write. The way they convey their thoughts and feelings is, to me, out of this world. Don&amp;#39;t mind me, I love poetry, but seeing these artists take on a novel length project while still keeping the quality and style of their own writing is simply masterful. Ocean Vuong is one of my favorite poets, and reading his novel I could not stop thinking about how he adapted to the medium so well.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering what are some of your favorites, and why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[If you've never read Gene Wolfe you should give him a go.]]></title><description><![CDATA[He's arguably one of, if not the best science fiction writer/s. He also does
absolutely fantastic fantasy as well. He's got a very dense style that can be
difficult to get into, and his books are meant as rereads. Give them a try
though, you won't regret it.

His work on The Book of the new sun…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3ppo7/if_youve_never_read_gene_wolfe_you_should_give/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3ppo7/if_youve_never_read_gene_wolfe_you_should_give/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 28 Nov 2021 02:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;He&amp;#39;s arguably one of, if not the best science fiction writer/s. 
He also does absolutely fantastic fantasy as well. He&amp;#39;s got a very dense style that can be difficult to get into, and his books are meant as rereads. Give them a try though, you won&amp;#39;t regret it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His work on The Book of the new sun tetralogy (cycle?) Is beyond inspiring. He creates a world which is something more than it seems at first description. Every seems both a lie and the truth at the same time, does the main character really reverse death or was the recipient really dead, or merely wounded? Plus the world building is magical, Urth a planet with a sun so close to death the stars are visible in the daytime sky. It&amp;#39;s fantastic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His fantasy works like The WizardKnight, and Latro in the Mist are beyond good as well. So if you&amp;#39;re not down with sci fi a good Arthurian tale my be just what you need. Or a story of a Roman soldier who loses his memory after a head wound but gains the ability to see God&amp;#39;s and mythical creatures. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also the man invented the process to cook Pringles, so we owe him some respect regardless.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to read poetry]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm uninitiated, but I assume that a poetry book can't be tackled like a regular
book, or is it?

I don't think I would enjoy the book if I had to read the same page over and
over again without a specific strategy. What kind of method do you use, or with
your experience, what works best to extract…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3f7wq/how_to_read_poetry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3f7wq/how_to_read_poetry/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m uninitiated, but I assume that a poetry book can&amp;#39;t be tackled like a regular book, or is it?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t think I would enjoy the book if I had to read the same page over and over again without a specific strategy. What kind of method do you use, or with your experience, what works best to extract and truly digest as much as possible from the text?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[In need of some philosophy books (16M)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Good morning everyone,

I'm getting interested in philosophy and I'd like some books to start. Since I'm
quite young I'd start with some easy books, but I don't mean high school books,
even some university ones would be good to start.

I spend almost all my free time thinking (also OVERthinking) so…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r3cyg1/in_need_of_some_philosophy_books_16m/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r3cyg1/in_need_of_some_philosophy_books_16m/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good morning everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m getting interested in philosophy and I&amp;#39;d like some books to start. Since I&amp;#39;m quite young I&amp;#39;d start with some easy books, but I don&amp;#39;t mean high school books, even some university ones would be good to start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I spend almost all my free time thinking (also OVERthinking) so I thought I could start reading philosophy books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d like to learn more about Greek philosophers, but since their books might be too difficult to start I&amp;#39;m here asking for some suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My favourite book is 1984 by George Orwell atm, I really like nonconformist books. I found it easy to understand it. Plato interest me but it&amp;#39;s probably too difficult.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for reading, I&amp;#39;m here for your suggestions!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Seven Husbands Of Evelyne Hugo]]></title><description><![CDATA[This book was BRILLIANT. I really loved Evelyne as a character and it was
fascinating to read about her life. She was so real, like a friend. It’s the
kind of story that sticks with you for weeks after you’ve read it. The author
really did it! Have you read it? Are you planning to? What did you…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3g955/the_seven_husbands_of_evelyne_hugo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3g955/the_seven_husbands_of_evelyne_hugo/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book was BRILLIANT. I really loved Evelyne as a character and it was fascinating to read about her life. She was so real, like a friend. It’s the kind of story that sticks with you for weeks after you’ve read it. The author really did it! Have you read it? Are you planning to? What did you think of it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What book had you changing your real life habits?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm rereading The Expanse series. The loving descriptions of large amounts of
coffee consumed by the crew have this espresso shooter craving big, steaming
cups. I may not have a spaceship or deadly missions on the edge of what's known,
but I can sip for a while and ponder the universe. How about…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3kash/what_book_had_you_changing_your_real_life_habits/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3kash/what_book_had_you_changing_your_real_life_habits/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m rereading The Expanse series. The loving descriptions of large amounts of coffee consumed by the crew have this espresso shooter craving big, steaming cups. I may not have a spaceship or deadly missions on the edge of what&amp;#39;s known, but I can sip for a while and ponder the universe. How about you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What’s one book (or series) you can read endlessly no matter what age or how many times you’ve read it before?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have a couple books that I can read over and over again, yet never get tired
of. The Harry Potter series is one for me because the story is so wonderful and
I always pick up on new things and hidden references. Plus, it’s kind of
nostalgic.

The Virgin Suicides is another one. I adore how the book…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r38amr/whats_one_book_or_series_you_can_read_endlessly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r38amr/whats_one_book_or_series_you_can_read_endlessly/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 23:32:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a couple books that I can read over and over again, yet never get tired of. The Harry Potter series is one for me because the story is so wonderful and I always pick up on new things and hidden references. Plus, it’s kind of nostalgic. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Virgin Suicides is another one. I adore how the book was written. So different and I always feel a different type of emotion depending on where I’m at in my life. It’s never the same emotions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last is The Messenger. This book is so pure, wholehearted, and has so many life lessons. It’s a quick and addicting read but everyone should read it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Honorable mention: The Giver&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carl Sagan's Cosmos was an awesome read.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Finished it 20 mins ago... Well, it was an awesome listen, the narrator was
outstanding in the majority of the book because of how much enthusiasm and
excitement is conveyed.

Although, the last chapter is what got me especially with how much self-conflict
I've been going through. I doubt a lot of…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3as2r/carl_sagans_cosmos_was_an_awesome_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r3as2r/carl_sagans_cosmos_was_an_awesome_read/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 14:14:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finished it 20 mins ago... Well, it was an awesome listen, the narrator was outstanding in the majority of the book because of how much enthusiasm and excitement is conveyed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although, the last chapter is what got me especially with how much self-conflict I&amp;#39;ve been going through. I doubt a lot of what I&amp;#39;m doing and my goals as being worth. That whole chapter felt like I was being told why I should keep on my educational pursuit.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books from your youth that DID age well]]></title><description><![CDATA[I saw a post about books from your youth that you reread and realized they
didn’t age well. On the flip side, what’s a book that you loved and read at a
young age that you reread recently and still loved? I want to hear all about
your books that stood the test of time and were still just as good in…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r373vp/books_from_your_youth_that_did_age_well/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r373vp/books_from_your_youth_that_did_age_well/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 13:26:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw a post about books from your youth that you reread and realized they didn’t age well. On the flip side, what’s a book that you loved and read at a young age that you reread recently and still loved? I want to hear all about your books that stood the test of time and were still just as good in your 30s as when you were in middle school!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mine is A Wrinkle in Time. I love it so much - I’ve reread it several times since I first read it in fourth grade and it’s really held up!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the most difficult book you have ever read?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I let you define difficult. For me, difficulty may concern the subject matter,
word usage, complexity of a story...or never-ending sentences, as this example
from Woolf's To the Lighthouse shows:

"She was now formidable to behold, and it was only in silence, looking up from
their plates, after she…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r37hmf/what_is_the_most_difficult_book_you_have_ever_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r37hmf/what_is_the_most_difficult_book_you_have_ever_read/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 11:54:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I let you define difficult. For me, difficulty may concern the subject matter, word usage, complexity of a story...or never-ending sentences, as this example from Woolf&amp;#39;s To the Lighthouse shows:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;She was now formidable to behold, and it was only in silence, looking up from their plates, after she had spoken so severely about Charles Tansley, that her daughters, Prue, Nancy, Rose--could sport with infidel ideas which they had brewed for themselves of a life different from hers; in Paris, perhaps; a wilder life; not always taking care of some man or other; for there was in all their minds a mute questioning of deference and chivalry, of the Bank of England and the Indian Empire, of ringed fingers and lace, though to them all there was something in this of the essence of beauty, which called out the manliness in their girlish hearts, and made them...&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is like 2/3 of the whole sentence, but you get the idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t read books known for being extremely difficult to read, like Finnegans Wake, but of the ones I&amp;#39;ve read, Woolf has been the most difficult one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Heroes of Olympus]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know everyone who likes mythology has probably heard of Percy Jackson but
there’s a continuation of the series called Heroes of Olympus that not as many
people seem to know about. I actually prefer this series to the Percy Jackson’s
and want more people to know about it

The books still include…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2z5ue/heroes_of_olympus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2z5ue/heroes_of_olympus/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 07:27:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know everyone who likes mythology has probably heard of Percy Jackson but there’s a continuation of the series called Heroes of Olympus that not as many people seem to know about. I actually prefer this series to the Percy Jackson’s and want more people to know about it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The books still include the regular crew, Percy, Annabeth, Charon but it introduces 5 new heroes, some Greek, some Roman! The Greeks are Leo, Jason and Piper. The Romans are Frank, Hazel and kinda Jason too (the book explains better than I could sos) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These 7 are on the quest that the prophecy that ended the last Percy Jackson book. The people trying to prevent this are Gaia, the earth herself and her children, the giants. Gaia is trying to wake and shake the world of her back and the giants are eliminating anyone trying to lull her back to sleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each book is considerably long with the shortest one being 500 pages and there’s five books but over those 2600 pages, it tells one of the greatest stories I’ve read in awhile. It’s a little bit dumbed down for the younger target audience but still it’s a great story. There’s a fair bit of romance in the books but it doesn’t intrude on the story and helps the characters develop together in a fantastic way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t want to spoil much so im going to end it here but I seriously suggest you give the series a try&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I read Lord of the Rings if I’ve seen the movies?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know the movies pretty well. Being that they’re so long I can’t decide if
knowing what will happen next will taint the reading experience.]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r2xaek/should_i_read_lord_of_the_rings_if_ive_seen_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r2xaek/should_i_read_lord_of_the_rings_if_ive_seen_the/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 27 Nov 2021 03:23:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know the movies pretty well. Being that they’re so long I can’t decide if knowing what will happen next will taint the reading experience.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I just finished "Project Hail Mary" By Andy Weir (Must Read) -no spoilers-]]></title><description><![CDATA[I haven't felt this ecstatic after reading a book since "The Secret History".

3 days ago. I found a reddit link
[https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/the-read-down/the-best-books-of-2021/]
leading to "Penguin Random House" 's list of 2021's best books. I had just
finished a few books and was looking…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2vsq5/i_just_finished_project_hail_mary_by_andy_weir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2vsq5/i_just_finished_project_hail_mary_by_andy_weir/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 22:20:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I haven&amp;#39;t felt this ecstatic after reading a book since &amp;quot;The Secret History&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3 days ago. I found a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/the-read-down/the-best-books-of-2021/&quot;&gt;reddit link&lt;/a&gt; leading to &amp;quot;Penguin Random House&amp;quot; &amp;#39;s list of 2021&amp;#39;s best books. I had just finished a few books and was looking for something good to pass my time. didn&amp;#39;t think I would come in contact with possibly one of my favorite books this year (I finished it in two days).&lt;br/&gt;
Of course, from the first chapter I recognized the same style as &amp;quot;The Martian&amp;quot; and kept wondering if it&amp;#39;s the same author:&lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;it is&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;br/&gt;
I don&amp;#39;t wanna spoil anything. Practically talking about any aspect of it spoils the experience, but to give you the general idea: &amp;quot;A man is in space&amp;quot;. That&amp;#39;s all you need and it&amp;#39;s all in the cover.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The writing is incredible, also very easy to understand. the physics and math is well explained for people who forgot that kind of stuff, and practically a walk in the park for people who retained their highschool-level science education.&lt;br/&gt;
Character building is sublime and you&amp;#39;ll feel tethered to the main Character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes; My voice sparked amidst a paragraph and scared me because I was so invested in the story. My mind used most of it&amp;#39;s power to build the world around it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;#39;t talk much about it. But if you&amp;#39;re looking for a good experience. I dearly recommend this book as it ignited my passion for science and more importantly, for &amp;quot;hard science-fiction&amp;quot;. One thing I learned, The best science fiction books are the ones set in your own time-line. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can&amp;#39;t wait what else will come from my newest favorite author.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To the Author: Thank you, you&amp;#39;ve made me a very happy person&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books from your youth that didn't age well]]></title><description><![CDATA[I was having a discussion with some friends about how a lot of the books we read
as teens or our early twenties just did not age well. It was interesting how we
each had a book that we use to love and now looking back at it we don't know
what the hell we were thinking.

For me it was the Perfect…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2rsh2/books_from_your_youth_that_didnt_age_well/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2rsh2/books_from_your_youth_that_didnt_age_well/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was having a discussion with some friends about how a lot of the books we read as teens or our early twenties just did not age well. It was interesting how we each had a book that we use to love and now looking back at it we don&amp;#39;t know what the hell we were thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me it was the Perfect Chemistry trilogy by Simone Elkeles. I used to adore those books but when I recently went back to re-read the first one I realized it was super racist / white savior complex. Like the first book on it&amp;#39;s own would have probably been fine but when you realize all three brothers are saved from gang life by a rich white girl....it&amp;#39;s not a great look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is a book you use to love but didn&amp;#39;t age well? Why?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I finished reading James Clavell's Shogun]]></title><description><![CDATA[And it is one of the best novels I've ever read and probably the best in the
historical fiction category. It might just be the best story ever told. Never
before has a book gripped me this much. It contains all these devious,
entertaining, bloodthirsty and incomprehensible and unpredictable…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2ve7d/i_finished_reading_james_clavells_shogun/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2ve7d/i_finished_reading_james_clavells_shogun/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 21:30:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;And it is one of the best novels I&amp;#39;ve ever read and probably the best in the historical fiction category. It might just be the best story ever told. Never before has a book gripped me this much. It contains all these devious, entertaining, bloodthirsty and incomprehensible and unpredictable characters who drive the conspiracy and blood laced plot that&amp;#39;s over too soon, despite being a full 1150 pages long and covering over a year. &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;The only problem I had was that the book doesn&amp;#39;t really have a climax. It has mini climaxes and scenes of hair raising tension but no ultimate climax. The resolution is in one page and the final chapter is just a monologue of things &lt;em&gt;that could happen&lt;/em&gt;.Considering the book is already this long,&lt;/span&gt; it&amp;#39;s understandable but I wish Clavell wrote a direct sequel, for the book is a great example of how incredible storytelling can overcome the lack of beautiful prose and a lot of plot and how for a novel to be entertaining, the art of storytelling is the key. The japanese short story writer Ryunosuke Akutagawa had a literary feud in the early 1920s with his contemporary Junichiro Tanizaki over whether story was more important than the way the story was told. Akutagawa held the latter position and I think he was right, after reading this book.10/10 from me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Has a "bad" book ever had a positive impact in your life?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I mean an objectively bad book: poorly written, with weak characters, bad plot,
etc. or a badly conceived non-fiction book that, for some reason, changed your
life in a positive way. In my case it was (supposedly) non-fiction: Chariots of
the Gods. I read it as a teenager and even at that time I…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2nuft/has_a_bad_book_ever_had_a_positive_impact_in_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2nuft/has_a_bad_book_ever_had_a_positive_impact_in_your/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:47:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean an objectively bad book: poorly written, with weak characters, bad plot, etc. or a badly conceived non-fiction book that, for some reason, changed your life in a positive way. In my case it was (supposedly) non-fiction: Chariots of the Gods. I  read it as a teenager and even at that time I considered the author&amp;#39;s arguments to be weak and his conclusions far-fetched. However, it turns out that at that time I was a serious catholic boy who never questioned the standard interpretation of the Bible. That book was the first time I saw someone showing a different &amp;quot;historical&amp;quot; view of the OT. It was actually the first step that led me to actually read the Bible in a critical way, and later to my current atheism (that&amp;#39;s a plus, in my opinion). In addition, I was interested in science and it happens that the book had an equation! The relativistic formula for time dilation. Independently of whatever bs the author was pushing, that formula blew my mind, and started a chain of events that eventually led to a PhD in Physics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[All The Light We Cannot See]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pulitzer Prize winner. I didn't think this one would appeal to me but I decided
to give it a chance and I'm so glad I did. It takes place in the period of the
rise of Hitler to the bitter defeat. Both at times darky disturbing and touching
tracing a young German boy and a young French blind girl…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2othc/all_the_light_we_cannot_see/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2othc/all_the_light_we_cannot_see/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 19:04:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pulitzer Prize winner. I didn&amp;#39;t think this one would appeal to me but I decided to give it a chance and I&amp;#39;m so glad I did.  It takes place in the period of the rise of Hitler to the bitter defeat. Both at times darky disturbing and touching tracing a young German boy and a young French blind girl until their lives intersect in an almost surreal manner. The writer has a very daring, almost confusing way of mixing the chronology but it works perfectly as the story unfolds. You will read of the true horror of Nazi Germany interwoven in the story and really an extraordinary young blind girl who never stops trying. Those who read it any thoughts ?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I finished reading Demons by Dostoevsky yesterday and I'm extremely sad]]></title><description><![CDATA[I really wanted the book to end by the time I was starting the third part. But
after a couple of chapters in, I really fell in love with the book once again.
But the last couple of chapters were really heartbreaking. I didn't realize that
the characters had become my friends and it would be this…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2mi0j/i_finished_reading_demons_by_dostoevsky_yesterday/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2mi0j/i_finished_reading_demons_by_dostoevsky_yesterday/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 18:30:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really wanted the book to end by the time I was starting the third part. But after a couple of chapters in, I really fell in love with the book once again. But the last couple of chapters were really heartbreaking. I didn&amp;#39;t realize that the characters had become my friends and it would be this hard to bear. I cried immediately after finishing it. And the sadness hasn&amp;#39;t still diminished.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I read “The Song of Achilles” for the first time, and WOW.]]></title><description><![CDATA[It was incredibly emotional, detailed, and just so good. I’m not gonna lie, I
cried at the end, just because the storytelling is so powerful at explaining the
grief, guilt and sadness that Patroclus has, and the pain that Achilles goes
through. It so damn good. My experience was enhanced by…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2jgw8/i_read_the_song_of_achilles_for_the_first_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r2jgw8/i_read_the_song_of_achilles_for_the_first_time/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 16:38:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was incredibly emotional, detailed, and just so good.  I’m not gonna lie, I cried at the end, just because the storytelling is so powerful at explaining the grief, guilt and sadness that Patroclus has, and the pain that Achilles goes through.  It so damn good.  My experience was enhanced by listening to “Achilles, Come Down” by Gang of Youths, which made the emotional scenes just so much more impactful and tear-jerking.  It really shows the internal struggles that Patroclus goes through near the ending of the story, culminating in the bittersweet ending of Patroclus pouring his heart out, reminiscing on his own memories of Achilles to Thetis, which shows the love and bond that the two had.  God, this was an incredible book and I wish I could read it again for the first time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What are your Top 3 books you'd re-read before you die?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi ppl!

What are your TOP 3 books you would like to re read before you die?

I've never really been a reader in my life but I want to change that.

Could you recommend anything awesome?

anything is fine! any genre!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r2g8bw/what_are_your_top_3_books_youd_reread_before_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r2g8bw/what_are_your_top_3_books_youd_reread_before_you/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 15:26:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi ppl!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are your TOP 3 books you would like to re read before you die?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never really been a reader in my life but I want to change that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Could you recommend anything awesome?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;anything is fine! any genre!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Here is a list of 100 free classic Christmas ebooks I've compiled from Project Gutenberg - (plus 1000+ other free books). Please enjoy :)]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r1yss4/here_is_a_list_of_100_free_classic_christmas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r1yss4/here_is_a_list_of_100_free_classic_christmas/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 02:01:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA['It was pretty overdue': Boise library book returned 110 years after being checked out]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r257u9/it_was_pretty_overdue_boise_library_book_returned/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/r257u9/it_was_pretty_overdue_boise_library_book_returned/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 21:30:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should I read dune?!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ok, so I recently watched the movie and I quite liked it. I know the book series
is huge, and I've never really read any book series before, so that's something
to take into consideration.

To help with the suggestions, my favorite books are Steppenwolf, One Hundred
Years of Solitude and the…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r206t0/should_i_read_dune/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/r206t0/should_i_read_dune/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 25 Nov 2021 19:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, so I recently watched the movie and I quite liked it. I know the book series is huge, and I&amp;#39;ve never really read any book series before, so that&amp;#39;s something to take into consideration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To help with the suggestions, my favorite books are Steppenwolf, One Hundred Years of Solitude and the Karamazov Brothers. In terms of author, Dostoievski is probably my favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think I&amp;#39;ve only read one Sci fi book and it was tiny: Time Machine, by HG Wells, which I really enjoyed. I think I might want to get into Sci-fi, but I don&amp;#39;t know if Dune is a good start. I have no particular problem with long books though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Should I go for it?!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>