<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 02 Jul 2021 04:28:37 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[I am Paul Theroux, travel writer and author of 56 books—AMA.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m the author of many highly acclaimed travelogues and novels, including The
Great Railway Bazaar, The Mosquito Coast, On the Plain of Snakes, and Under the
Wave at Waimea
[https://www.hmhbooks.com/shop/books/Under-the-Wave-at-Waimea/9780358446286]. In
2015, I was awarded a Royal Medal from the…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n20yaj/i_am_paul_theroux_travel_writer_and_author_of_56/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n20yaj/i_am_paul_theroux_travel_writer_and_author_of_56/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 21:37:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m the author of many highly acclaimed travelogues and novels, including The Great Railway Bazaar, The Mosquito Coast, On the Plain of Snakes, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hmhbooks.com/shop/books/Under-the-Wave-at-Waimea/9780358446286&quot;&gt;Under the Wave at Waimea&lt;/a&gt;. In 2015, I was awarded a Royal Medal from the Royal Geographical Society for “the encouragement of geographical discovery through travel writing.” My books, The Old Patagonian Express: By Train through the Americas, and The Mosquito Coast were both nominated for the American Book Award. Many of my books have been made into films and series including The Mosquito Coast, which is now an Apple TV series starring my nephew, Justin Theroux. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about me here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paultheroux.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.paultheroux.com/&lt;/a&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/paultheroux_?lang=en&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/paultheroux_?lang=en&lt;/a&gt;
Instagram: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/paul.theroux/?hl=en&quot;&gt;https://www.instagram.com/paul.theroux/?hl=en&lt;/a&gt;
Facebook: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Paul-Theroux-1021525607879470/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/Paul-Theroux-1021525607879470/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/i7xqhiaperv61.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/i7xqhiaperv61.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm 19 yo, am I too old to read and appreciate the six of crows books (or the shadow and bone ones)?]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Netflix show turned out average but I'd like to read the books and fill in
the gaps the show left. They could've done better with the world building,
everything seemed so rushed I think they might have missed some important
things.]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1ud6j/im_19_yo_am_i_too_old_to_read_and_appreciate_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1ud6j/im_19_yo_am_i_too_old_to_read_and_appreciate_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:27:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Netflix show turned out average but I&amp;#39;d like to read the books and fill in the gaps the show left. They could&amp;#39;ve done better with the world building, everything seemed so rushed I think they might have missed some important things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is one book you keep going back to?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I read Anna Karenina by Leo Tolstoy and it has stuck with me ever since. Every
time I pick up any book I can't help but draw similarities between the
characters of Anna Karenina. Well to be fair it is quite a long book so I
suppose it's impact has been far greater than any other due to the amount…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1q31q/what_is_one_book_you_keep_going_back_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1q31q/what_is_one_book_you_keep_going_back_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 15:53:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read Anna Karenina by Leo Tolstoy and it has stuck with me ever since. Every time I pick up any book I can&amp;#39;t help but draw similarities between the characters of Anna Karenina. Well to be fair it is quite a long book so I suppose it&amp;#39;s impact has been far greater than any other due to the amount of time I spent with it. However it is one book that I think will stay with me for a while😄.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Tale of Two Cities is very relevant today.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm reading A Tale of Two Cities, and realizing that we are experiencing the
same sort of institutional decay Dickens criticized in the novel. Monseigneur is
a particularly interesting representation of this decay because he shows how
institutions can be corrupted to the point where they no longer…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1tnb9/a_tale_of_two_cities_is_very_relevant_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1tnb9/a_tale_of_two_cities_is_very_relevant_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 15:28:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m reading A Tale of Two Cities, and realizing that we are experiencing the same sort of institutional decay Dickens criticized in the novel. Monseigneur is a particularly interesting representation of this decay because he shows how institutions can be corrupted to the point where they no longer serve their intended purpose.  I couldn&amp;#39;t help but think about our media, and how they are so corrupted by ideology that they lost touch with reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They think they are Madame Defarge, when really they are Monseigneur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can we please talk about Leonardo da vinci's biography by Walter Isaacson]]></title><description><![CDATA[I just finished reading this amazing book and it was genuinely one of my
greatest reads. Walter Isaacson, the master biographer, brilliantly shows us the
life of a genius, whose interests ranged from planetary motion to as eccentric
as "analysis of a woodpecker's tongue". You read that right. One…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1jchh/can_we_please_talk_about_leonardo_da_vincis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1jchh/can_we_please_talk_about_leonardo_da_vincis/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 11:25:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading this amazing book and it was genuinely one of my greatest reads. Walter Isaacson, the master biographer, brilliantly  shows us the life of a genius, whose interests ranged from planetary motion to as eccentric as &amp;quot;analysis of a woodpecker&amp;#39;s tongue&amp;quot;. You read that right. One cannot help but marvel at the genius of Leonardo and appreciate the calibre of his mind! Had he published his works, he would have deservingly been credited with the discovery of friction, Bernoulli&amp;#39;s laws, Newton&amp;#39;s third law, functioning of the aortic valve and the scientific method. He was centuries ahead of his time and his fascinating notebooks are filled with beautiful drawings of anatomy, which have been explained in a simple manner by Walter Isaacson. Science aside, I don&amp;#39;t think I need to mention his world famous paintings like Mona lisa, the last supper and my favourite, Saint John the Baptist. He was as much as an artist as a scientist and had a intense curiosity about everything in the world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are  some key ideas I learned from the book which I&amp;#39;m surely going to implement in my own life:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;1)  Be curious. Be relentlessly curious about everything. It can be as vague as  &amp;quot;inspecting the tongue of a woodpecker&amp;quot; and as serious as understanding the way light from the sun reaches the planets&amp;quot;. Just have a relentless  and a random curiosity about everything life has to offer and be a seeker of knowledge.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2)  Seek knowledge not to make a profit or boast, but for its own sake. Seek knowledge to appreciate and enjoy life. &amp;quot;Not all knowledge has to be useful. Sometimes it can for pure pleasure&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;3)   Retain  a child-like sense of wonder. Don a mask of simplicity and like a child, look at the world as a canvas full of colours and scenes to be drawn upon.

4)  Always wonder about why things are the way they are. We may appreciate the blue sky, but we never reflect on why the sky is blue. Leonardo did. And so did Einstein.

5)  Observe! Observe everything and enjoy movement, silence and flow of nature around you.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6)  Go down rabbit holes that amaze you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7)  Be fearless about changing your opinions as you gather new insights and let go of your past knowledge if new facts disapprove it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;8)  Be a perfectionist. Don&amp;#39;t settle for  &amp;quot;good enough&amp;quot;.  Delay projects if you feel they are not perfect. Leonardo carried Mona Lisa and Adoration of the Magi with him even during his final moments, always ready for a new stroke of the brush. Likewise, Steve jobs made sure the circuit boards of the first Macintosh looked beautiful, even though nobody was going to see them. &amp;quot;Real artists care about the beauty of the parts unseen&amp;quot;.

9) Create not only for others and for profit, but for your personal joy.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) Collaborate. One man can never surpass what 100 men can do together. Singular vision may be important, but execution is often best with a team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;11) Take notes about things that inspire you

12) Be open to mysteries. Not everything needs sharp lines and well definitions. Had that been the case, the beautiful Sfumato so vivid in Mona Lisa would never exist ( The renowned &amp;quot;seductive&amp;quot; smile of Mona Lisa is accomplished through a Leonardo special technique called Sfumato)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s it. I hope you guys found this valuable. Have a good day:))&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does your own personal circle read?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm not talking about friends we have online, I mean your own friends and family
in person, do they actually read or you the lone book worm? My own personal
circle says they are just not good readers so they don't read books which leaves
me all alone when it comes to discussing books except for…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n17cnx/does_your_own_personal_circle_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n17cnx/does_your_own_personal_circle_read/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 05:29:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not talking about friends we have online, I mean your own friends and family in person, do they actually read or you the lone book worm?  My own personal circle says they are just not good readers so they don&amp;#39;t read books which leaves me all alone when it comes to discussing books except for reddit. I&amp;#39;m wondering if most people aren&amp;#39;t really that into reading compared to watching movies and TV shows?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Easy reads that feel like a warm hug]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m going through a really difficult time right now and just need to be
distracted from the pain. I recently read The House in the Cerulean Sea and wish
I hadn’t read it yet so I could read it now, as it’s exactly the type of book I
need. Looking for other fun books that are full of life, joy, and…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1gs9p/easy_reads_that_feel_like_a_warm_hug/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1gs9p/easy_reads_that_feel_like_a_warm_hug/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going through a really difficult time right now and just need to be distracted from the pain. I recently read The House in the Cerulean Sea and wish I hadn’t read it yet so I could read it now, as it’s exactly the type of book I need. Looking for other fun books that are full of life, joy, and hope. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Going into a rehab program and can only bring books, all my “books” are on audible and I can’t bring anything “smart” to listen on. Not looking for charity, just guidance would be amazing.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve written a good bit on Reddit but this is by far the most uneasy I’ve felt
about a post. I started to create another account but decided that if anything,
being able to see my profile and history of activity could help show that this
is genuine and not just some one and done account.

So I’m…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1gwe3/going_into_a_rehab_program_and_can_only_bring/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1gwe3/going_into_a_rehab_program_and_can_only_bring/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve written a good bit on Reddit but this is by far the most uneasy I’ve felt about a post. I started to create another account but decided that if anything, being able to see my profile and history of activity could help show that this is genuine and not just some one and done account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m going into a 60-day program, state funded and free (which is amazing), and I’ve a pack list of what I can and can’t bring. All the hygenics, 7 days of clothes, etc. I’ve got. But the line that hits me is the last.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last line of things to bring are comfort items. “Photos, books, letters”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really have any photos or letters, the few I have just make me sad so I figure they’re best left home. But as audible books have been my escape for so long, I feel like books are one thing that could mean a lot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know we’ll have counseling throughout each weekday (not sure about weekends), and a gym to work out in once a day, but due to covid they’ve suspended any visitation from family, any leaving the site, so for 60 days it’s just me and the 13 other people in there with me. I plan and hope to make friends, but even with friends there’s only so much time you can spend before you just want to read a book and escape to another world for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about the library but that’s a no go as there’s no way to return them, or even extend the rental from inside as internet and such is non-grata.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I was wondering if someone had any advice? I imagine there has to be people with books they wouldn’t care to get rid of, I know when I read Game of Thrones I kept forgetting to bring it to work and I’d just buy another copy cause I couldn’t wait my whole shift to read the next chapter. I must’ve ended up with 2-3 copies of each book and probably four copies of the first one. That was years ago though when I was still working as a paramedic and could afford to buy a book just to avoid having to go all day without reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh how times have changed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice, recommendations, or thoughts would be truly appreciated. I’ll be honest, I’m absolutely terrified at the idea of doing this but frankly I’m out of options and this is my last hope of getting things together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if anyone’s spent time in a similar setting I’d love to hear any advice or thoughts you have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fantasy that has protagonists aged mid 20s and up]]></title><description><![CDATA[I love fantasy but am very tired of reading ab teenagers. I've read lotr and
asoiaf. I want to explore a new world :)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n14sc8/fantasy_that_has_protagonists_aged_mid_20s_and_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n14sc8/fantasy_that_has_protagonists_aged_mid_20s_and_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:57:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love fantasy but am very tired of reading ab teenagers. I&amp;#39;ve read lotr and asoiaf.
I want to explore a new world :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fantasy romance (Steamy book are ON the table)]]></title><description><![CDATA[As we all know lockdown has us lonely and in need of some good old fashioned
steaminess. I would love a fantasy romance with preferably some more adult/sexy
bits. I’ve just finished a pirate romance and I loved it and I need more!
Hopefully I’ll find my perfect next read on here!!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n138k3/fantasy_romance_steamy_book_are_on_the_table/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n138k3/fantasy_romance_steamy_book_are_on_the_table/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 18:42:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we all know lockdown has us lonely and in need of some good old fashioned steaminess. I would love a fantasy romance with preferably some more adult/sexy bits. I’ve just finished a pirate romance and I loved it and I need more! Hopefully I’ll find my perfect next read on here!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Study shows printed books are still preferred to e-books]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n134y4/study_shows_printed_books_are_still_preferred_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n134y4/study_shows_printed_books_are_still_preferred_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:34:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Teacher claims that fantasy isn't "Literature"]]></title><description><![CDATA[Okay, so I'm a high-school student in the Netherlands. I got back into reading
just a couple of months ago and I read a lot of fantasy in English (currently
reading mistborn). A few days ago, I was interested in seeing if there are any
fantasy classics from the Netherlands. So I looked up online, to…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n11u0f/teacher_claims_that_fantasy_isnt_literature/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n11u0f/teacher_claims_that_fantasy_isnt_literature/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 12:41:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, so I&amp;#39;m a high-school student in the Netherlands. I got back into reading just a couple of months ago and I read a lot of fantasy in English (currently reading mistborn). A few days ago, I was interested in seeing if there are any fantasy classics from the Netherlands. So I looked up online, to see if there is some kind of &amp;quot;Dutch Tolkien&amp;quot;. I couldn&amp;#39;t find a lot, so I went and asked my Dutch Literature teacher if there is a fantasy genre in Dutch literature and if she knows of a &amp;quot;Dutch Tolkien&amp;quot;. She told me bluntly that I shouldn&amp;#39;t read fantasy and that she doesn&amp;#39;t consider it to be &amp;quot;real literature&amp;quot;. She basically thinks that Tolkien&amp;#39;s books aren&amp;#39;t &amp;quot;real literature&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That teacher is one of the biggest gatekeepers I know. She keeps rambling about how sad it is that kids don&amp;#39;t read much anymore and then she literally claims that certain genres shouldn&amp;#39;t be read. She&amp;#39;s also one of those people who say that listening to audiobooks doesn&amp;#39;t count as reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I&amp;#39;m just gonna keep reading my &amp;quot;not real literature&amp;quot; and my teacher can continue being an ignorant gatekeeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m looking for a book with secrets doors, rooms, underground passageway, and a mystery to solve !]]></title><description><![CDATA[After reading inheritance game I feel deep into it. The concept of solving
mysteries and looking for clues really brought an interest in me. I’ve been
trying to find something similar but failed. So if anyone know any books that
have that concept please let me know !]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0sphc/im_looking_for_a_book_with_secrets_doors_rooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0sphc/im_looking_for_a_book_with_secrets_doors_rooms/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:47:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After reading inheritance game I feel deep into it. The concept of solving mysteries and looking for clues really brought an interest in me. I’ve been trying to find something similar but failed. So if anyone know any books that have that concept please let me know !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I've recently discovered that my obsession with more has been ruining my passion for reading.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've always loved to read from a young age. It had gotten to a point where I was
reading nearly 100 books a year from many different genres. Once covid started,
I realized that I'd never be able to read everything I wanted to, and it sent me
into an existential, downward spiral. I was paralyzed, and…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0fnpl/ive_recently_discovered_that_my_obsession_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0fnpl/ive_recently_discovered_that_my_obsession_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 03:31:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always loved to read from a young age. It had gotten to a point where I was reading nearly 100 books a year from many different genres. Once covid started, I realized that I&amp;#39;d never be able to read everything I wanted to, and it sent me into an existential, downward spiral. I was paralyzed, and instead of doing the expected and reading even more, I scrutinized my reading speed and how many pages I needed to get through each day. When I inevitably failed to reach my goals, I was disappointed and began to lose the love of reading I had in the past. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I began to come to terms with this. Stemming from the realization that life itself is finite. It&amp;#39;s funny, I obviously always knew that life is fleeting, but I never fully understood this. After reading some works by ancient stoic philosophers I realized, that quantity is never the answer. A person that reads few books well, is often much wiser than one that reads many books hastily. I&amp;#39;m sure this &amp;quot;profound&amp;quot; realization is trivial for a lot of you, but it has certainly helped me to grapple with the impending sense of &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not moving fast enough and that&amp;#39;s a bad thing.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your time when you read, life and books are beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I want to read about greek mythology]]></title><description><![CDATA[I want to read a book about all those famous stories of greek mythology and
their gods, but don't know where to begin. Is there a book that contains all the
stories, or are there many? I have no idea.

Thank you in advance.]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0cw83/i_want_to_read_about_greek_mythology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0cw83/i_want_to_read_about_greek_mythology/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 02:25:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to read a book about all those famous stories of greek mythology and their gods, but don&amp;#39;t know where to begin. Is there a book that contains all the stories, or are there many? I have no idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Suggest me a book from male point of view about how to handle a breakup. It would be better if it is in a novel form.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The breakup topic has a monopoly of women as much as I have felt. It will be
quite good if I could get some male advice on this, preferably in a novel or a
story form.

What I really want is a novel where a girl leaves a man who loved her immensely
but not enough by her standards. How did he…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0ingl/suggest_me_a_book_from_male_point_of_view_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0ingl/suggest_me_a_book_from_male_point_of_view_about/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 20:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breakup topic has a monopoly of women as much as I have felt. It will be quite good if I could get some male advice on this, preferably in a novel or a story form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I really want is a novel where a girl leaves a man who loved her immensely but not enough by her standards. How did he overcome that trauma?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S: Something like 500 days of summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DisneyMustPay: authors form task force to fight for missing royalty payments relating to Star Wars/Buffy/Alien/Spider-Man/Stargate/Indiana Jones/and more books and comics]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0keso/disneymustpay_authors_form_task_force_to_fight/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0keso/disneymustpay_authors_form_task_force_to_fight/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just finished Grapes of Wrath by Steinbeck for the first time, what a good book. (Spoilers inside)]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yall, I could not put this book down. I knew it was going to be crazy when they
just glossed over the pig eating the baby. I had to Google to make sure I was
understanding, but obviously this was nothing compared to the rest of the book

I kept reading on hoping somebody, ANYBODY, would get a…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0di8r/just_finished_grapes_of_wrath_by_steinbeck_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0di8r/just_finished_grapes_of_wrath_by_steinbeck_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 16:02:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yall, I could not put this book down. I knew it was going to be crazy when they just glossed over the pig eating the baby. I had to Google to make sure I was understanding, but obviously this was nothing compared to the rest of the book&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I kept reading on hoping somebody, ANYBODY, would get a semblance of a happy ending. Tom, AL, Rose of Sharon, Ma, ANYONE. But I guess sometimes that isn&amp;#39;t how life works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like this book has some current themes as well about the seeds of discontent, about people who are just continously getting stepped on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all I would read it again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Have you ever read Leo Tolstoy's short stories and novellas? Well, now here's your chance with all of them compiled in a free ebook for (as far as I know) the first time! Post your favorites in the comments!]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07yo5/have_you_ever_read_leo_tolstoys_short_stories_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07yo5/have_you_ever_read_leo_tolstoys_short_stories_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:32:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which is the best non-fiction book you have read?]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mznih3/which_is_the_best_nonfiction_book_you_have_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mznih3/which_is_the_best_nonfiction_book_you_have_read/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 07:58:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I am LOVING The Expanse!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Some might disagree (and that’s fine), but I think The Expanse series is so well
written…especially the diverse range of characters and character development.

I’m currently about a little bit less than half-way through Book 3 Abaddon’s
Gate and I just finished reading my 10th chapter in just today…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07b3d/i_am_loving_the_expanse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07b3d/i_am_loving_the_expanse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 07:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some might disagree (and that’s fine), but I think The Expanse series is so well written…especially the diverse range of characters and character development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m currently about a little bit less than half-way through Book 3 &lt;em&gt;Abaddon’s Gate&lt;/em&gt; and I just finished reading my 10th chapter in just today alone — You know you’re enjoying a book after you’ve read 10 chapters in one day without really realizing it; you think, “I must have read 3…maybe 4 chapters at the most”…then you realize it’s actually 10!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like the “setting” of &lt;em&gt;Firefly&lt;/em&gt; and the political intrigue and social “dynamics” of &lt;em&gt;Game of Thrones&lt;/em&gt;, I’m almost positive you’ll love The Expanse!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just read annihilation.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wow. What did i just read? The surreal world of Area X reminded me of an acid
trip. Is there any books similar that focus on discovering and exploring strange
worlds? I already plan on reading Borne by the same author.]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n03f8f/just_read_annihilation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n03f8f/just_read_annihilation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 05:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow. What did i just read? The surreal world of Area X reminded me of an acid trip. Is there any books similar that focus on discovering and exploring strange worlds? I already plan on reading Borne by the same author.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[HELP! I just finished watching Shadow & Bone on Netflix and am craving an epic read that's similar but uhhh... maybe with sex?! ;)]]></title><description><![CDATA[I'm not asking for much, just book suggestions that are similar to Shadow &
Bone. So... great sexual tension, meaningful character arcs, set in a world with
some sort of kingdom/royalty, and doesn't shy away from a sex scene every now
and then....

Thank you in advance!!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n01gf3/help_i_just_finished_watching_shadow_bone_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n01gf3/help_i_just_finished_watching_shadow_bone_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 04:36:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not asking for much, just book suggestions that are similar to Shadow &amp;amp; Bone. So... great sexual tension, meaningful character arcs, set in a world with some sort of kingdom/royalty, and doesn&amp;#39;t shy away from a sex scene every now and then....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[John Le Carré’s The Constant Gardener is a masterpiece.]]></title><description><![CDATA[This is the first title I’ve read from this author and I’m stunned by the skill
of his writing. Unlike other intrigue/thriller novels which rely on withholding
information and a timely reveal at end, Le Carré offers a completely different
experience. What he provides is a series of expanding…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02yzc/john_le_carrés_the_constant_gardener_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02yzc/john_le_carrés_the_constant_gardener_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 03:03:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first title I’ve read from this author and I’m stunned by the skill of his writing. Unlike other intrigue/thriller novels which rely on withholding information and a timely reveal at end, Le Carré offers a completely different experience. What he provides is a series of expanding revelations, impressive in detail and research, combined with fully developed characters whose motivations are sometimes not even known to themselves. I’m about 2/3 of the way in and I never want this ride to end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Blood Meridian: The Greatest Last Paragraph in Literature?]]></title><description><![CDATA[A few days ago, I finished reading Blood Meridian for the first time. I think it
is fair to say that few novels have ever stuck around with me the way Blood
Meridian has. I know it has its fair share of detractors, it’s too meandering,
too violent, too philosophical, etc. To each their own, I cannot…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzzphd/blood_meridian_the_greatest_last_paragraph_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzzphd/blood_meridian_the_greatest_last_paragraph_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:29:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few days ago, I finished reading Blood Meridian for the first time. I think it is fair to say that few novels have ever stuck around with me the way Blood Meridian has. I know it has its fair share of detractors, it’s too meandering, too violent, too philosophical, etc. To each their own, I cannot change your mind. Personally, I thought it was a masterpiece and one of the greatest works of experimental fiction that I have ever read. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think everything which is so powerful about this novel can be summarized in the last paragraph. I had never thought about what my favorite last paragraph was until reading this book. I have probably reread it six times since finishing and cannot help but be drawn back to it. It is one of the most harrowing passages I have ever read and it serves as a fantastic knot for tying together all of the larger themes, ideas, and meanings of the novel. Everything about it is simply perfect. The lyrical repetition in language, the vividness of imagery, the Biblical allusions, and the deeper metaphorical layers of “the dance”. I found it to be brilliant. The passage is branded into my brain and I know I will go back to reread it many more times. It is a great favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What were your thoughts on this final passage? If it did not resonate with you, which final paragraphs have?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[‘There Is a Tension There’: Publishers Draw Fire for Signing Trump Officials]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02xzl/there_is_a_tension_there_publishers_draw_fire_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02xzl/there_is_a_tension_there_publishers_draw_fire_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:29:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Opening a Small-Town Bookstore During the Pandemic Was the Craziest Thing We Ever Did]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzvdvy/opening_a_smalltown_bookstore_during_the_pandemic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzvdvy/opening_a_smalltown_bookstore_during_the_pandemic/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:20:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else find themselves with tons of favorite books but no real favorite author?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have authors that I enjoy, but none that I would really classify as my
"favorite." I have tried reading books from the same authors of course, but
either they become too formulaic over time, or they're enjoyable but not what I
would call a favorite.

I feel a little self-conscious about it because…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzou2z/anyone_else_find_themselves_with_tons_of_favorite/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzou2z/anyone_else_find_themselves_with_tons_of_favorite/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:26:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have authors that I enjoy, but none that I would really classify as my &amp;quot;favorite.&amp;quot; I have tried reading books from the same authors of course, but either they become too formulaic over time, or they&amp;#39;re enjoyable but not what I would call a favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel a little self-conscious about it because reading is my main hobby, and people will sometimes ask me about my favorite authors, but I have none! Am I alone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm Bruce Sterling, I'm a Texan science fiction writer who spends a lot of time in Europe. I'm a cyberpunk, so I'm up to weird mischief. For decades on end, really. AMA]]></title><description><![CDATA[My goal is to wander the earth, stay out of prisons and clinics, and get some
fiction and nonfiction written.Â Â At the moment I'm in Ibiza.Â It's not the
normal Ibiza, because they're under quarantine, but I'm not a normal guy, so I
don't mind their current situation.

I have a new book out called…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzr388/im_bruce_sterling_im_a_texan_science_fiction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzr388/im_bruce_sterling_im_a_texan_science_fiction/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 17:12:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My goal is to wander the earth, stay out of prisons and clinics, and get some fiction and nonfiction written.Â Â 
At the moment I&amp;#39;m in Ibiza.Â  It&amp;#39;s not the normal Ibiza, because they&amp;#39;re under quarantine, but I&amp;#39;m not a normal guy, so I don&amp;#39;t mind their current situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a new book out called &amp;quot;Robot Artists and Black Swans&amp;quot; and it&amp;#39;s got seven stories in it that involve robot artists, black swans, the Shroud of Turin, and other curiosities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/9g60c1k6iqv61.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/9g60c1k6iqv61.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What to read when you don’t like yourself and doubt all your achievements?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yes this does not sound nice but that’s just how I would evaluate my last 5
years of life.

If you have dealt with similar situation and have a few good books that helped
you change the outlook on yourself, feel free to suggest them. Can be nonfiction
psychology or philosophy. Fiction would be fine…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mzn6mw/what_to_read_when_you_dont_like_yourself_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mzn6mw/what_to_read_when_you_dont_like_yourself_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 14:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes this does not sound nice but that’s just how I would evaluate my last 5 years of life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have dealt with similar situation and have a few good books that helped you change the outlook on yourself, feel free to suggest them. Can be nonfiction psychology or philosophy. Fiction would be fine too but I would prefer nonfiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Change My Mind: Reading is much more enjoyable and rewarding if you read slow and don't rush]]></title><description><![CDATA[I used to think in order to read "a lot," you had to first get a stack of books,
and read them all cover to cover. So, in order to get through them, I would just
rush through them resulting in me forgetting everything that I had just read.
This was even more evident when I wanted to tell others…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzc80b/change_my_mind_reading_is_much_more_enjoyable_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzc80b/change_my_mind_reading_is_much_more_enjoyable_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:41:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to think in order to read &amp;quot;a lot,&amp;quot; you had to first get a stack of books, and read them all cover to cover. So, in order to get through them, I would just rush through them resulting in me forgetting everything that I had just read. This was even more evident when I wanted to tell others about what I was currently reading or my thoughts on a particular book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, instead of reading 3-4 books a month, I just read one book every 2-3 weeks. I also forced myself to read slower and be more diligent about taking notes, looking things up, etc. This has made a big difference not only how much I remember, but it has basically made me fall in love with reading all over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry if this sounded lame or whatever, but thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[98 percent of the books that publishers released in 2020 sold fewer than 5,000 copies]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzhksv/98_percent_of_the_books_that_publishers_released/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzhksv/98_percent_of_the_books_that_publishers_released/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 07:48:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone else have trouble with reacting to characters in fiction as if they were real? I'm talking about not being able to watch most comedy shows because I'm full of second hand embarrassment for them, angry when a character is mistreated and doesn't get justice, incredibly sad when they suffer etc?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I hope this is allowed. I've been chewing on it for a long time and I really
want to know if this happens to anyone else and if anyone has advice on how to
manage it.

I'm putting this in books because most of the material I react to is written,
but its all fiction, written, animated, real person…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzba2p/anyone_else_have_trouble_with_reacting_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzba2p/anyone_else_have_trouble_with_reacting_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 07:01:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hope this is allowed. I&amp;#39;ve been chewing on it for a long time and I really want to know if this happens to anyone else and if anyone has advice on how to manage it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m putting this in books because most of the material I react to is written, but its all fiction, written, animated, real person acting with characters in negative situations. I was an avid reader as a child and fictional worlds and characters of all kinds were my escape from a lot of stuff. My life is much better nowadays and I don&amp;#39;t use it to escape reality now, just for enjoyment but I feel like I was so intensely engaged with fiction when I was young that my brain just can&amp;#39;t help but react as if the people and situations are real, that I&amp;#39;ve conditioned myself to react this way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel dumb even saying this. I know they&amp;#39;re not real. I&amp;#39;m very firmly rooted in reality. But the emotional reaction can be so debilitating it makes me avoid reading/watching something that I know will throw my equilibrium off when I need to focus on studying/working/life in general. I can read something and days later be furious/desperately sad for the character that&amp;#39;s suffering. Often I can&amp;#39;t get past that part, can&amp;#39;t read it at all, end up skipping whole chapters/episodes etc. Some I can&amp;#39;t continue with at all. Just this week I&amp;#39;ve put down a book I was really enjoying because the main character had a bone broken by their boyfriend and their father joked with the guy. Horrible yes, but NOT REAL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s especially weird as I&amp;#39;m not prone to over the top displays of emotion in real life. I do have mild, well managed depression and a severe anxiety disorder, but this too is managed by medication and therapy when I need it. It&amp;#39;s probably not helping but I don&amp;#39;t think its majorly influencing my feelings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate this. I love fiction and I hate that this gets in the way of me enjoying it. Please tell me I&amp;#39;m not the only one and what you do to overcome it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Flowers for Algernon.. I'm crushed.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started Flowers for Algernon yesterday and by noon today I was done. Done with
the book and done for.



The entire second half I felt like I was holding my breath, until I finally read
that last fateful line on the last page (which will remain forever etched in my
memory). Once I was finished the…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mze3br/flowers_for_algernon_im_crushed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mze3br/flowers_for_algernon_im_crushed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:57:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started Flowers for Algernon yesterday and by noon today I was done. Done with the book and done for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire second half I felt like I was holding my breath, until I finally read that last fateful line on the last page (which will remain forever etched in my memory). Once I was finished the only thing I could manage to exhale was an uncontrollable barrage of streaming tears. I even went for a walk afterwards to try to make sense of this…experience but it&amp;#39;s been no use. My mind has been numb all day. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That brings me to this post. I haven’t ever written about a book before but I feel that writing this out may help me to fully comprehend it. I&amp;#39;d also love to hear what some of you took away from this masterpiece. I know many people read this book in high school but I wasn’t as lucky. My English teacher was somewhat discouraging and pretty much killed my love for literature… so only now am I getting to read these classics, a decade later. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe the most heartbreaking part of the book to me was that throughout his life Charlie was never able to strike a balance between his intellectual and emotional self. For his entire life leading up to the operation, all he wished for was to be smart. After the operation, he acquired the intellect he’d always wanted but now he found himself emotionally challenged. This process once again reversed itself as his intellect began to deteriorate. He never was able to have both &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can remember two brief moments during which he was somewhat centered: the first during the initial weeks after the operation when he starts falling in love with Alice and still hasn&amp;#39;t come to terms with his genius but this was tainted by his unresolved family issues and confusion about his development. The second was once his intellect began to decline again, when its just him and Alice and he wants to fight to retain his genius, or whatever is left of it at that point. She even tells him, “I’ve just been waiting. You’re about at my level again”. Unfortunately, this moment too, is tarnished by his dread of what is to come. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt that he was never able to find true happiness. And that is what broke me the most. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime around the latter half of the book it became obvious to me that it would not end well for Charlie. But I kept wishing. For something, even the slightest of redemption. It arrived for a moment when the bakery owner and his coworkers accepted him back into their lives but that too was short-lived. Ultimately though, I think we all know that this is how it had to end. I’m glad Keyes decided against a flowery ending - there is nothing about this book that I would change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to end by quoting some passages I thought were particularly poignant: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he confesses his feelings to Alice after the operation but she turns him down - “How does a person go about learning how to act towards another person” This isn’t a remarkable thought on its own but taken into context I thought it was a very profound take on our social nature and the constructs we have built around that nature. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During his argument with Nemur - “Intelligence and education that hasn’t been tempered by human affection isn’t worth a damn”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His last time at the university, when talking to Burt - “I passed your floor on the way up and now I’m passing it on the way down, and I don’t think I’ll be taking this elevator again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he’s with Alice in the end - “And as I lay here with her I could see how important physical love was, how necessary it was for us to be in each other’s arms, giving and taking. The universe was exploding, each particle away from the next, hurtling us into dark and lonely space, eventually tearing us away from each other - child out of the womb, friend away from friend, moving from each other, each through his own pathway toward the goal-box of solitary death. But this was the counterweight, the act of binding and holding.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And last - “please… please don’t let me forget how to read and write”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I read Frankenstein and I was pleasantly surprised at how little I knew of the story.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Everything I “knew” from movies or retellings seemed to be slightly off or
exaggerated. I found it comical how the novel introduced Frankenstein and his
creation in such an odd place and then worked backwards from there. I also found
it interesting how the creature was much less of a traditional…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzcnem/i_read_frankenstein_and_i_was_pleasantly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzcnem/i_read_frankenstein_and_i_was_pleasantly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:35:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything I “knew” from movies or retellings seemed to be slightly off or exaggerated. 
I found it comical how the novel introduced Frankenstein and his creation in such an odd place and then worked backwards from there. I also found it interesting how the creature was much less of a traditional monster than I had expected.
I would HIGHLY recommend. 
What’re your thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Decided to quit playing videogames and read books instead]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys, recently quit playing video games cause I’ve been heavily addicted to
them recently. I guess I’ll start reading books instead during my free time. I
really like fantasy novels such as the inheritance cycle and sci fi novels like
a hitchhikers guide to the galaxy. All suggestions are…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz3bro/decided_to_quit_playing_videogames_and_read_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz3bro/decided_to_quit_playing_videogames_and_read_books/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 01:17:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, recently quit playing video games cause I’ve been heavily addicted to them recently. I guess I’ll start reading books instead during my free time. I really like fantasy novels such as the inheritance cycle and sci fi novels like a hitchhikers guide to the galaxy. All suggestions are appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I’m Brit Bennett, best-selling author of The Mothers and The Vanishing Half. AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’m a writer, reader, and lover of stories. Previous books include The Mothers
and The Vanishing Half. I’m currently working on my third novel, which is about
a girl group. Pandemic hobbies include podcast-walks, alphabetizing my
playlists, and indulging my worst TV habits. Ask me anything!

Proof:…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myzpbz/im_brit_bennett_bestselling_author_of_the_mothers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myzpbz/im_brit_bennett_bestselling_author_of_the_mothers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 22:55:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a writer, reader, and lover of stories. Previous books include The Mothers and The Vanishing Half. I’m currently working on my third novel, which is about a girl group. Pandemic hobbies include podcast-walks, alphabetizing my playlists, and indulging my worst TV habits. Ask me anything!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/sau6q9mv7ru61.png&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/sau6q9mv7ru61.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Reading every night has made me an overall happier person]]></title><description><![CDATA[I know this has been talked about on this sub before (in archived posts) but I
just wanted to share this personal revelation I recently had:

I used to read all the time growing up and then kind of stopped during college
and a few years into grad school because of limited time or other…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mz1rd7/reading_every_night_has_made_me_an_overall/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mz1rd7/reading_every_night_has_made_me_an_overall/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:13:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know this has been talked about on this sub before (in archived posts) but I just wanted to share this personal revelation I recently had:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to read all the time growing up and then kind of stopped during college and a few years into grad school because of limited time or other priorities. For the first half of grad school, I was really anxious and would have trouble falling and staying sleeping too. A couple of years ago (halfway into grad school), I was going on a solo trip and decided to pick a book or two to read while alone on this trip. I picked two thrillers and after this trip, I became addicted to reading more mystery/crime/thriller novels, trying to read at least a little bit each night. Not only does it help me fall asleep but every day I feel a pang of happiness about the fact that I get to return to my exciting book at night and this happiness seems to indirectly affect my general mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also think the Kindle (or e-reader) and the library&amp;#39;s overdrive are the greatest inventions ever because I can read about a book a week without ever having to leave my bed. I also very recently started checking out thriller audiobooks (that I read separately from but in parallel with my nighttime book) from my library to listen to at the gym and it makes my workouts so much more bearable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read for pure enjoyment and it made me realize that finding the right genre(s) for each individual person is so important. Some people may find it hard to get through a book and get turned off of reading for a while but I believe they are just reading the wrong type of book and that there is a genre out there they will get sucked into like I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I had a brief hiatus from thrillers last year to re-read the entire Harry Potter series and that contributed the same amount of happiness and excitement.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do others have similar experiences and thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoughts of a non-Christian on The Brothers Karamazov]]></title><description><![CDATA[I recently finished reading The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky, a
novel that I have been toting around for a while now. I dreaded reading it,
partly out of fear that being someone who is as far removed from the Christian
faith as is culturally possible, I wouldn't connect with some of the…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myx6sv/thoughts_of_a_nonchristian_on_the_brothers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myx6sv/thoughts_of_a_nonchristian_on_the_brothers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:13:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky, a novel that I have been toting around for a while now. I dreaded reading it, partly out of fear that being someone who is as far removed from the Christian faith as is culturally possible, I wouldn&amp;#39;t connect with some of the theological discussions that I suspected would make up most of the book&amp;#39;s content. In short, I was wary of it being something that seeks to &amp;#39;convert&amp;#39; or persuade the reader towards Christianity. To be clear, I was born and raised in a Hindu community, and now consider myself an agnostic when it comes to the Divine Question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, I was very much in the wrong about what the novel is about and what it sets out to achieve, because yes, while it is heavily steeped in Christian imagery and culture (which was inevitable given Fyodor Dostoyevsky&amp;#39;s background), the novel deals with the idea of God and faith in a much more direct, generalized manner, and instead uses the faith merely as a vehicle with which to grapple some seriously troubling existential questions. If you&amp;#39;d permit me, I&amp;#39;d like to start a discussion here about those themes. The two major ideas that the novel seemed to gravitate around were family and faith, and Dostoyevsky intertwined them with each other beautifully, so that the novel essentially asks the question: Is it possible to escape your most base, depraved urges (family), and if yes, then how (faith)? This question is explored in the form of the three titular brothers, and without beating about the bush, I&amp;#39;d like to lay out my thoughts about how the novel accomplishes that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I considered Alyosha and Smerdyakov to be essentially the antithesis of each other. Both of them had (supposedly) the same father, which meant that both of them were equally susceptible to the Karamazovian tendencies of debauchery, hedonism, and reckless self destruction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Alyosha was a man of faith, and despite his faith being tested multiple times throughout the novel by various characters as well as circumstances, he always &lt;em&gt;chose&lt;/em&gt;, consciously, to take the nobler path and bear the suffering that comes with it. One of my favorite bits of the novel is when, after the demise of Father Zosima, his corpse begins to reek terribly, which causes a temporary crisis of faith for his followers. This was an exhilarating turn of events for me, because, as I mentioned, I expected this novel to be very preachy and stern when it came to religion and faith, but I instead found Dostoyevsky willingly putting his characters in circumstances where their belief is challenged by the universe, and the only reason to keep their faith is their choice to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smerdyakov, on the other hand, was a psychopath. He subscribed to Ivan&amp;#39;s philosophy of &amp;quot;everything is permitted&amp;quot; (a philosophy that, ironically, Ivan himself did not fully believe in), and it led to him completely ruining the lives of at least two of his three half-brothers, as well as of course his father. This seemed to be Dostoyevsky straightforwardly telling us that godless/nihilist individuals can and will succumb to their worst impulses. The most interesting character, then, was someone who lay in the middle of this spectrum: Ivan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ivan was a rational, intelligent scholar who wanted to believe wholeheartedly in faith, but could not bring himself to do so because of all the logical as well as existential inconsistencies that doing so caused him to wrestle with. His qualms with faith are best represented in what are two of the novel&amp;#39;s best chapters: &lt;em&gt;The Grand Inquisitor&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Devil&lt;/em&gt;, in which we find the scientific, rational, stripped-down approach of nihilism attacking the more lofty ideas of the Christian faith. Ivan is, however, unable to resolve these issues, causing him to go mad and fall into illness by the end of the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conclude, I was pleasantly surprised by how intelligent and thought-provoking the story was, and I think that Dostoyevsky wanted us to realize that reconciling faith with logic is a Herculean task that will only cause us misery, and rejecting faith is a surefire way to become selfish, egotistical and misanthropic. The only way is to willingly choose to have faith, to be compassionate and sympathetic towards your fellow human beings irrespective of what tragedy may befall you. This is a highly subjective interpretation of course, and I&amp;#39;m thrilled to find out what you took away from it. What does this novel mean to you? What are some chapters or characters or moments or lines that resonate deeply with you? I&amp;#39;d love to have a discussion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Summer job at sea]]></title><description><![CDATA[I’ve got a job on a commercial fishing boat this summer, no TV, no cell service,
no WiFi. I’m going to load up my kindle before I get there. I’m looking for
books that relate to my situation. Top of my list so far are Old Man and the Sea
and Treasure Island.

Anything set on the open ocean,…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz111m/summer_job_at_sea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz111m/summer_job_at_sea/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:50:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve got a job on a commercial fishing boat this summer, no TV, no cell service, no WiFi. I’m going to load up my kindle before I get there. I’m looking for books that relate to my situation. Top of my list so far are Old Man and the Sea and Treasure Island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anything set on the open ocean, hopefully not centered around a struggle for my life (ie Life of Pi or Adrift), will make the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bookworms/fast readers of reddit, question about reading comprehension/speed for nonfictional/educational/textbooks]]></title><description><![CDATA[When reading nonfictional books or textbooks, do you read through each sentence
with a fine-tooth comb (and you still go through it pretty fast because you have
a high?/good? reading comprehension) or do you understand it like idk 60-90% of
what it's saying (a good amount more than just the gist of…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mynjqz/bookwormsfast_readers_of_reddit_question_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mynjqz/bookwormsfast_readers_of_reddit_question_about/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:56:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When reading nonfictional books or textbooks, do you read through each sentence with a fine-tooth comb (and you still go through it pretty fast because you have a high?/good? reading comprehension) or do you understand it like idk 60-90% of what it&amp;#39;s saying (a good amount more than just the gist of it) and move on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that I pick apart almost every word of the sentence. And I think it&amp;#39;s because I&amp;#39;m mostly detailed oriented and meticulous.  Also, while sometimes getting distracted in the process. Like I&amp;#39;ll be like okay this refers to this thing in this example, this means this, that means that, reread, and oh what&amp;#39;s this thing on my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[There is a special place in hell for people whose Goodreads reviews contain spoilers and no spoiler warnings.]]></title><description><![CDATA[The title of this post says what it needs to say but, in honour of the rules, I
will tell you exactly why I came to post this. Be forewarned, only 49% of this
post is sarcasm and, while I have no intention to offend, I also have no
intention not to offend.

Here it goes:

I opened up Goodreads for…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mywhvu/there_is_a_special_place_in_hell_for_people_whose/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mywhvu/there_is_a_special_place_in_hell_for_people_whose/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:17:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The title of this post says what it needs to say but, in honour of the rules, I will tell you exactly why I came to post this. Be forewarned, only 49% of this post is sarcasm and, while I have no intention to offend, I also have no intention not to offend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it goes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I opened up Goodreads for no particular reason. Just quietly scrolling and harming no one. I am on leave today and I can do whatever I like, and all I want to do is a little nothing. Tomorrow is public holiday here, so I’ve given myself a really long weekend. I figured I’d keep things peaceful. I expect that was too much to ask. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across a book trending in the Thriller section - &lt;em&gt;The Moonlight Child&lt;/em&gt; by Karen McQuestion. It’s got a 4.22 rating and that’s quite high, in my estimation, especially for something that probably isn’t literary fiction or destined to be a classic. (But who knows? I haven’t read it, and I could be wildly mistaken.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating aside, I was intrigued by the synopsis, so I read the reviews. Well. Of course I read the reviews. Reviews are vital. A public good, written (usually) by the best among us. A well-written review is invaluable, but reading through them is a dangerous business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, sometimes reviewers are just parading around as Samaritans when they are much more akin to Satan. They remind us how easy it is for vicious psychopaths to review books on Goodreads. These people are the ones that publish reviews that contain spoilers without including spoiler warnings. There is a special place in hell for them. I truly worry for their friends and family. Villains. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will now never read &lt;em&gt;The Moonlight Child&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anyone have a problem with reading too fast?]]></title><description><![CDATA[When I read books I enjoy, my enthusiasm for knowing more of the story forces me
to rush. I would sometimes automatically skip sentences and try to get to the
next part of the story. Does that happen to anyone here and if so, how do you
guys stop it? I feel like I don't get to enjoy the book as I…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my5cwa/anyone_have_a_problem_with_reading_too_fast/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my5cwa/anyone_have_a_problem_with_reading_too_fast/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 05:13:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I read books I enjoy, my enthusiasm for knowing more of the story forces me to rush. I would sometimes automatically skip sentences and try to get to the next part of the story. Does that happen to anyone here and if so, how do you guys stop it? I feel like I don&amp;#39;t get to enjoy the book as I miss some details by rushing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Please recommend me your gentlest books.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've been silently reading this subreddit and am often moved by you
compassionate, intelligent strangers. So I'd thought despite terrible shyness to
ask you all for gentle, comforting books of any genre, fiction or nonfiction. My
favorite go to books for when I'm feeling raw and vulnerable are: The…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myj4id/please_recommend_me_your_gentlest_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myj4id/please_recommend_me_your_gentlest_books/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been silently reading this subreddit and am often moved by you compassionate, intelligent strangers. So I&amp;#39;d thought despite terrible shyness to ask you  all for gentle, comforting books of any genre, fiction or nonfiction. My favorite go to books for when I&amp;#39;m feeling raw and vulnerable are:  The History of Love by Nicole Krauss , The Vulnerable Observer by Ruth Behar, and Salt by Nayyirah Waheed. I know this is a pretty vague request, so I hope my go-tos provide some guidance to what I&amp;#39;m looking for. I am open to anything. Apologies and Thanks in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[What's your most controversial opinion on either books or on a specific book?]]></title><description><![CDATA[Was having a conversation with a friend and this topic came up so it got me
thinking, and now I'm curious as to what other people have to say. My own
personal hot take is that Anna Karenina is a terrible novel and that she should
have been hit by a train earlier to spare us all the BS. That or every…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myjw4t/whats_your_most_controversial_opinion_on_either/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myjw4t/whats_your_most_controversial_opinion_on_either/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was having a conversation with a friend and this topic came up so it got me thinking, and now I&amp;#39;m curious as to what other people have to say. My own personal hot take is that Anna Karenina is a terrible novel &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;and that she should have been hit by a train earlier to spare us all the BS.  &lt;/span&gt;That or every Dan Brown book is greatly overrated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Psychological horror books?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I really like horror stuff and I’m looking forward to read books with suspense
and psychological. I would also like to read books like Carrie by Stephen King,
I loved it :)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myg4yv/psychological_horror_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myg4yv/psychological_horror_books/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 23:30:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really like horror stuff and I’m looking forward to read books with suspense and psychological. I would also like to read books like Carrie by Stephen King, I loved it :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thank God for Libraries]]></title><description><![CDATA[So I'm an avid reader. As a kid I'd eat up books faster than my parents could
supply them. As a teenager I slowly slipped out of my reading and by late teens
I hadn't picked up a book unless it was mandatory for school. I'm in my early
20s now and rediscovering reading and nothing has helped me more…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4mfa/thank_god_for_libraries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4mfa/thank_god_for_libraries/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 19:38:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;m an avid reader. As a kid I&amp;#39;d eat up books faster than my parents could supply them. As a teenager I slowly slipped out of my reading and by late teens I hadn&amp;#39;t picked up a book unless it was mandatory for school. I&amp;#39;m in my early 20s now and rediscovering reading and nothing has helped me more than my library&amp;#39;s ebook app. With most libraries being shut or too far away to get to, ebooks have been such a delight. Especially because I&amp;#39;ve realised I read way quicker if it&amp;#39;s an ebook rather than a physical copy (something about not knowing how many pages I have left makes me more likely to not put it down).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve recently read Deeplight by Francis Hardinge, The Authenticity Project by Clare Pooley, Wink by Rob Harrell, Lie With Me by Phillipe Besson, A Bear Called Paddington by Michael Bond and The House With Chicken Legs by Sophie Anderson, all within the past 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s amazing how libraries give us so much for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Books about parallel universes, time travelling etc.]]></title><description><![CDATA[I already read dark matter 😅]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my3mfr/books_about_parallel_universes_time_travelling_etc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my3mfr/books_about_parallel_universes_time_travelling_etc/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 18:17:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I already read dark matter 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Someone just told me that there's "no real value" in spending time reading books]]></title><description><![CDATA[I had replied to someone's comment where they said they felt a little guilty for
finishing a whole book in the last 2 days, when they could have spent their time
doing more practical things. I said reading is a great thing to invest your time
in. Someone replied to my comment criticizing it because…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4z95/someone_just_told_me_that_theres_no_real_value_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4z95/someone_just_told_me_that_theres_no_real_value_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:53:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had replied to someone&amp;#39;s comment where they said they felt a little guilty for finishing a whole book in the last 2 days, when they could have spent their time doing more practical things. I said reading is a great thing to invest your time in. Someone replied to my comment criticizing it because there&amp;#39;s no &amp;quot;investment value in reading fiction novels besides the pure enjoyment factor&amp;quot; and that spending time doing something that has no real value can be detrimental.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t even understand that point of view. Books are incredibly valuable beyond just enjoyment. Most importantly they have helped my mental health in very meaningful, personal ways during times where I was depressed, anxious or heartbroken. They have made me feel less alone, given me empathy for all types of different people, affected me in a genuine emotional way, given me a new perspective, etc. If people don&amp;#39;t think fiction books have value they have been seriously missing out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, what&amp;#39;s with people knocking things for being fun instead of practical. If someone wants to spend their time reading a book &lt;em&gt;just because&lt;/em&gt; it&amp;#39;s enjoyable, that&amp;#39;s still not a waste of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I want to understand love.]]></title><description><![CDATA[When it comes to love I’ve never known what I’m doing. I’ve been haunted by an
ex (my first love) for 4 years, and I’m trying to navigate my new relationship
with my current girlfriend. My parents never taught me about love and I never
had any love stories I could use to understand myself or my…]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my2dj9/i_want_to_understand_love/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my2dj9/i_want_to_understand_love/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:43:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to love I’ve never known what I’m doing. I’ve been haunted by an ex (my first love) for 4 years, and I’m trying to navigate my new relationship with my current girlfriend. My parents never taught me about love and I never had any love stories I could use to understand myself or my relationships growing up. Science and research are helpful (I’m a nerd), but what I really need is a good story that can really touch me and give me ways to think about love. I don’t want any unrealistic, princess in the tower stuff, but something real I can take-in and learn from. I’m a guy, but I’m open to all suggestions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I appreciate everything anyone has to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>