<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 04:31:00 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼學校仍然把 "去問愛麗絲 "放在他們的課程中？]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我在學校時，我被迫在英語課上閱讀比阿特麗斯-斯帕克的《去問愛麗絲》。
英語課。這本書被介紹爲一本真實的日記和真實的故事，與市場上的說法完全一致。
它是以市場的方式介紹的。當我開始閱讀時，我注意到其中的情節是不現實的。
所以在谷歌上快速搜索後，我發現它是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ob318o/why_do_schools_still_put_go_ask_alice_in_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ob318o/why_do_schools_still_put_go_ask_alice_in_their/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 20:09:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was in school I was forced to read Go ask Alice by Beatrice Sparks for english class. It was introduced as a real diary and true story, exactly the way it was marketed. When I started reading I noticed the scenarios were unrealistic so a quick google search led me to figuring out it was literary fraud and not even slightly real. I also figured out that many schools still assign this as reading material.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is not only fraud but also very poorly written and poorly researched. The story is full of cliches and many of the main characters experiences with drugs are not even close to reality.
It angers me that people still assign this book as reading material, because it was obviously solely written to make money off off people who believed it was real and wanted their kids to stay away from drugs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are enough drug-related horror stories. Why read this garbage?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是一個有點受保護的中下階層的白人直男。在挑戰我的偏見和拓寬我的世界觀方面，哪些書會讓我大開眼界，信息量大，而且對我來說很重要？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我目前正在閱讀Ta-Nehisi Coates的 "Between the world and me"，這本書的內容與我的個人經歷非常不同。
它所描述的個人經歷與我自己的非常不同，它鼓勵我去
它鼓勵我正視我自己的一些庇護性觀念。

我最近讀了 "我們該何去何從：混亂還是社區？" 作者：馬丁-路德
金的文章，而這...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ob1wyp/im_a_somewhat_sheltered_lowermiddle_class/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ob1wyp/im_a_somewhat_sheltered_lowermiddle_class/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 19:51:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m currently reading “between the world and me” be Ta-Nehisi Coates, and it’s personalized experiences very different from my own, and it’s encouraged me to confront some of my own sheltered notions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I recently read “where do we go from here: chaos or community?” By Martin Luther King, and that was similarly eye opening. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What other books can you recommend, for me to gain some insight into experiences that are not immediately accessible or apparent to a middle class white American male?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I’m especially interested in learning more about race issues, and the experiences of people from other races. But feel free to recommend books dealing with other social issues, just please explain in the comments why you think this book could be informative to me.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I wasn’t expecting so many great suggestions so quickly- thank you to everyone! I’m going to save this post and use it as my reading list over the next couple months it seems!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I appreciate all the recommendations, and the insights! Thanks again&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[患有阿斯伯格症的年輕女性角色的書籍推薦？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的一個朋友是個年輕女性，最近得知她患有自閉症。I
有時我發現很難理解她的想法，這導致了我們之間的誤解。
導致我們之間的誤解。所以我想讀一本小說，讓我能夠
獲得對自閉症患者生活的洞察力。

我意識到，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oatatj/book_recs_with_a_young_woman_character_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oatatj/book_recs_with_a_young_woman_character_with/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:01:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A friend of mine who is a young woman has recently learnt that she has autism. I sometimes find it difficult to understand how she thinks, which leads to misunderstandings between us. So I&amp;#39;d like to read a fiction novel that allows me to gain insight to living with asperger&amp;#39;s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am aware that everyone experiences it differently, and no two people are alike. But I still think that this might help me learn more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am into most fiction, but not very hooked on sci-fi. But please recommend anything you find might fit&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I have been informed that &amp;quot;asperger&amp;#39;s&amp;quot; is an out-dated and not appropriate term to use, I apologize for this. The comments have been helpful though, so I will continue to learn more and better myself on this area.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit 2: Unfortunately I cannot change the title, but I have edited the text to say &amp;quot;autism&amp;quot; instead. Sorry for the wording of the title.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我既不是尼爾-蓋曼，也不是安迪-威爾（也不是任何如此出色的人），但我確實喜歡寫科學幻想故事，特別是那些有大量行動的故事，如《戰鬥密碼》傳奇。我是亞歷山大-達爾文，AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如你可能從標題中得到的，我最近有一些嚴重的冒名頂替綜合症。
特別是在r/books [/r/books]上做AMA。我犯了一個錯誤，那就是
我犯了一個錯誤，在做這個之前，我看了一下 "所有時間 "的投票列表，看到我的英雄們，如
蓋曼、威爾、桑德森、阿特伍德、勞倫斯和洛伊絲***。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ob0clt/i_am_neither_neil_gaiman_nor_andy_weir_nor_anyone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ob0clt/i_am_neither_neil_gaiman_nor_andy_weir_nor_anyone/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 17:30:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As you might get from the title, I&amp;#39;ve got some severe imposter syndrome lately, in particular doing an AMA here on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/books&quot;&gt;r/books&lt;/a&gt;. I made the mistake of looking at the &amp;#39;all time&amp;#39; upvoted list before doing this and saw my heroes like Gaiman, Weir, Sanderson, Atwood, Lawrence and Lois f**king Lowry (who I read as required reading in middle school).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry. Again, imposter syndrome. Even though I&amp;#39;ve now completed my debut trilogy, it doesn&amp;#39;t seem to ever go away.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sooo.... the Combat Codes was recently described as &amp;quot;an action-packed, bare-knuckle brawl that follows an orphan&amp;#39;s rags-to-riches story as he is tempered into a human weapon.&amp;quot; I promise you a real, live reviewer wrote that and it wasn&amp;#39;t my mom (who still refuses to read my books because there&amp;#39;s too much violence in them).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m pumped that CC seems to have hit the spot for many readers who dig martial arts movies. I&amp;#39;m a big fan of old school Bruce Lee and Jet Li movies, the Matrix and more recently the shows &amp;#39;Warrior&amp;#39; (HBO) and &amp;#39;Cobra Kai&amp;#39; (Netflix). I&amp;#39;ve even had some readers tell me that my books have gotten them back into practicing martial arts as adults, which is the coolest thing ever! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Outside of writing, I teach Brazilian Jiu Jitsu (it&amp;#39;s like wrestling in pajamas), I have two (soon to be three) daughters and I love a good bánh mì sandwich (I&amp;#39;m half vietnamese).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m very proud of the artwork for all three of my books, done by Felix Ortiz and Shawn King, in particular for the last of the series, Blacklight Born. You can probably tell the covers are heavily inspired by old-school Star Wars posters.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/0VYxNhg&quot;&gt;Combat Codes Cover&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/AB57aio&quot;&gt;Grievar&amp;#39;s Blood Cover&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/nuu9OCt&quot;&gt;Blacklight Born Cover&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last year Combat Codes made it as a finalist in Mark Lawrence&amp;#39;s SPFBO contest (best 10 of 300 books), which is pretty awesome, though by many of the judges standards it wasn&amp;#39;t considered to be fantasy because it has lo-fi tech and is light on the swords / sorcery aspect. I&amp;#39;m actually heavily inspired by jRPGS like Final Fantasy and Chrono Trigger, where the tech and magic are intertwined seamlessly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyhow, if you&amp;#39;re interested in a quick, fun, action-packed read, feel free to pick up the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B084GC1PRG&quot;&gt;first two books in the series for $0.99 each&lt;/a&gt; :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh yeah, I&amp;#39;m also working on a cool new series with the folks over at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wraithmarked.com/&quot;&gt;Wraithmarked Creative&lt;/a&gt; called &amp;#39;The Rising Fist&amp;#39; which I describe as a Southeast Asian inspired &amp;quot;Gladiator meets Stormlight Archive&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah, that&amp;#39;s about it. Again, I feel a bit like I&amp;#39;m wasting space here when you could very well be chatting with someone like &lt;a href=&quot;/u/MarkLawrence&quot;&gt;/u/MarkLawrence&lt;/a&gt; himself (who is one of my favorite authors and did an AMA  7 years ago.... yeesh.) But what the hell, while I&amp;#39;m here: AMA. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof:
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/4k31ztwb72871.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/4k31ztwb72871.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在讀《爬蟲唱歌的地方》......哇，寫得真好。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我只讀到第九章，但我已經感覺到我個人認識所有的人物，特別是Kya。
人物，特別是Kya。不要讓我開始對沼澤和周圍地區的描述。
沼澤和周圍地區的描述......很美。



如果你已經讀過或正在讀《爬蟲唱歌的地方》，你有什麼想法？
你對它的看法是什麼？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oawoxa/im_currently_reading_where_the_crawdads_sing_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oawoxa/im_currently_reading_where_the_crawdads_sing_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 14:46:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m only on chapter 9 and I already feel like I personally know all the characters, Kya especially. And don&amp;#39;t get me started on the description of the marsh and surrounding area... beautiful. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have read or are currently reading &amp;quot;Where The Crawdads Sing&amp;quot;, what are your thoughts on it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的未婚夫非常討厭這本書，他把它燒了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[前一段時間，他和他的班級被要求閱讀這本書作爲一項作業。

他很喜歡書，他幾乎是在囤積書籍，但這本書他非常討厭，以至於
他把它燒掉了。

伊恩-麥克尤恩的《持久的愛》。

他稱這本書是最長的無意義的胡言亂語的敘述，並認爲它最好用於
在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oatgxg/my_fiancé_hates_this_book_so_much_he_burned_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oatgxg/my_fiancé_hates_this_book_so_much_he_burned_it/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 13:05:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back a while ago he and his class were asked to read it for an assignment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He loves books, he practically hoards them, but this book he hated so much that he consigned it to fire.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Enduring Love by Ian McEwan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He called it the longest narrative of pointless drivel and thinks it best used in torture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never read it myself as I&amp;#39;m not much of a reader aside from the odd book on graphic design. But I&amp;#39;d be curious to know what everyone else&amp;#39;s thoughts here are on it and if my other half overreacted just a touch. 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["她釋放了一股她沒有意識到的氣息"...。爲什麼每個人都對這句話如此煩惱？]]></title><description><![CDATA[編輯（最後的想法）。評論裏有一些很好的解釋。它
似乎大多數人不喜歡這個短語，因爲它是一個老生常談。我個人認爲。
即使它是一個陳詞濫調，它也能完成工作。如果一個作者能夠重新創造出
與這句話相同的感覺或視覺效果，在更大的範圍內。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oaozg7/she_released_a_breath_she_didnt_realise_she_was/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oaozg7/she_released_a_breath_she_didnt_realise_she_was/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 06:21:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EDIT (final thoughts):
There are some great explanations in the comments. It seems most people don&amp;#39;t like this phrase because it is a cliche. Personally, even though it is a cliche, it gets the job done. And if an author can recreate the same feeling or visualization as this phrase in a more original way, then that&amp;#39;s great. But if not  this phrase is just fine, thank you very much. Original, creative, and engaging storytelling is important to me but I don&amp;#39;t think every single sentence needs to be original and creative for the writing as a whole to be effective. If an author has creative and original writing but there are some cliches sprinkled in here and there, I personally really don&amp;#39;t mind. I appreciate originality in writing as much as i appreciate straight to the point familiar wording i can relate to. The presence of cliches in the writing doesnt instantly detract from my enjoyment, and I think that is why I got annoyed when, from my perspective, it seemed like people were making it way too big a problem than it needed to be. But reading the comments i see that for many, the use of cliches is a sign of lazy writing and it makes it hard to be engaged with the story. Understandable. I get it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;ORIGINAL POST:
Every booktuber and book reviewer i come across on the internet seems to have a personal grudge against this phrase. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is the big deal?? Yes, it is used often but I think holding a breath you didn&amp;#39;t realise you were holding is definitely something that has happened to most people in real life. I mean, it certainly happens to me so I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s unrealistic for it to happen to characters in books. It accurately describes what can happen to someone after a tense event has passed.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I mean what other way is an author supposed to convey the character ... literally releasing a breath they didnt realise they were holding??!! It&amp;#39;s like saying authors can no longer write that their characters &amp;quot;woke up and had breakfast&amp;quot; because authors are aLWaYs mAking thEir chAracTErs wAke uP aNd eAt brEakfAst and it&amp;#39;s GETting OLd. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What about the phrase, &amp;quot;I could hardly keep my eyes open&amp;quot;. It is also a very commonly used phrase that authors use when a character is tired but I don&amp;#39;t see any booktubers or reviewers complaining that the line is overused.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just get so tired of reading reviews that get so hung up on the one time the author used that phrase in their writing. EVERY SINGLE TIME I read a book that has this phrase, there will be at least one review going on a mini rant about the line being used in the book. Like, okay....it&amp;#39;s getting old now. You can stop freaking out about authors using this phrase, thank you. We get it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what, authors can no longer write things because phrases that describe something relatable and easy for a reader to visualize is too often used by other authors?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[所以我的妻子在即將到來的新娘洗禮中收到了這個東西（見評論）。幫助列出一些她可能還沒有讀過的好的晦澀的書。]]></title><description><![CDATA[最喜歡閱讀的準新娘的一個簡單要求：帶着
爲我的收藏帶來一本書，新的或舊的，由你選擇。心理驚悚小說。
浪漫小說，真實犯罪是我在業餘時間閱讀的幾種類型。請遵守我的願望
而不是禮物。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oai09y/so_my_wife_received_this_for_an_upcoming_bridal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oai09y/so_my_wife_received_this_for_an_upcoming_bridal/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 05:15:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A simple request from the bride to be whose favorite thing to do is read: bring a book for my collection, new or used, it is your selection. Psych thrillers, romance, true crime are a few genres I read in spare time. Please abide my wish instead of a gift.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一個23歲的沒有經驗的幻想讀者，希望得到幻想書的推薦。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，如果我說我在尋找什麼，那是在撒謊，但我已經讀了一些最常見的。
最常見的，但沒有什麼成功的分支。所以我想
我向你們這些更有經驗的讀者徵求一些建議。我知道我在尋找
一些好的幻想小說，最好是高級幻想小說，雖然我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oab5b7/a_inexperienced_fantasy_reader_at_23_looking_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oab5b7/a_inexperienced_fantasy_reader_at_23_looking_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 03:25:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, so Id be lying If I said exactly what Im looking for but Ive read a few of the most common ones, but had little success branching out of that. So I guess Im asking you all more experienced readers for some advice. I know Im looking for some good fantasy though, preferably High fantasy though I did enjoy Twilight (I know)....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To give a little context Ive always loved the standard fantasy in video games(Warhammer, Warcraft), Though Eragon wasnt a super good story plot wise, it had enough magic, cuteness and romance to keep me going. So I guess I got a weakness for the whole Fantasy action/romance. Ive also covered some Norse gods books in Norwegian. And Tolkien is Tolkien. :D However Ive had little success outside of this.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Game of Thrones was ok, a little too slow paced, but Tyrion and a few other charas made it worth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Books Ive disliked so far: Maze runner, The Hunger Games, Harry Potter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Been looking myself for awhile with little success, so would be awesome to get some from someone a little familiar with books in the genre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[書籍播客]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好! 一個多月前我在這裏發帖，想找一些好書
播客推薦，你們都沒有讓我失望! 我想分享一些
我最喜歡聽的一些播客，也聽聽你們最喜歡的。

馬龍和傑克讀死人》--獲得布克爾獎的《馬龍和傑克讀死人》。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oaipcr/book_podcasts/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oaipcr/book_podcasts/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:44:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! I posted on here over a month ago trying to find some good book podcast recommendations and you all did not disappoint! I wanted to share some of my favorites that I’ve been listening to and hear about your favorites too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Marlon and Jake Read Dead People&lt;/strong&gt;—The booker prize award winning author Marlon James and his editor run this podcast. The second season started this week! They discuss classic books and have really engaging discussion and banter. If you’re a fan of literary fiction or classics check this out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Top Shelf Reads&lt;/strong&gt;—This is a newer podcast that does a great job of balancing book reviews and discussion topics about various reading topics. They introduced me to A Fine Balance, which I’m currently enjoying! Their episodes feel varied—not just recommendation after recommendation. Very impressed so far. They seem to focus on lit fiction, historical fiction, sci-fi/fantasy, weird fiction, and some narrative non fiction and philosophy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bookshop Interview&lt;/strong&gt;—This is a fun podcast to hear interviews from lesser known authors. I’ve enjoyed what I’ve heard so far. If you want insight on the writing process from authors, check it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Literary Friction&lt;/strong&gt;—Another podcast geared towards literary fiction but they do a great job of not making it a “thing”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Book Review (NYT)&lt;/strong&gt;—A professional podcast that I listen to when they cover a book I am interested in. The Hamnet episode was great!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Book Riot&lt;/strong&gt;—another professional show that has great hosts covering publishing and book news. Love their inclusive/progressive focus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you listened to any of these? What do you think? Did I leave off your favorite?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[喬萬尼的房間》--詹姆斯-鮑德溫--我所讀過的最好的三角戀之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是我讀過的詹姆斯-鮑德溫的第一部小說作品，我對它的剋制和情感力量印象深刻。
它的剋制和情感力量給我留下了非常深刻的印象。它講述了一個故事
他在巴黎漫無目的地生活在當地一家同性戀酒吧的顧客中。
當地同性戀酒吧的顧客中漫無目的地生活。大衛對每個人都產生了普遍的厭惡感......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oaejit/giovannis_room_james_baldwin_one_of_the_best_love/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oaejit/giovannis_room_james_baldwin_one_of_the_best_love/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:13:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first work of fiction from James Baldwin that I&amp;#39;ve read and I was very impressed with its restraint and emotional power. It tells the story of a young American named David who lives aimlessly in Paris among the clientele of a local gay bar. David develops a general loathing of everyone and cannot seem to find his place in the world or find love. Baldwin makes it very clear that his protagonist is bisexual, but the homosexual themes of the plot are almost secondary to the way his characters navigate the Parisian cityscape as vulnerable, culturally ambivalent wanderers with too much time and not enough money. David struggles between his desire to place himself in heteronormative society, and his desire to be sexually fulfilled by men. He finds himself torn between his New World sincerity and the ironic distance of the Old World. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second part of the book is definitely the strongest. Arguments are profound, but the quiet moments between the flareups also resonate with cinematic-like poetry. Characters grapple with their future, but the central dilemma of the novel continues to linger far beyond the novels&amp;#39; scope.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought it was a fantastic read and I am very interested in reading more fiction by James Baldwin in the future. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.worldcat.org/oclc/952068467&quot;&gt;WorldCat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不相信我上當了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完《公主新娘》。我從來沒有看過這部電影，但我從流行文化的參考資料中對它有足夠的瞭解。
我沒有看過電影，但我從流行文化的參考資料中知道了足夠多的著名臺詞，比如。
"不可思議"，或 "你好。我的名字是伊尼戈-蒙託亞。你殺了我父親。
準備受死吧。"但我並不真正瞭解......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oacu01/i_cant_believe_i_fell_for_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oacu01/i_cant_believe_i_fell_for_it/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 18:53:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading The Princess Bride. I&amp;#39;ve never seen the movie, but I knew enough about it from pop culture references to know the famous lines like, &amp;quot;Inconceivable,&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Hello. My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die,&amp;quot; but I didn&amp;#39;t really know anything about the plot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I believed every word about the supposed &amp;quot;abridgement.&amp;quot; I mean, I had never heard of a country called Florin or an author called Morgenstern, but I just figured there&amp;#39;s probably a lot of places and authors I&amp;#39;ve never heard of and went along with it. So I finished the book, which I enjoyed immensely, read the first chapter of the &amp;quot;sequel&amp;quot; and decided to Google it to see if King ever finished it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then I realized. And I&amp;#39;ve never felt more gullible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please tell me I&amp;#39;m not alone in being fooled because I&amp;#39;ve never felt quite so silly lol&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尼爾-蓋曼斯在《美國之神》中省略了耶穌，這太有意思了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[當《美國衆神》第一次被推薦給我時，有人告訴我這是一場文化戰爭。
戰爭。發動戰爭的雙方是我們過去崇拜的偶像和我們現在實際崇拜的偶像。
我們現在真正崇拜的偶像。也許是爲了避免我受到破壞，他們從來沒有提到有關的神靈會是什麼？
提到有關的神是不太知名的神。在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oa7rjp/neil_gaimans_omission_of_jesus_in_american_gods/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oa7rjp/neil_gaimans_omission_of_jesus_in_american_gods/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:37:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When &amp;#39;American Gods&amp;#39; was first recommended to me, I was told it was a cultural war. The sides waging war being the idols we used to worship vs the idols we actually worship now. Maybe in an effort to save me from spoilers they never mentioned that the gods in question would be lesser known Gods. In my mind I thought that Jesus, Muhammad, Buddha, Chebbeniathan, and other prominent modern Gods would be the main characters warring against internet, and media. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was taken aback by the inclusion of much older lesser known Gods. I loved the native American and ancient tribal God segments. I never imagined Odin would play such a focal point in a story like this. I was blown away by my inability to see that the United States that I know is only a few hundred years old. Being that most of it&amp;#39;s current citizens have relatively recent immigrated from somewhere else, the gods are foreign and far beyond my scope. So characters like Czernobog and Mr. Nancy were awesome. Midway through the book I accepted what I was reading and really enjoyed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It wasn&amp;#39;t until the end where Gaiman addressed his omission of Jesus specifically. He said that it was because he didn&amp;#39;t write a prominent role for him, and that only lightly including such a larger than life character wouldn&amp;#39;t be the proper way to go about it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m curious what the rest of you think about it. I know that often what we say to explain our actions often veils intentions that we not only keep from others, but ourselves. He seems to be someone with a clear history of some denomination of Jesus based worship. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fear doesn&amp;#39;t necessarily seem to be the right word I&amp;#39;d use. But speaking as someone who formally used to partake in Christian and catholic worship, publicly representing Jesus in a way that doesn&amp;#39;t align with the Bible isn&amp;#39;t something I don&amp;#39;t mind seeing when tasteful. But it&amp;#39;s definitely not something I&amp;#39;d do publicly or professionally myself. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I loved the bit that he wrote for him visiting shadow on the tree. That whole vigil for Odin as well as shadow himself ran some not so subtle parallel with the crucifixion. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I thought the book was great, I&amp;#39;m sad to hear that the show had so many problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[書中有什麼東西讓你自動成爲一星的嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在Goodreads上查看我的閱讀書架，發現了一個模式，即我所有的一星評級的書都是如此。
我的一星評級的書。我一直有強烈的正義感，無論何時，一個角色做了可怕的事情，卻沒有得到任何獎勵。
角色做了可怕的事情卻沒有得到任何後果/得到了他們想要的東西。
他們想要的東西，這就毀了我的整本書。是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oa0qtv/is_there_anything_in_book_that_makes_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oa0qtv/is_there_anything_in_book_that_makes_it/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 13:37:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was looking through my read shelf on Goodreads and found a pattern with all of my one star rated books. I’ve always had a strong sense of justice and anytime a character does something awful and receives no consequences/ gets exactly what they wanted anyway, it ruins the entire book for me. Is there anything that you absolutely can’t stand in books, that completely takes you out of the novel?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[能給我帶來像《哈利-波特》那樣舒適感覺的最佳奇幻書籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已經讀過無數次《哈利-波特》......。

我喜歡書中那些舒適的感覺，如對落雪、聖誕節、洞穴等的描述。
降雪、聖誕節、洞穴等等...。

  即使提到這些也給我一種舒適的感覺。

有什麼推薦嗎？

P.S - 不僅僅是幻想，任何類型的都可以！:-)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oa0f7o/best_fantasy_books_that_can_give_me_a_cozy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/oa0f7o/best_fantasy_books_that_can_give_me_a_cozy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 07:19:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have read Harry Potter countless number of times...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the cozy feelings that are there in the books such as the descriptions of snow fall, Christmas, The Burrow etc etc...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wow!! Even mentioning all this gave me a cozy feel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any recommendations?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S - Not just Fantasy, any genre!:-)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一個非常好的系列。阿特米斯-福爾]]></title><description><![CDATA[雖然不是世界上最好的書，但《阿特米斯-福爾》系列是我最喜歡的前10本書之一。
10本最喜歡的讀物之一。如果你想讓自己像個孩子，我會強烈推薦它。
再度回到童年。它介於兒童童話書和成人小說的中間位置。
小說。

作者是Eoin Colfer（我不知道如何...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9y0aj/a_mighty_fine_series_artemis_fowl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9y0aj/a_mighty_fine_series_artemis_fowl/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 03:51:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;While not the best books in the world, the Artemis Fowl series is among my Top 10 favorite reads. I would strongly recommend it if you want to feel like a kid again. It is somewhere in the middle of a kids fairy tale book, and an adult&amp;#39;s fiction novel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Written by Eoin Colfer (I don&amp;#39;t know how to pronounce it either), Artemis Fowl is a series of 8 books about 12 year old named, well, Artemis Fowl. He is a genius, having the highest IQ in Europe, is a multi-millionaire, and is a criminal mastermind, running the Fowl corporate crime enterprise. He becomes fascinated with the existence of fairies when he is trying to raise funds to find his lost father, believed to be dead when his transport ship blew up in Russia. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read the book. You will not regret it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛剛讀完加繆的《異鄉人》。我錯過了什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀了《異鄉人》，我發現主角是一個反社會的人，其
唯一值得稱道的品質是誠實，而默爾索有時甚至濫用誠實。
繆爾索甚至有時會濫用這一點，直言不諱，但他卻沒有得到任何好處，反而傷害了他人。

我覺得在審判過程中提出的一些觀點似乎是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9uoh0/just_finished_the_stranger_by_camus_what_did_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9uoh0/just_finished_the_stranger_by_camus_what_did_i/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 03:17:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just read The Stranger, and I found the main character to be a sociopath whose only redeeming quality was honesty, and Meursault even abused that at times, being bluntly honest in ways that gained him nothing but hurt others.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt as though some of the points being made during the trial were reasonable, but I felt that Camus’ intent was for me to root for Meursault in spite of his faults, but I feel like he was just obtuse and awful throughout.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any help understanding Camus’ intent for the book or character would be great, and any personal takes would help too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你們有時會不會覺得沒有準備好從一本書中繼續前進？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完這本短篇小說集，我在想這是一個很好的時間來繼續閱讀另一本書。
我想現在是繼續閱讀另一本書的好時機。但我一直在想
再重讀一遍，或者至少只是瀏覽一些精選的頁面，也許只是
看一下章節的標題，我不知道。

我只是希望有...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9s9fk/do_you_guys_sometimes_just_not_feel_ready_to_move/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9s9fk/do_you_guys_sometimes_just_not_feel_ready_to_move/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 23:55:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading this collection of short stories, and I was thinking it would be a good time to move on to another book. But I just keep thinking about rereading them again, or at least just browsing a few select pages, maybe just looking at the chapter titles I dunno.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wish there were more adventures I guess, don’t really feel like I’m finished with the book, even though I’ve read it. Don’t really know how else to explain it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不受歡迎的意見。人們對青少年小說的要求過於苛刻]]></title><description><![CDATA[當你拿起一本YA書，那麼它就會是YA，對嗎？它的銷售對象是
它的市場對象是年輕人，在情節上通常以他們爲中心。主題不會
除了 "善惡之爭 "或 "禁忌之愛"，還有一些陳詞濫調等等，主題不會太深刻。
這是因爲它不會吸引普通青少年的注意力，如果...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9qblz/unpopular_opinion_people_are_too_harsh_on_ya/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9qblz/unpopular_opinion_people_are_too_harsh_on_ya/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 22:37:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When you pick up a YA book, then it&amp;#39;s going to be YA, right? It&amp;#39;s marketed to young adults and usually centered around them in terms of plot. The themes won&amp;#39;t be too deep beyond &amp;quot;good vs evil&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;forbidden love&amp;quot; and tropes and so on. That&amp;#39;s because it won&amp;#39;t hold the attention of the average teen if it&amp;#39;s too complicated or requiring a lot of literary skill to decipher. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s not going to be &amp;quot;Blood Meridian&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Giovanni&amp;#39;s Room&amp;quot; concerning how the story is centered. As a young reader myself, I can admit that I&amp;#39;m not extraordinarily fond of YA fiction. But it caters to a certain audience, so when I see adults reading it and then complaining about it feels odd since they weren&amp;#39;t the target audience to begin with. If it has an interesting premise, sells well, and the plot is exciting enough and doesn&amp;#39;t promote harmful behaviors, then I think it shouldn&amp;#39;t be compared to books that were obviously going to be more critically acclaimed because they were meant for adults, and for adults to analyze. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course people can critique books, but I just feel like expecting more than your standard YA fiction with romance, action, and good vs evil is setting yourself up for disappointment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[開普敦圖書館的 "書香門第 "誕生於海運集裝箱中]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9738c/joy_of_books_in_cape_town_library_born_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9738c/joy_of_books_in_cape_town_library_born_in/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 21:29:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一本書的糟糕文筆能以多快的速度讓你反感？]]></title><description><![CDATA[不需要細說（除非你想），一個作者如何快速地
疏遠你？我不是在談論內容，我是指在實際的
寫作的工藝。在過去的兩個星期裏，我已經看完了兩本不同的書
因爲作者的寫作能力，我在三頁之內就看完了。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9oww2/how_fast_can_a_books_bad_writing_turn_you_off/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9oww2/how_fast_can_a_books_bad_writing_turn_you_off/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 20:22:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without needing to go into detail (unless you want to) how quickly can an author alienate you? And I’m not talking about content, I mean in terms of the actual craft of writing. In the last two weeks I’ve been done with  two different books within three pages  because of the writing ability of the authors. Does anybody else get annoyed that fast at what you feel is bad writing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[瑪麗-雷諾撰寫的《波斯男孩》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完這本書，想把它推薦給任何歷史小說的愛好者。
小說的愛好者推薦。故事講述的是巴戈斯，一個太監，在亞歷山大大帝戰勝波斯的大流士後不久，被贈予作爲僕人。
在亞歷山大大帝戰勝波斯的大流士後不久，他被贈予作爲僕人。
巴戈亞斯是一個真實的歷史人物，他在書中只是偶爾被提及。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9iac6/the_persian_boy_by_mary_renault/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9iac6/the_persian_boy_by_mary_renault/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:45:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished this up and wanted to recommend it to any fans of historical fiction here.  The story follows Bagoas, a eunuch gifted as a servant to Alexander the Great not long after his great victory over Darius of Persia.  Bagoas is a real historical person who gets only occasional mention in the records of Alexander’s life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book is a wonder.  The prose is accessible while also being lyrical and even poetic at times.  The scope is astounding, allowing the reader to see Alexander’s campaigns firsthand.  And Bagoas is a sensitive, thoughtful, and sympathetic figure amidst the cruelty and splendor of the ancient world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The portrait of Alexander himself is the real treat here though, in my opinion.  The book shows us a nuanced yet extraordinary character who is heroic, flawed, loving, and a visionary leader.  This is one of those stories in which knowing how it ends takes nothing away from the journey.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10/10&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我已經讀完了邁克爾-查本的《卡瓦里耶和克萊的奇妙冒險》，回去重讀我最喜歡的一本舊書，感覺很奇妙]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像標題所說的，回到過去，徹底重讀我最喜歡的《卡瓦里耶和克萊的奇妙冒險》，這是一種奇妙的感覺。
我最喜歡的書，《卡瓦里耶和克萊的奇妙冒險》。特別是
第二次讀時，我已經長大了，第一次看到所有這些
貫穿全書的小細節和預示，我已經...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9mx7w/ive_finished_reading_the_amazing_adventures_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9mx7w/ive_finished_reading_the_amazing_adventures_of/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:20:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the title says, it&amp;#39;s an amazing feeling to go back and thoroughly re-read a favorite book of mine, The Amazing Adventures of Kavalier and Clay. Especially the second time around I&amp;#39;m now older and seeing for the first time all these little details and foreshadowing throughout the book I&amp;#39;ve missed reading through for the first time. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It makes me appreciate on going back and reading your favorite book or book series and seeing all these hidden little gems scattered throughout the book the second time around and probably not really realizing how important that little detail will become later on in the plot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just love it when authors do this and we readers won&amp;#39;t realize it until the moment comes and everything makes all sense and clicks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否有辦法避免有關自殺的書籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想知道是否有人知道有什麼資源可以識別那些以自殺爲主題的書籍。
自殺。昨晚我正在讀一本書，其中一個人物意外地自殺了。
而閱讀這本書的個人反響讓我大半夜都睡不着。
夜。

請注意，這並不是說書中有自殺的情節。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9lfwq/is_there_a_way_to_avoid_books_about_suicide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9lfwq/is_there_a_way_to_avoid_books_about_suicide/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:20:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m wondering if anyone knows a resource that identifies books that feature suicide. Last night I was reading a book and a character unexpectedly killed themself, and the personal repercussions of reading that kept me up for most of the night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please note, this is NOT saying that books which feature suicides should not be written, or that they should come with warnings, or that suicide in books should be written in a specific style. I&amp;#39;m just saying that, right now, I would prefer not to read books that feature suicide, and I&amp;#39;m wondering if someone has created a resource for me and readers like me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Finally, since it may come up, I am not suicidal, nor am I considering self-harm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[白癡]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛完成了白癡的第一部分，我真的印象深刻。有人在這個帖子中說
說他們認爲《卡爾茲馬佐夫兄弟》是有史以來最好的書。
時間。很自然，我就去買了這本書，但我也買了《白癡》（我想讀它作爲對作者的熱身）。
我想讀它作爲對作者的熱身）。) 陀思妥耶夫斯基有...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o92pnr/the_idiot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o92pnr/the_idiot/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 19:02:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished part one of the idiot and I am really impressed. Someone posted in this sub that they thought the brothers karzmazov was the best book of all time. Naturally, I went out and bought the book, but I also bought the idiot (I wanted to read it as a warm up to the author). Dostoevsky has an ability in creating characters that I’ve never seen any other author have. His characters are emotionally raw. Many of the characters in the book are rich, and the way that they are written feels hilarious, but also completely accurate in context. So much happens in the first part of this book alone, and what was mind blowing to me was that it happened in only one day. My favorite characters are the prince (who I relate to) and nastasya filipovna. The way that nastasya brings out the disbelief, anger, and hilarity of the rest of the cast was a great read. I’m excited to finish the book soon. Do you consider these two characters to be some of fyodor’s best? Who else if not?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你好，我是道格拉斯-斯圖爾特，2020年布克獎得主舒吉-貝恩的作者。AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一名蘇格蘭裔美國作家和編劇。我的處女作《Shuggie Bain》。
贏得了2020年布克獎，併入圍了國家圖書獎。
筆會/海明威獎以及其他一些文學獎項的決賽。舒吉-貝恩贏得了
美國藝術學院的蘇-考夫曼獎。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9n3ed/hiya_im_douglas_stuart_author_of_shuggie_bain/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9n3ed/hiya_im_douglas_stuart_author_of_shuggie_bain/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 18:05:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a Scottish-American author and screenwriter. My debut novel, Shuggie Bain, won the 2020 Booker Prize and was a finalist for the National Book Award, PEN/Hemingway Award, as well as several other literary awards. Shuggie Bain won the Sue Kaufman Prize from the American Academy of Arts and Letters. It was named both the British Book of the Year, and Debut of the Year at the 2021 British Book Awards. It is to be translated into over thirty-eight languages and adapted for television in partnership with A24 Pictures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was born in Glasgow, Scotland, and hold an MA from the Royal College of Art in London, but since 2000 I have lived and loved in New York City. My short stories, “Found Wanting,” and “The Englishman,” were published in The New Yorker. I am hard at work on a second novel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/33j38z2buu771.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/33j38z2buu771.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你開始自己的小型免費圖書館...]]></title><description><![CDATA[你放在裏面的第一輪書會是什麼樣子？你會從
是從經典開始，還是從羣衆喜聞樂見的書籍開始？

你會使用流通的主題（例如，六月的自豪月，夏天的海灘讀物，聖誕節的書籍）嗎？
夏天的海灘讀物，冬天的聖誕讀物），或者你會用你最近讀過的任何書來儲存它？
最近剛讀過的書？

我是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9bbqd/if_you_started_your_own_little_free_library/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9bbqd/if_you_started_your_own_little_free_library/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 14:20:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What would the first round of books you put in it look like? Would you start with classics or go for crowd pleasers? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would you use circulating themes (i.e. Pride Month in June, beach reads in summer, Christmas books in winter) or would you stock it with whatever you&amp;#39;d just recently read? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m curious about how people are actually using their own Little Free Libraries, or how they&amp;#39;d set up their own (potential) one. I&amp;#39;m planning on starting one eventually and I&amp;#39;d love to hear your ideas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的伴侶有創傷性疾病和抑鬱症，我需要一本書來更好地瞭解她。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，我的伴侶從小就有創傷性疾病和抑鬱症，在她的生活中沒有任何事情可以解決。
她的生活和她有很多的家庭問題，所以她有很多的創傷。
我想找一本書來更好地瞭解她，我應該避免說什麼？
因爲我知道我在她身邊必須要小心，她很敏感......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o9hcr7/my_partner_has_ptsd_and_depression_i_need_a_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o9hcr7/my_partner_has_ptsd_and_depression_i_need_a_book/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 13:45:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello my partner has ptsd from childhood and depression, nothing worked out in her life and she had a lot of family problems so she has a lot of trauma and I&amp;#39;m looking for a book to understand her better, and what should i avoid saying because i know i have to be careful around her she&amp;#39;s sensitive to certain things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有沒有一個像Goodreads那樣的應用程序，實際上有一個簡單的用戶界面？]]></title><description><![CDATA[上帝，我討厭Goodreads。你記錄書籍、給它們評分、添加朋友、看
朋友的活動，等等。我可以說上好幾天。這個界面實在是太糟糕了
和笨重。

有沒有一個Goodreads的替代品能夠真正得到人們的喜愛和關注？
有沒有更接近於Letterboxd的簡單性的東西？

如果...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9evwi/is_there_an_app_like_goodreads_that_actually_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9evwi/is_there_an_app_like_goodreads_that_actually_has/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 11:44:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;God I hate Goodreads. The way you log books, rate them, add friends, see friend’s activity, etc. I could go on for days. The interface is just terrible and clunky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there a Goodreads alternative that actually gets frequent love and attention? Something closer to the simplicity of Letterboxd?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If not, can somebody PLEASE make one!!?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;EDIT: Looking hopefully for an app with a social/friends element to it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我昨晚剛看完《站立》（完整版和未剪輯版）--一些初步想法。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我把《站立》放在書架上已經有好幾年了，從來沒有真正記住它的內容。
它是關於什麼的。但當我提到這個名字時，每個人都對我大喊 "經典"。
所以它在我的腦海中排了一陣子的書。我決定
把它作爲我2021年的目標，因爲這一年很奇怪。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9b0zg/i_just_finished_the_stand_complete_uncut_last/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o9b0zg/i_just_finished_the_stand_complete_uncut_last/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 06:24:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve had The Stand on my shelf for a handful of years, never really remembering what it was about. But everyone just screamed &amp;quot;classic&amp;quot; at me when I mentioned the name, so it sat in my mental book queue for a while. Go figure I decide to make it my goal for the year 2021 after the bizarre year that was 2020, super-flu and everything. Anyway...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At 1153 pages, this is the longest book I have ever finished. I figured I&amp;#39;d be able to knock out 100 pages each month, have it finished by the end of the year. Well, I guess things got rolling and plot arcs started spinning faster, and now I&amp;#39;m done with the whole thing twice as fast as I&amp;#39;d planned. I really did enjoy it, especially with the new series coming out recently and being able to watch that with a slight delay to avoid spoilers. (I have several thoughts on the mini-series, but I&amp;#39;ll focus on just the book here.) Bottom line here is: I&amp;#39;m so glad I didn&amp;#39;t let a bulky book scare me away from reading a thrilling story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first impression as I started reading was that King never really does many dramatic moments of horror or the literary equivalent of a jump-scare. His style is more insidious. Instead of spaced out moments that spike the drama, there&amp;#39;s a slow, sneaky build of... discomfort. I&amp;#39;m reading along and feeling just mild unease at what&amp;#39;s unfolding. There&amp;#39;s always something just on the periphery causing worry or tension or something, and not anything popping out and going, &amp;quot;BOO!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It took a while to establish all of the characters and start weaving all of the different threads together, but once it took off, then it was on. I really appreciated the diversity of characters and their struggles. Maybe I will appreciate them even more on my next reading of it. And I really like when they start raising the question: now that we have a chance to start over and do things differently, &lt;em&gt;will we&lt;/em&gt;? I think it speaks to our constant NEED to evolve and break old patterns even when they&amp;#39;re &amp;quot;tradition&amp;quot; or familiar or just hegemonic. There were tons of things I enjoyed about this, but these are the things that jumped out first. Oh - and Tom Cullen&amp;#39;s prayer on the way home. That is fuggin&amp;#39; gold, and I burst out laughing at first encounter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what now? I feel hungover now. Like I can&amp;#39;t even decide what to pull out of my massive literary queue to read next. How does anything follow THAT? I genuinely don&amp;#39;t know. I&amp;#39;ll probably have to veer toward something totally different to avoid any comparison, a biography or something. But again, I&amp;#39;m very glad I tackled this personal challenge and feel like I&amp;#39;ve joined many others of you that have gone on this same journey. I welcome your thoughts, memories, reflections or anything else related to your own reading of The Stand. Cheers, and thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[盲目的刺客》--瑪格麗特-阿特伍德]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我不像這裏的大多數人那樣熱衷於閱讀，但我年輕的時候曾經是。
最近，我開始嘗試再次閱讀，而且進展很順利。
很好。

在網上不同的網站上，你現在可以訂購一種叫做 "與書相約 "的東西。
書"，大多數選項允許你選擇一個流派......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8t9fh/the_blind_assassin_margaret_atwood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8t9fh/the_blind_assassin_margaret_atwood/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 02:55:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;m not an avid reader like most here, but I used to be when I was younger. Recently I&amp;#39;ve started trying to get into reading again and it&amp;#39;s going wonderfully.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On different sites online you can now order something called &amp;quot;Blind date with a book&amp;quot;, with most options allowing you to choose a genre or point the seller in the direction of the kind of books you&amp;#39;d like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was so happy to receive my little mystery book yesterday and even happier when I opened it up and saw the Blind Assassin. I&amp;#39;d never heard of it (Or Margaret Atwood for that matter) but I looked it up and saw that it was mostly met with positive reviews. The biggest thing I read was about her style of writing, but I was in no way prepared for the way this woman tears through your soul. So many chapters ending with quotes that leave my hair standing on end. I&amp;#39;m not sure whether it&amp;#39;s due to her being a poet, but I get goosebumps so often and I&amp;#39;m only 200 pages in. I cannot put this book down.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think she describes mental health fantastically, without ever saying that&amp;#39;s what she&amp;#39;s doing. I knew after the first chapter that I&amp;#39;d be hooked when she ended it with &amp;quot;&lt;em&gt;Tell me where it hurts,&lt;/em&gt; she&amp;#39;d say. &lt;em&gt;Stop howling. Just calm down and show me where.&lt;/em&gt;
But some people can&amp;#39;t tell where it hurts. They can&amp;#39;t calm down. They can&amp;#39;t ever stop howling&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can&amp;#39;t wait to of finished this book and be able to share my full thoughts on it. Truly the only book I have ever felt compelled to write and talk about.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雅克的《紅牆》書籍將由Netflix改編]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o93ktc/jacques_redwall_books_to_be_adapted_by_netflix/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o93ktc/jacques_redwall_books_to_be_adapted_by_netflix/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 02:07:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對帕特里克-羅斯福斯的印象相當不好]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個幻想小說的忠實讀者，但一直在猶豫是否要開始閱讀《風的名字》，因爲他的寫作時間表很慢。
因爲他寫書的時間表太慢。我並不介意在一個系列作品完成之前就開始寫，以支持作者。
我不介意在一個系列完成之前開始，以支持作者，但在這一點上，他似乎永遠不會完成它。
但在這一點上，基本上他似乎永遠不會完成它。

然而，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o91lmb/fairly_unimpressed_with_patrick_rothfuss/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o91lmb/fairly_unimpressed_with_patrick_rothfuss/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 22:50:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So Im a big fantasy reader but have been pretty hesitant to start To Name The Wind because of the slow timetable with which he is writing the books.  I don&amp;#39;t mind starting a series before its finished to support the author but at this point it basically seems he&amp;#39;s never going to finish it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, a bunch of my friends kept telling me it was worth to read even if he doesn&amp;#39;t finish. They said it was in their top 5 fantasy books so I finally caved in and read the first book.  Overall, I really wasn&amp;#39;t impressed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My biggest gripes were:
1)  Having Kovthe tell the story. It kinda breaks any suspense of what will happen to him if we already know he&amp;#39;ll turn out basically fine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2)  The prose itself was pretty good, he definitely has a way with words. But sometimes it almost felt arrogant, like he was trying to show off by his writing
 It took me out of the story sometimes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Probably my biggest problem, Kovthe is just ridiculous. He is like the epitome of &amp;quot;....and then the entire room stood up and clapped for me&amp;quot;. Like that literally happens lol.  He is just the best at everything; youngest wizard ever, all the girls love him, super intelligent, greatest musician, literally talks about how he knows how to size up a horse and a town.  Its so stupid. There are no real challenges in his life. He talks about how &amp;quot;if this were a made up story things would have just worked out great, but they didnt&amp;quot; yet two chapters later he&amp;#39;s figured everything out and everyone clapped.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I could go on, but I&amp;#39;ll stop fow now.  I&amp;#39;ll probably read the second book just to shut my friends up, but overall, definitely not my favorite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[偷書賊》--馬庫斯-祖薩克]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一本我以前曾試圖讀過兩三遍的書
但我就是做不到。我總是讀到5、6頁就停下來。然後，這本書會
就這樣被遺忘在那裏。

但這次我終於做到了 老實說，我不知道爲什麼我沒有能夠
早點讀完它。

我被吸...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ynxc/the_book_thief_markus_zusak/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ynxc/the_book_thief_markus_zusak/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 21:57:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is one book that I&amp;#39;ve made an attempt to read two or three times previously but I just couldn&amp;#39;t do it. I&amp;#39;d always stop at 5 or 6 pages. Then, the book would just lay forgotten there. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I finally did it this time! And I honestly don&amp;#39;t know why I wasn&amp;#39;t able to read it earlier. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was sucked into the world right from the start. Markus Zusak&amp;#39;s writing style was just so different and easy to read through. I was flying through the book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The stoy itself is so honest, raw and heart-wrenching. Liesel is such an extraordinary character and this story is so powerful. All the others characters were well fleshed out and the ending broke my heart. I&amp;#39;ve not read a lot of World War-centric books but now, I think I&amp;#39;m going to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不要孤獨，不要無所事事"：400年曆史的自助書的祕密被解開了]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8vr1n/be_not_solitary_be_not_idle_secrets_of_400yearold/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8vr1n/be_not_solitary_be_not_idle_secrets_of_400yearold/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 19:08:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[斯蒂芬-金的書有那麼可怕嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從來沒有讀過他的書，因爲我一般不喜歡血腥或非常恐怖的東西。
恐怖的東西。不過我倒是喜歡有一些恐怖元素的驚悚小說。你認爲斯蒂芬-金的書屬於哪種類型？
你會把斯蒂芬-金的書放在哪一端？從1-10的恐怖程度和
可能給我帶來惡夢的程度？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8mdiq/are_stephen_king_books_that_scary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8mdiq/are_stephen_king_books_that_scary/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 18:29:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve never read one of his books because I generally don&amp;#39;t like gore or very scary stuff. I do enjoy thrillers with some scary elements though. What end of the scary spectrum would you place Stephen King&amp;#39;s books? From 1-10 how scary and likely to give me nightmares are they?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[霍比特人》值得作爲一個獨立的作品來閱讀嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，兩年前我試圖閱讀《指環王》，但無法進入其中。
它。

我聽說《霍比特人》是一本很好的溫馨讀物，那麼我應該去讀嗎？或者
我是否應該再給《指環王》三部曲一個機會？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8yorg/is_the_hobbit_worth_reading_as_a_stand_alone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8yorg/is_the_hobbit_worth_reading_as_a_stand_alone/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 17:32:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I tried to read &amp;#39;The Lord Of The Rings&amp;#39; 2 years ago, but couldn&amp;#39;t get into it..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have heard that &amp;#39;The Hobbit&amp;#39; is a great cozy read..So should I go for it? Or should I give Lord of the rings trilogy one more chance?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪些書是你至少重讀2遍的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[> 我知道這不是一個推薦書籍的子，但這有助於人們找到一些
> 偉大的書籍，因爲這個分站有更多的成員，所以請不要刪除
> 這個帖子

我是個新書迷，去年才養成讀書的習慣，讀的書很少。
我是個新書迷，去年剛養成了讀書的習慣，讀了一些書，有一件事讓我印象深刻，那就是選...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8wzwt/what_are_the_books_you_reread_at_least_2_times/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8wzwt/what_are_the_books_you_reread_at_least_2_times/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 15:58:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I know this is not a book suggesting sub, but this helps people find some great books because there are more members in this sub, so please don&amp;#39;t remove this post&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m new to books, I just adopted the reading habit last year, and read few books, and one thing that striking me is to pick that particular book and re-read it again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know the exact reason, maybe I wanna experience it again, maybe look at the whole story in another way, or I just don&amp;#39;t understand the way the author wrote.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whatever it might be, we re-read it because we think it&amp;#39;s a masterpiece and worth enough time to spend again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, these are books I re-read(some I read twice and some are once but I don&amp;#39;t mind reading them again because I consider them as a masterpiece):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Stranger by Albert Camus - Short book, and at first I didn&amp;#39;t understand shit, done it twice and got the whole picture clearly (&lt;em&gt;I don&amp;#39;t mind reading it again&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Surely You&amp;#39;re Joking Mr. Feynman by Himself - What can I say about this book, every chapter is just awesome and when I share these stories with my friends they all seem to be interested to listen to know more about Richard Feynman. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Influence by Robert Cialdini - In the first chapter itself, it hooked me into the book, and everything he said in the book is just purely based on psychological experiments and they are interesting too (&lt;em&gt;Also happened to pick Pre-Suasion and read but this book is not just the level of Influence book&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Start With Why by Simon Sinek - After his Ted Talk, I just inspired to pick the book and I read it and All I can say this is more than I imagined (&lt;em&gt;That time I was more into business and want to study companies so that I can build a good company so I re-read 2 times&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Originals By Adam Grant - Yes, the same as above, want to study how originals are made of and I just wanna study more in detail and know better.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Subtle Art Of Not Giving A Fuck by Mark Manson - Twice and I can&amp;#39;t say how much it impacted my life and also his entire blog is just awesome (&lt;em&gt;Models also a great book by him&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How To Fail At Almost Everything &amp;amp; Still Win Big by Scott Adams - No more words for this book, many of the self-help books took inspiration from this book because it just a masterpiece.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Obstacle Is The Way By Ryan Holiday - I can say he&amp;#39;s the best stoic writer and he just brings Marcus Aurelius, Seneca, Epictetus (&lt;em&gt;I can&amp;#39;t easily comprehend these people&amp;#39;s work easily without the help of a dictionary&lt;/em&gt;) work in simple words and explains clearly with historical stories that happened in the past (&lt;em&gt;Also Ego Is the Enemy is also a great book IMO&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Man&amp;#39;s Searching For Meaning by Viktor Frankl - You all already know why it&amp;#39;s a masterpiece.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Requiem For A Dream by  Hubert Selby - This doesn&amp;#39;t come under re-reading because I&amp;#39;m not that strong enough but I consider this is just a masterpiece. At first, my friend suggested me movie and also he said it was adopted from a novel, So I just picked the book and read it, I didn&amp;#39;t understand few things but overall I felt it&amp;#39;s fine and then, I watched the movie, it was more painful and I couldn&amp;#39;t recommend enough to any teenager to read this book or watch the movie at least (&lt;em&gt;Mostly Movie&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you may probably be thinking I&amp;#39;m an amateur because I mostly mentioned self-help books, yes I read around 40+ and mostly are self-help genre.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, you can list yours, so that people here will understand what are some great books. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;#39;t hesitate if it&amp;#39;s fiction or biographies or even self-help, list out any kind of genre and the right people will find them as a great recommendation.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The House In The Cerulean Sea》值得一讀嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是讀着《哈利-波特》長大的，已經讀了好幾遍。

我是否會以同樣的方式被這本書迷住？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8svbs/is_the_house_in_the_cerulean_sea_worth_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8svbs/is_the_house_in_the_cerulean_sea_worth_reading/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 14:55:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have grown up reading Harry Potter several times..&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Will I be enchanted in the same manner by this book?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國人的思想被束縛]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不久前讀完了這本書，我認爲這是一本非常重要的書。Haidt
和Lukianoff（作者）討論了他們所謂的 "安全主義 "在美國的興起。
美國的 "安全主義 "的興起，以及它是如何反作用於我們並創造出一種不容忍和脆弱的文化。
脆弱的文化。他們提出了令人信服的論點。

我在想...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ns9j/the_coddling_of_the_american_mind/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ns9j/the_coddling_of_the_american_mind/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 13:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finished this book a bit ago, and I think it&amp;#39;s a really important read.  Haidt and Lukianoff (the authors) discuss the rise of what they call &amp;quot;safetyism&amp;quot; in America, and how it&amp;#39;s backfiring on us and creating a culture of intolerance and fragility.  They make convincing arguments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering who else had read it and what your thoughts were.  Specifically:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Students or teachers in academia these days: what did you think of the book&amp;#39;s portrayal of college campuses?  As some one who graduated college in 2007, I found the scenarios they detail quite disturbing.  They describe a culture of students who deem opposing ideas &amp;quot;harmful&amp;quot;, hunting out the ideologically impure and punishing them along with anyone who sides with them, which sounds a lot like Mao&amp;#39;s Cultural Revolution, which they also reference in the book.  Or Twitter come to life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Parents: What did you think of the book&amp;#39;s depictions child-rearing over the years: how now there is less free play and way more scheduled, adult-supervised activities.  Do you see or feel this difference?  I&amp;#39;m not a parent so I really wonder what it&amp;#39;s like raising kids these days.  Not easy, I&amp;#39;m sure!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Anyone and everyone else: any interesting points that I left out?  Any counterarguments to the book&amp;#39;s hypothesis?  Or agreements?  I&amp;#39;m all ears.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你認爲喬治-RR-馬丁和帕特里克-羅斯福斯發生了什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[本世紀最著名和最成功的兩位作家，都已經
似乎都停止了寫作。

羅斯福斯據說正在完成他的三部曲，但他的最後一本書是在十多年前（2011年）出版的。
十年前（2011年）。

馬丁在他的7部系列中寫了5本書。他的最後一部作品也是在2011年發佈的。

你是怎麼...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8t83d/what_do_you_think_happened_to_george_rr_martin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8t83d/what_do_you_think_happened_to_george_rr_martin/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 11:31:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the most famous and successful writers of this century and both have seemingly stopped writing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rothfuss is supposedly finishing his trilogy but his last book was released over a decade ago (2011).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Martin has written 5 books in his 7 part series. His last release was also 2011.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think happened to these men? Too much pressure? Lost the spark and passion?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m actually surprised the publishing houses havent sued for breach of contract or hired ghost writers to help.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not one of those fans who insist they should write. I actually think its fine if they retire (although I will be sad) but the silence is very unusual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you guys make of it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我喜歡《傲慢與偏見》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如標題所說，我喜歡《傲慢與偏見》。我最喜歡的書之一。不
我不知道還有多少人喜歡這本書，但我毫不羞愧地說，我
愛它。首先，伊麗莎白-班納特是一個令人難以置信的女主角，我很難找到像她這樣的人。
我很難找到像她這樣的人。這些人物...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8p59t/i_love_pride_and_prejudice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8p59t/i_love_pride_and_prejudice/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 05:53:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the title says, I love Pride and Prejudice. One of my favorite books. Don’t know how many other guys love that book but I have no shame in saying that I love it. First off, Elizabeth Bennet is an incredibly awesome heroine and I have a hard time finding others who are like her. The characters are all well developed and some very humorous (looking at you Mr Collins). Personally (potwntial spoilers ahead) I find tremendous hilarity when a certain  someone make an attempt at a marriage proposal( a proprsal which should taught as an example of how &amp;quot;not&amp;quot; to make a proposal). The book also gives a great analysis or class/privalage and the sort during its era. I could go on for longer but I won&amp;#39;t to waste any more of anyones time.  I&amp;#39;d be happy to discuss more in PM&amp;#39;s though&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在這個子裏有很多人不是天然的讀者嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道很多人在成長過程中讀了很多書，後來現在可以
以閃電般的速度閱讀。

然而，我很好奇，這裏是否有像我這樣的 "遲到者 "讀者？
我自己？如果有的話，是什麼讓你開始閱讀娛樂的？

我在20歲的時候開始學習歷史，並且...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ii1g/are_there_many_people_in_this_sub_who_are_not/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ii1g/are_there_many_people_in_this_sub_who_are_not/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 04:29:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know many people who read a lot of books growing up and subsequently can now read at a lightning fast pace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I&amp;#39;m curious if there are any &amp;#39;late to the party&amp;#39; readers in here like myself? And if so, what got you into reading for entertainment?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started studying History when I was 20 and read &amp;#39;Brave New World&amp;#39; as people kept on referring to it in my classes. I also now find reading to be a duty, even if it is at a snail&amp;#39;s pace. I feel like I owe it to myself to read, by our society&amp;#39;s standards, the best books ever written.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;edit: grammar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英國圖書館和博物館聯合起來，從私人買家手中拯救 "驚人的 "失落圖書館]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ld0j/uk_libraries_and_museums_unite_to_save/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8ld0j/uk_libraries_and_museums_unite_to_save/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 02:12:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[祕密的歷史]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完唐娜-塔特的《祕密歷史》，非常喜歡。
我實際上要去本寧頓學院，該學院是哈姆登學院的基礎，也是塔特學習的地方。
總之，我讀過她的其他書，但我不是很喜歡。
但我不是她的超級粉絲。有沒有人對她的書有什麼建議？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8jbok/the_secret_history/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8jbok/the_secret_history/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 01:09:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished the Secret History by Donna Tartte and LOVED it. (Side Note: I’m actually going to Bennington College which is the college that Hamden College is based on and where Tartte studied) anyways I have read her other books but I wasn’t a huge fan. Does anyone have any suggestions for books with a similar vibe to this one?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你讀過的哪本書不止一次，而且一直讓你感覺很特別？]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們。

我一直在努力尋找一本好書來填補夏天的時間。
夏天。在重讀了一些我最喜歡的書之後，我想知道是否有誰
你們中的任何一個人有一個故事，你總是去看它。這本書是什麼，它給你
這種驚人的、永不滿足的幸福和愛的感覺...。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8fx8b/which_book_have_you_read_more_than_once_and_has/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o8fx8b/which_book_have_you_read_more_than_once_and_has/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 01:09:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been struggling to find a good book to fill in the time during the summer. And after re-reading some of my favorite books, I was wondering if any of you has a story, which you always go to. What is this book that gives you this amazing insatiable feeling of happiness and love towards that specific story and characters?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love to hear your suggestions and what makes them so special for you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[陀思妥耶夫斯基與俄羅斯的命名規則]]></title><description><![CDATA[今天看完了《罪與罰》，很喜歡，但我對俄羅斯的命名方式非常不熟悉，這讓我非常困惑。
但我對俄羅斯的命名慣例極爲陌生，這讓我在閱讀時感到非常困惑。
在閱讀過程中。有誰能向我解釋一下，不同的名字變化背後是什麼？
名的不同變化？

例如，羅迪昂-羅曼諾維奇-拉斯科利尼科夫又名羅迪亞又名......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8a6yr/dostoevsky_russian_naming_conventions/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8a6yr/dostoevsky_russian_naming_conventions/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 17:46:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finished and loved Crime and Punishment today, but I am extremely unfamiliar with Russian naming conventions which was a source of great confusion for me while reading. Can anybody explain to me what is behind the different variations of names? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;E.g. Rodion Romanovitch Raskolnikov aka Rodya aka Rodenka aka Rodka&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dmitri Prokovitch Razumikhin aka Mitia aka Mitry aka Mitka&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Avdotia Romanovna Raskolnikov aka Dunya aka Dunechka&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;or &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sofya Semyonovna Marmeladov aka Sonya aka Somechka&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like I kind of missed out on the implied context of the name variations, so I’d really appreciate if someone who has some background knowledge about this could help me out here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[起初我想，這太瘋狂了"：利用小說預測下一場戰爭的真實計劃]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8a3wv/at_first_i_thought_this_is_crazy_the_reallife/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8a3wv/at_first_i_thought_this_is_crazy_the_reallife/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 16:33:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1984年的結局]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近讀完了喬治-奧威爾的《1984》，這本書很精彩，但是
結局是令人難以置信的病態和相當的靈魂崩潰。個人永遠無法克服來自政府的不可逾越的控制，而這一想法
個人永遠無法克服來自政府的不可逾越的控制和順從的壓力。
在結束這本書時，我被嚇壞了。我正在努力...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8bgml/the_ending_of_1984/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8bgml/the_ending_of_1984/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:20:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading George Orwell&amp;#39;s &lt;em&gt;1984&lt;/em&gt; and it was fantastic, but the ending was incredibly morbid and quite soul crushing. The idea that the individual can never overcome the insurmountable control from the government and pressure to conform left me floored upon ending the book. I&amp;#39;m trying to make sure I fully understand the authors decision of the ending because I know there is good reason behind it and I&amp;#39;m curious what you all thought about it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["西線靜悄悄》，E.M.雷馬克著]]></title><description><![CDATA[幾天前我讀完了《西線靜悄悄》。所以這是
我開始閱讀雷馬克的第一本書。我對他感到非常高興。這本書
這本書迫使我思考成爲一名士兵的真正含義，以及在戰爭中是否有任何榮譽？
在戰爭中是否有任何榮譽？我曾經想過要成爲一名軍人。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8a70m/all_quiet_on_the_western_front_by_e_m_remarque/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o8a70m/all_quiet_on_the_western_front_by_e_m_remarque/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 14:29:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve finished «All Quiet on the Western Front» several days ago. So this the first book since I started reading Remarque. And I&amp;#39;m very delighted of him. This book is forcing to think about what really means to be a soldier and would there is any honour at war? Once I thought about to become a soldier and even dreamed to work in the special forces maybe. But this book and changes in my mental health turn my minds of military in another way. I don&amp;#39;t have the wishes to become the soldier anymore. I want to be a medic. Remarque showed the war as it really is. No honour, no heroism, only lousy trenches and fear of death. Also I learnt some material about the World War I. There is an opinion that because Entente has superior in manpower, it could to lose more than Germany and its Allies. It really hard to realise that your Motherland don&amp;#39;t care about your personality. It only cares that you&amp;#39;re a soldier — manpower that can be spent for the most terrific purposes. And in general, World War I seemed more scary than World War II (even WWII has much more deaths). It breaks all values and foundations of the past. World before WWI and after is very different. If after WWII was the Cold War but people were really happy and enjoy the peace, so after WWI the humanity had the global pandemic, terrific economic crisis and rise of totalitarianism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also I wanted to pay attention to some shocking scenes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1) I really love how Remarque showed Kemmerich&amp;#39;s death. He is literally given a page, but how it affects on me. I almost cried. It&amp;#39;s the young boy who only ended a college and he died at war. He was very young and he died. His leg was cut off. Author make the emotional effect more stronger by telling the past of this guy. Masterpiece.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2) Entire chapter when Paul came home on vacations. Remarque showed his returning very nice. Some time ago the main hero was under shelling, and now he&amp;#39;s enjoying his home and places of childhood. He even doesn&amp;#39;t trust what happens. He regrets he came home. And farewell with mother finally breaks my heart. It very familiar to me to be far away out of mother. Honestly, I cried at this scene. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3) Scene where Paul killed the French soldier. Oh my God. What a monologue. What reason to some German kill some French, really? And here I realised one thing. I&amp;#39;ve got how propaganda profitable to the Governments in war is. Only think about this. It&amp;#39;s really hard to kill another man thinking that he has a beloved wife kids. He can love, suffer and cry as you. So during the wars propaganda dehumanize the enemy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;4) The pre final chapter. This one nicely showed how Germany was demoralized at the end of WWI. Poor and hungry they were retreating from their positions. And the deaths of all main heroes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually. I&amp;#39;d like to say that Remarque is the genius of his time. He&amp;#39;s one of the first who was talking about how war terrible is. He literally showed truly face of war. And now I totally get what for his books were under ban in the Nazi Germany.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>