<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jul 2021 07:22:38 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[我是保羅-特魯，旅行作家和56本書的作者--美國。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是許多備受讚譽的遊記和小說的作者，包括《鐵路大巴扎》、《蚊子海岸》、《蛇的平原》和《海底世界》。
大鐵路集市》、《蚊子海岸》、《在蛇的平原上》和《在威美亞的海浪下》。
威美亞的海浪下
[https://www.hmhbooks.com/shop/books/Under-the-Wave-at-Waimea/9780358446286]。在
2015年，我被授予英國皇家勳章。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n20yaj/i_am_paul_theroux_travel_writer_and_author_of_56/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n20yaj/i_am_paul_theroux_travel_writer_and_author_of_56/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 21:37:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m the author of many highly acclaimed travelogues and novels, including The Great Railway Bazaar, The Mosquito Coast, On the Plain of Snakes, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.hmhbooks.com/shop/books/Under-the-Wave-at-Waimea/9780358446286&quot;&gt;Under the Wave at Waimea&lt;/a&gt;. In 2015, I was awarded a Royal Medal from the Royal Geographical Society for “the encouragement of geographical discovery through travel writing.” My books, The Old Patagonian Express: By Train through the Americas, and The Mosquito Coast were both nominated for the American Book Award. Many of my books have been made into films and series including The Mosquito Coast, which is now an Apple TV series starring my nephew, Justin Theroux. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn more about me here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paultheroux.com/&quot;&gt;https://www.paultheroux.com/&lt;/a&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/paultheroux_?lang=en&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/paultheroux_?lang=en&lt;/a&gt;
Instagram: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/paul.theroux/?hl=en&quot;&gt;https://www.instagram.com/paul.theroux/?hl=en&lt;/a&gt;
Facebook: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/Paul-Theroux-1021525607879470/&quot;&gt;https://www.facebook.com/Paul-Theroux-1021525607879470/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/i7xqhiaperv61.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/i7xqhiaperv61.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我已經19歲了，我是不是太老了，不能閱讀和欣賞《烏鴉六號》（或《影子與骨頭》）？]]></title><description><![CDATA[Netflix的節目效果一般，但我想閱讀書籍並填補
填補該劇留下的空白。他們可以在世界建設方面做得更好。
一切都顯得如此倉促，我想他們可能錯過了一些重要的
事情。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1ud6j/im_19_yo_am_i_too_old_to_read_and_appreciate_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1ud6j/im_19_yo_am_i_too_old_to_read_and_appreciate_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 20:27:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Netflix show turned out average but I&amp;#39;d like to read the books and fill in the gaps the show left. They could&amp;#39;ve done better with the world building, everything seemed so rushed I think they might have missed some important things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你一直回味的一本書是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我讀過列夫-托爾斯泰的《安娜-卡列尼娜》，從那時起，它就一直伴隨着我。每次
當我拿起任何一本書時，我都會情不自禁地在《安娜-卡列尼娜》中的人物之間找到相似之處。
安娜-卡列尼娜》中的人物。公平地說，這是一本相當長的書，所以我想它的影響已經很深了。
我想它的影響遠遠大於其他的書，因爲它的數量......。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1q31q/what_is_one_book_you_keep_going_back_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1q31q/what_is_one_book_you_keep_going_back_to/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 15:53:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read Anna Karenina by Leo Tolstoy and it has stuck with me ever since. Every time I pick up any book I can&amp;#39;t help but draw similarities between the characters of Anna Karenina. Well to be fair it is quite a long book so I suppose it&amp;#39;s impact has been far greater than any other due to the amount of time I spent with it. However it is one book that I think will stay with me for a while😄.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[雙城記》在今天非常有意義。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在閱讀《雙城記》，並意識到我們正在經歷狄更斯在小說中批評的那種制度性衰敗。
我們正在經歷狄更斯在小說中所批評的那種制度上的腐化。蒙西涅爾是
是這種腐朽的一個特別有趣的代表，因爲他展示了
體制可以被腐蝕到不再有任何作用的地步......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1tnb9/a_tale_of_two_cities_is_very_relevant_today/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1tnb9/a_tale_of_two_cities_is_very_relevant_today/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 15:28:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m reading A Tale of Two Cities, and realizing that we are experiencing the same sort of institutional decay Dickens criticized in the novel. Monseigneur is a particularly interesting representation of this decay because he shows how institutions can be corrupted to the point where they no longer serve their intended purpose.  I couldn&amp;#39;t help but think about our media, and how they are so corrupted by ideology that they lost touch with reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They think they are Madame Defarge, when really they are Monseigneur.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們能不能談談沃爾特-艾薩克森的《達芬奇傳》？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完這本神奇的書，它確實是我最喜歡的書之一。
最大的讀物之一。沃爾特-艾薩克森（Walter Isaacson），這位大師級的傳記作家，出色地向我們展示了一位天才的一生。
一位天才的一生，他的興趣範圍從行星運動到古怪的
如 "啄木鳥的舌頭分析"。你沒看錯。一...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1jchh/can_we_please_talk_about_leonardo_da_vincis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1jchh/can_we_please_talk_about_leonardo_da_vincis/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 11:25:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading this amazing book and it was genuinely one of my greatest reads. Walter Isaacson, the master biographer, brilliantly  shows us the life of a genius, whose interests ranged from planetary motion to as eccentric as &amp;quot;analysis of a woodpecker&amp;#39;s tongue&amp;quot;. You read that right. One cannot help but marvel at the genius of Leonardo and appreciate the calibre of his mind! Had he published his works, he would have deservingly been credited with the discovery of friction, Bernoulli&amp;#39;s laws, Newton&amp;#39;s third law, functioning of the aortic valve and the scientific method. He was centuries ahead of his time and his fascinating notebooks are filled with beautiful drawings of anatomy, which have been explained in a simple manner by Walter Isaacson. Science aside, I don&amp;#39;t think I need to mention his world famous paintings like Mona lisa, the last supper and my favourite, Saint John the Baptist. He was as much as an artist as a scientist and had a intense curiosity about everything in the world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are  some key ideas I learned from the book which I&amp;#39;m surely going to implement in my own life:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;1)  Be curious. Be relentlessly curious about everything. It can be as vague as  &amp;quot;inspecting the tongue of a woodpecker&amp;quot; and as serious as understanding the way light from the sun reaches the planets&amp;quot;. Just have a relentless  and a random curiosity about everything life has to offer and be a seeker of knowledge.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2)  Seek knowledge not to make a profit or boast, but for its own sake. Seek knowledge to appreciate and enjoy life. &amp;quot;Not all knowledge has to be useful. Sometimes it can for pure pleasure&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;3)   Retain  a child-like sense of wonder. Don a mask of simplicity and like a child, look at the world as a canvas full of colours and scenes to be drawn upon.

4)  Always wonder about why things are the way they are. We may appreciate the blue sky, but we never reflect on why the sky is blue. Leonardo did. And so did Einstein.

5)  Observe! Observe everything and enjoy movement, silence and flow of nature around you.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;6)  Go down rabbit holes that amaze you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;7)  Be fearless about changing your opinions as you gather new insights and let go of your past knowledge if new facts disapprove it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;8)  Be a perfectionist. Don&amp;#39;t settle for  &amp;quot;good enough&amp;quot;.  Delay projects if you feel they are not perfect. Leonardo carried Mona Lisa and Adoration of the Magi with him even during his final moments, always ready for a new stroke of the brush. Likewise, Steve jobs made sure the circuit boards of the first Macintosh looked beautiful, even though nobody was going to see them. &amp;quot;Real artists care about the beauty of the parts unseen&amp;quot;.

9) Create not only for others and for profit, but for your personal joy.
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;10) Collaborate. One man can never surpass what 100 men can do together. Singular vision may be important, but execution is often best with a team.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;11) Take notes about things that inspire you

12) Be open to mysteries. Not everything needs sharp lines and well definitions. Had that been the case, the beautiful Sfumato so vivid in Mona Lisa would never exist ( The renowned &amp;quot;seductive&amp;quot; smile of Mona Lisa is accomplished through a Leonardo special technique called Sfumato)
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s it. I hope you guys found this valuable. Have a good day:))&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你自己的個人圈子有閱讀嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不是在說我們在網上的朋友，我是指你自己的朋友和家人。
人，他們是否真的閱讀，還是你是孤獨的書蟲？我自己的個人
說他們只是不善於閱讀，所以他們不看書，這使
在討論書的時候，我是孤獨的，除了......。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n17cnx/does_your_own_personal_circle_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n17cnx/does_your_own_personal_circle_read/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 05:29:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not talking about friends we have online, I mean your own friends and family in person, do they actually read or you the lone book worm?  My own personal circle says they are just not good readers so they don&amp;#39;t read books which leaves me all alone when it comes to discussing books except for reddit. I&amp;#39;m wondering if most people aren&amp;#39;t really that into reading compared to watching movies and TV shows?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[輕鬆閱讀，感覺像一個溫暖的懷抱]]></title><description><![CDATA[我現在正在經歷一個非常困難的時期，只是需要從痛苦中轉移注意力。
分散對痛苦的注意力。我最近讀了《塞魯利亞海的房子》，並希望
我還沒有讀過，所以我現在可以讀它，因爲它正是我需要的那類書。
需要的。正在尋找其他充滿生命力、快樂的有趣的書，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1gs9p/easy_reads_that_feel_like_a_warm_hug/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n1gs9p/easy_reads_that_feel_like_a_warm_hug/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m going through a really difficult time right now and just need to be distracted from the pain. I recently read The House in the Cerulean Sea and wish I hadn’t read it yet so I could read it now, as it’s exactly the type of book I need. Looking for other fun books that are full of life, joy, and hope. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我將進入一個康復項目，只能帶書，我所有的 "書 "都是有聲的，我不能帶任何 "聰明 "的東西來聽。我不是在尋找慈善機構，只要有指導就好了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在Reddit上寫了很多東西，但這是迄今爲止我覺得最不安的一次
的帖子。我開始創建另一個賬戶，但決定，如果有什麼事情。
能夠看到我的個人資料和活動歷史可以幫助表明這
是真實的，而不僅僅是一些一勞永逸的賬戶。

所以我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1gwe3/going_into_a_rehab_program_and_can_only_bring/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n1gwe3/going_into_a_rehab_program_and_can_only_bring/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Apr 2021 02:25:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve written a good bit on Reddit but this is by far the most uneasy I’ve felt about a post. I started to create another account but decided that if anything, being able to see my profile and history of activity could help show that this is genuine and not just some one and done account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I’m going into a 60-day program, state funded and free (which is amazing), and I’ve a pack list of what I can and can’t bring. All the hygenics, 7 days of clothes, etc. I’ve got. But the line that hits me is the last.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The last line of things to bring are comfort items. “Photos, books, letters”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don’t really have any photos or letters, the few I have just make me sad so I figure they’re best left home. But as audible books have been my escape for so long, I feel like books are one thing that could mean a lot. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know we’ll have counseling throughout each weekday (not sure about weekends), and a gym to work out in once a day, but due to covid they’ve suspended any visitation from family, any leaving the site, so for 60 days it’s just me and the 13 other people in there with me. I plan and hope to make friends, but even with friends there’s only so much time you can spend before you just want to read a book and escape to another world for a while.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thought about the library but that’s a no go as there’s no way to return them, or even extend the rental from inside as internet and such is non-grata.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I was wondering if someone had any advice? I imagine there has to be people with books they wouldn’t care to get rid of, I know when I read Game of Thrones I kept forgetting to bring it to work and I’d just buy another copy cause I couldn’t wait my whole shift to read the next chapter. I must’ve ended up with 2-3 copies of each book and probably four copies of the first one. That was years ago though when I was still working as a paramedic and could afford to buy a book just to avoid having to go all day without reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oh how times have changed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any advice, recommendations, or thoughts would be truly appreciated. I’ll be honest, I’m absolutely terrified at the idea of doing this but frankly I’m out of options and this is my last hope of getting things together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if anyone’s spent time in a similar setting I’d love to hear any advice or thoughts you have.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[主角年齡在20歲以上的奇幻作品]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜歡幻想，但對閱讀青少年的幻想非常厭煩。我讀過《洛特勒》和
asoiaf。我想探索一個新的世界 :)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n14sc8/fantasy_that_has_protagonists_aged_mid_20s_and_up/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n14sc8/fantasy_that_has_protagonists_aged_mid_20s_and_up/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 22:57:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love fantasy but am very tired of reading ab teenagers. I&amp;#39;ve read lotr and asoiaf.
I want to explore a new world :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幻想的浪漫（蒸汽書是在桌上）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我們都知道，禁閉使我們感到孤獨，需要一些好的老式的
淫蕩。我希望能有一個幻想中的浪漫故事，最好能有一些更成熟/性感的部分。
碎片。我剛剛看完一部海盜題材的浪漫小說，我很喜歡，我需要更多！希望我能夠找到我想要的。
希望我能在這裏找到我完美的下一個讀物！！。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n138k3/fantasy_romance_steamy_book_are_on_the_table/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n138k3/fantasy_romance_steamy_book_are_on_the_table/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 18:42:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we all know lockdown has us lonely and in need of some good old fashioned steaminess. I would love a fantasy romance with preferably some more adult/sexy bits. I’ve just finished a pirate romance and I loved it and I need more! Hopefully I’ll find my perfect next read on here!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[研究顯示印刷書籍仍比電子書更受歡迎]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n134y4/study_shows_printed_books_are_still_preferred_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n134y4/study_shows_printed_books_are_still_preferred_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 14:34:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[教師稱幻想不是 "文學"]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我是荷蘭的一名高中生。我重新開始閱讀
就在幾個月前，我讀了很多英文的幻想小說（目前正在讀mistborn）。
目前正在讀《迷霧》）。) 幾天前，我很想看看是否有任何
來自荷蘭的奇幻經典作品。所以我在網上查了一下，以...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n11u0f/teacher_claims_that_fantasy_isnt_literature/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n11u0f/teacher_claims_that_fantasy_isnt_literature/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 12:41:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, so I&amp;#39;m a high-school student in the Netherlands. I got back into reading just a couple of months ago and I read a lot of fantasy in English (currently reading mistborn). A few days ago, I was interested in seeing if there are any fantasy classics from the Netherlands. So I looked up online, to see if there is some kind of &amp;quot;Dutch Tolkien&amp;quot;. I couldn&amp;#39;t find a lot, so I went and asked my Dutch Literature teacher if there is a fantasy genre in Dutch literature and if she knows of a &amp;quot;Dutch Tolkien&amp;quot;. She told me bluntly that I shouldn&amp;#39;t read fantasy and that she doesn&amp;#39;t consider it to be &amp;quot;real literature&amp;quot;. She basically thinks that Tolkien&amp;#39;s books aren&amp;#39;t &amp;quot;real literature&amp;quot;. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That teacher is one of the biggest gatekeepers I know. She keeps rambling about how sad it is that kids don&amp;#39;t read much anymore and then she literally claims that certain genres shouldn&amp;#39;t be read. She&amp;#39;s also one of those people who say that listening to audiobooks doesn&amp;#39;t count as reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well I&amp;#39;m just gonna keep reading my &amp;quot;not real literature&amp;quot; and my teacher can continue being an ignorant gatekeeper.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在尋找一本有祕密的門、房間、地下通道，以及需要解決的謎題的書 !]]></title><description><![CDATA[看完繼承遊戲後，我覺得深陷其中。解開謎團和尋找線索的概念
揭開神祕面紗和尋找線索的概念真的給我帶來了興趣。我一直
試圖找到類似的東西，但沒有成功。因此，如果有人知道有什麼書
有這樣的概念，請讓我知道!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0sphc/im_looking_for_a_book_with_secrets_doors_rooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0sphc/im_looking_for_a_book_with_secrets_doors_rooms/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 04:47:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After reading inheritance game I feel deep into it. The concept of solving mysteries and looking for clues really brought an interest in me. I’ve been trying to find something similar but failed. So if anyone know any books that have that concept please let me know !&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我最近發現，我對更多的癡迷已經破壞了我對閱讀的熱情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從小就喜歡讀書。我已經達到了這樣的程度
每年閱讀近100本書，涉及許多不同的流派。一旦covid開始。
我意識到，我永遠不可能讀完所有我想讀的書，這讓我
這讓我陷入了一個存在感極低的漩渦。我癱瘓了，而且...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0fnpl/ive_recently_discovered_that_my_obsession_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0fnpl/ive_recently_discovered_that_my_obsession_with/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 03:31:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always loved to read from a young age. It had gotten to a point where I was reading nearly 100 books a year from many different genres. Once covid started, I realized that I&amp;#39;d never be able to read everything I wanted to, and it sent me into an existential, downward spiral. I was paralyzed, and instead of doing the expected and reading even more, I scrutinized my reading speed and how many pages I needed to get through each day. When I inevitably failed to reach my goals, I was disappointed and began to lose the love of reading I had in the past. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently, I began to come to terms with this. Stemming from the realization that life itself is finite. It&amp;#39;s funny, I obviously always knew that life is fleeting, but I never fully understood this. After reading some works by ancient stoic philosophers I realized, that quantity is never the answer. A person that reads few books well, is often much wiser than one that reads many books hastily. I&amp;#39;m sure this &amp;quot;profound&amp;quot; realization is trivial for a lot of you, but it has certainly helped me to grapple with the impending sense of &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;m not moving fast enough and that&amp;#39;s a bad thing.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your time when you read, life and books are beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想閱讀希臘神話的內容]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想讀一本關於所有那些著名的希臘神話故事和他們的神的書。
他們的諸神，但不知道從哪裏開始。是否有一本書包含所有的
故事，還是有很多故事？我不知道。

提前謝謝你。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0cw83/i_want_to_read_about_greek_mythology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0cw83/i_want_to_read_about_greek_mythology/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2021 02:25:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to read a book about all those famous stories of greek mythology and their gods, but don&amp;#39;t know where to begin. Is there a book that contains all the stories, or are there many? I have no idea.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[給我推薦一本從男性角度出發的關於如何處理分手的書。如果是小說形式的就更好了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[分手的話題是由女性壟斷的，正如我所感受到的那樣。如果我能在這方面得到一些男性的建議，那將是
如果我能在這方面得到一些男性的建議就好了，最好是以小說或
故事的形式。

我真正想要的是這樣一部小說：一個女孩離開一個非常愛她的男人
但以她的標準來說還不夠。他是如何...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0ingl/suggest_me_a_book_from_male_point_of_view_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n0ingl/suggest_me_a_book_from_male_point_of_view_about/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 20:13:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The breakup topic has a monopoly of women as much as I have felt. It will be quite good if I could get some male advice on this, preferably in a novel or a story form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I really want is a novel where a girl leaves a man who loved her immensely but not enough by her standards. How did he overcome that trauma?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P.S: Something like 500 days of summer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DisneyMustPay：作者們組成了一個特別小組，以爭取與《星球大戰》/《復仇者聯盟》/《蜘蛛俠》/《奪寶奇兵》/以及更多書籍和漫畫有關的失蹤版稅付款]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0keso/disneymustpay_authors_form_task_force_to_fight/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0keso/disneymustpay_authors_form_task_force_to_fight/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 18:34:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛讀完斯坦貝克的《憤怒的葡萄》，這是一本好書。(裏面有劇透)]]></title><description><![CDATA[諸位，我無法放下這本書。我知道這本書會很瘋狂，當他們
他們對豬喫嬰兒的事隻字不提。我不得不在谷歌上搜索，以確保我
但顯然，與書中的其他部分相比，這不算什麼。

我繼續讀下去，希望有人，任何一個人，能夠得到一個...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0di8r/just_finished_grapes_of_wrath_by_steinbeck_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n0di8r/just_finished_grapes_of_wrath_by_steinbeck_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 16:02:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yall, I could not put this book down. I knew it was going to be crazy when they just glossed over the pig eating the baby. I had to Google to make sure I was understanding, but obviously this was nothing compared to the rest of the book&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I kept reading on hoping somebody, ANYBODY, would get a semblance of a happy ending. Tom, AL, Rose of Sharon, Ma, ANYONE. But I guess sometimes that isn&amp;#39;t how life works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like this book has some current themes as well about the seeds of discontent, about people who are just continously getting stepped on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All in all I would read it again.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你讀過列夫-托爾斯泰的短篇小說和長篇小說嗎？那麼，現在你的機會來了，所有這些故事都被編入了免費電子書，（據我所知）這還是第一次 在評論中發表你最喜歡的作品吧]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07yo5/have_you_ever_read_leo_tolstoys_short_stories_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07yo5/have_you_ever_read_leo_tolstoys_short_stories_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 08:32:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你讀過的最好的非虛構類書籍是哪一本？]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mznih3/which_is_the_best_nonfiction_book_you_have_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mznih3/which_is_the_best_nonfiction_book_you_have_read/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 07:58:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我很喜歡《無間道》!]]></title><description><![CDATA[有些人可能不同意（這很好），但我認爲《遠征》系列寫得非常好。
寫得非常好......尤其是各種不同的人物和人物發展。

我目前正在閱讀第三冊《阿巴頓之門》，還不到一半的篇幅。
門，我今天剛讀完第10章......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07b3d/i_am_loving_the_expanse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n07b3d/i_am_loving_the_expanse/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 07:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some might disagree (and that’s fine), but I think The Expanse series is so well written…especially the diverse range of characters and character development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m currently about a little bit less than half-way through Book 3 &lt;em&gt;Abaddon’s Gate&lt;/em&gt; and I just finished reading my 10th chapter in just today alone — You know you’re enjoying a book after you’ve read 10 chapters in one day without really realizing it; you think, “I must have read 3…maybe 4 chapters at the most”…then you realize it’s actually 10!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you like the “setting” of &lt;em&gt;Firefly&lt;/em&gt; and the political intrigue and social “dynamics” of &lt;em&gt;Game of Thrones&lt;/em&gt;, I’m almost positive you’ll love The Expanse!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[就讀湮滅。]]></title><description><![CDATA[哇。我剛剛讀了什麼？X區的超現實世界讓我想起了迷幻的
旅行。有沒有類似的書，專注於發現和探索奇怪的
世界？我已經計劃閱讀同一作者的《Borne》。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n03f8f/just_read_annihilation/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n03f8f/just_read_annihilation/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 05:33:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow. What did i just read? The surreal world of Area X reminded me of an acid trip. Is there any books similar that focus on discovering and exploring strange worlds? I already plan on reading Borne by the same author.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幫幫我吧! 我剛剛在Netflix上看完《影子與骨頭》，渴望有一本類似的史詩讀物，但呃......也許是有性的！；)]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的要求不高，只是推薦一些與《影子與骨頭》相似的書。
骨頭。那麼......偉大的性張力，有意義的角色弧線，設定在一個有某種王國/王權的世界裏，並且不迴避性愛場景。
某種王國/皇室的世界，並且不迴避偶爾的性場景
然後....

提前感謝您！!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n01gf3/help_i_just_finished_watching_shadow_bone_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/n01gf3/help_i_just_finished_watching_shadow_bone_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 04:36:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not asking for much, just book suggestions that are similar to Shadow &amp;amp; Bone. So... great sexual tension, meaningful character arcs, set in a world with some sort of kingdom/royalty, and doesn&amp;#39;t shy away from a sex scene every now and then....&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[約翰-勒卡雷的《永恆的園丁》是一部傑作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是我讀到的這位作者的第一部作品，我被他的寫作技巧驚呆了。
他的寫作技巧所震驚。與其他依靠隱瞞信息並在結尾及時揭曉的陰謀/驚悚小說不同
信息並在結尾處及時揭開謎底，勒卡雷提供了一種完全不同的
經驗。他所提供的是一系列不斷擴大的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02yzc/john_le_carrés_the_constant_gardener_is_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02yzc/john_le_carrés_the_constant_gardener_is_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 03:03:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first title I’ve read from this author and I’m stunned by the skill of his writing. Unlike other intrigue/thriller novels which rely on withholding information and a timely reveal at end, Le Carré offers a completely different experience. What he provides is a series of expanding revelations, impressive in detail and research, combined with fully developed characters whose motivations are sometimes not even known to themselves. I’m about 2/3 of the way in and I never want this ride to end.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[血色子午線》。文學中最偉大的最後一段？]]></title><description><![CDATA[幾天前，我第一次讀完了《血色子午線》。我認爲
可以說，很少有小說能像《血色子午線》那樣讓我難以忘懷。
子午線》。我知道它有相當多的批評者，它太蜿蜒曲折。
太暴力，太哲學化，等等。每個人都有自己的看法，我不能...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzzphd/blood_meridian_the_greatest_last_paragraph_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzzphd/blood_meridian_the_greatest_last_paragraph_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:29:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few days ago, I finished reading Blood Meridian for the first time. I think it is fair to say that few novels have ever stuck around with me the way Blood Meridian has. I know it has its fair share of detractors, it’s too meandering, too violent, too philosophical, etc. To each their own, I cannot change your mind. Personally, I thought it was a masterpiece and one of the greatest works of experimental fiction that I have ever read. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I think everything which is so powerful about this novel can be summarized in the last paragraph. I had never thought about what my favorite last paragraph was until reading this book. I have probably reread it six times since finishing and cannot help but be drawn back to it. It is one of the most harrowing passages I have ever read and it serves as a fantastic knot for tying together all of the larger themes, ideas, and meanings of the novel. Everything about it is simply perfect. The lyrical repetition in language, the vividness of imagery, the Biblical allusions, and the deeper metaphorical layers of “the dance”. I found it to be brilliant. The passage is branded into my brain and I know I will go back to reread it many more times. It is a great favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What were your thoughts on this final passage? If it did not resonate with you, which final paragraphs have?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[那裏有一種緊張的氣氛"。出版商因簽署特朗普的官員而受到抨擊]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02xzl/there_is_a_tension_there_publishers_draw_fire_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/n02xzl/there_is_a_tension_there_publishers_draw_fire_for/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 02:29:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在大流行期間開一家小鎮書店是我們做過的最瘋狂的事情]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzvdvy/opening_a_smalltown_bookstore_during_the_pandemic/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzvdvy/opening_a_smalltown_bookstore_during_the_pandemic/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2021 01:20:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有沒有人發現自己有很多喜歡的書，但沒有真正喜歡的作者？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有自己喜歡的作家，但沒有一個能真正歸類爲我的
"最喜歡的"。當然，我也嘗試過閱讀同一些作者的書，但是
但隨着時間的推移，它們要麼變得過於公式化，要麼是令人愉快，但不是我所謂的最愛。
我的最愛。

我對此感到有點自責，因爲...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzou2z/anyone_else_find_themselves_with_tons_of_favorite/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzou2z/anyone_else_find_themselves_with_tons_of_favorite/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 23:26:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have authors that I enjoy, but none that I would really classify as my &amp;quot;favorite.&amp;quot; I have tried reading books from the same authors of course, but either they become too formulaic over time, or they&amp;#39;re enjoyable but not what I would call a favorite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel a little self-conscious about it because reading is my main hobby, and people will sometimes ask me about my favorite authors, but I have none! Am I alone?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是布魯斯-斯特林，我是一個德克薩斯州的科幻小說作家，在歐洲呆了很長時間。我是一個賽博朋克，所以我經常搞一些奇怪的惡作劇。幾十年來一直如此，真的。AMA]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的目標是在地球上游蕩，遠離監獄和診所，並寫一些小說和非小說。
目前，我在伊比沙島。
這不是正常的伊比沙島，因爲他們被隔離了，但我不是一個正常的人，所以我不介意他們目前的狀況。
我不介意他們目前的狀況。

我有一本新書出版了，叫...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzr388/im_bruce_sterling_im_a_texan_science_fiction/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzr388/im_bruce_sterling_im_a_texan_science_fiction/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 17:12:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My goal is to wander the earth, stay out of prisons and clinics, and get some fiction and nonfiction written.Â Â 
At the moment I&amp;#39;m in Ibiza.Â  It&amp;#39;s not the normal Ibiza, because they&amp;#39;re under quarantine, but I&amp;#39;m not a normal guy, so I don&amp;#39;t mind their current situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a new book out called &amp;quot;Robot Artists and Black Swans&amp;quot; and it&amp;#39;s got seven stories in it that involve robot artists, black swans, the Shroud of Turin, and other curiosities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/9g60c1k6iqv61.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/9g60c1k6iqv61.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當你不喜歡自己並懷疑自己的所有成就時，該讀些什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[是的，這聽起來不怎麼好，但這就是我對自己最後5年生命的評價。
年的生活。

如果你處理過類似的情況，並且有幾本幫助你改變自己的好書
你改變了對自己的看法，歡迎推薦。可以是非小說類的
心理學或哲學。小說也可以...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mzn6mw/what_to_read_when_you_dont_like_yourself_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mzn6mw/what_to_read_when_you_dont_like_yourself_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 14:45:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes this does not sound nice but that’s just how I would evaluate my last 5 years of life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have dealt with similar situation and have a few good books that helped you change the outlook on yourself, feel free to suggest them. Can be nonfiction psychology or philosophy. Fiction would be fine too but I would prefer nonfiction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[改變我的想法。如果你讀得慢，不急於求成，閱讀會更愉快，更有收穫。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾經認爲，爲了 "大量閱讀"，你必須首先得到一摞書。
並把它們從頭到尾全部讀完。因此，爲了讀完這些書，我只是
所以，爲了讀完這些書，我就匆匆忙忙地讀完，結果把剛讀過的東西都忘了。
當我想告訴別人時，這一點就更加明顯了。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzc80b/change_my_mind_reading_is_much_more_enjoyable_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzc80b/change_my_mind_reading_is_much_more_enjoyable_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 09:41:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to think in order to read &amp;quot;a lot,&amp;quot; you had to first get a stack of books, and read them all cover to cover. So, in order to get through them, I would just rush through them resulting in me forgetting everything that I had just read. This was even more evident when I wanted to tell others about what I was currently reading or my thoughts on a particular book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, instead of reading 3-4 books a month, I just read one book every 2-3 weeks. I also forced myself to read slower and be more diligent about taking notes, looking things up, etc. This has made a big difference not only how much I remember, but it has basically made me fall in love with reading all over again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry if this sounded lame or whatever, but thanks for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[出版商在2020年發行的書籍中，98%的銷量低於5,000冊]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzhksv/98_percent_of_the_books_that_publishers_released/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzhksv/98_percent_of_the_books_that_publishers_released/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 07:48:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有人對小說中的人物的反應有困難，好像他們是真實的一樣？我說的是不能看大多數喜劇節目，因爲我對他們充滿了第二手的尷尬，當一個角色被虐待而得不到公正時，我很生氣，當他們遭受痛苦時，我無比悲傷等等？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我希望這是被允許的。我已經思考了很久，我真的想知道是否還有人發生這種情況？
我想知道是否有其他人發生這種情況，以及是否有人有關於如何處理的建議。
管理它。

我把這個放在書裏，因爲我反應的大部分材料都是書面的。
但它都是虛構的，有書面的，有動畫的，有真人的......。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzba2p/anyone_else_have_trouble_with_reacting_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzba2p/anyone_else_have_trouble_with_reacting_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 07:01:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hope this is allowed. I&amp;#39;ve been chewing on it for a long time and I really want to know if this happens to anyone else and if anyone has advice on how to manage it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m putting this in books because most of the material I react to is written, but its all fiction, written, animated, real person acting with characters in negative situations. I was an avid reader as a child and fictional worlds and characters of all kinds were my escape from a lot of stuff. My life is much better nowadays and I don&amp;#39;t use it to escape reality now, just for enjoyment but I feel like I was so intensely engaged with fiction when I was young that my brain just can&amp;#39;t help but react as if the people and situations are real, that I&amp;#39;ve conditioned myself to react this way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel dumb even saying this. I know they&amp;#39;re not real. I&amp;#39;m very firmly rooted in reality. But the emotional reaction can be so debilitating it makes me avoid reading/watching something that I know will throw my equilibrium off when I need to focus on studying/working/life in general. I can read something and days later be furious/desperately sad for the character that&amp;#39;s suffering. Often I can&amp;#39;t get past that part, can&amp;#39;t read it at all, end up skipping whole chapters/episodes etc. Some I can&amp;#39;t continue with at all. Just this week I&amp;#39;ve put down a book I was really enjoying because the main character had a bone broken by their boyfriend and their father joked with the guy. Horrible yes, but NOT REAL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s especially weird as I&amp;#39;m not prone to over the top displays of emotion in real life. I do have mild, well managed depression and a severe anxiety disorder, but this too is managed by medication and therapy when I need it. It&amp;#39;s probably not helping but I don&amp;#39;t think its majorly influencing my feelings. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hate this. I love fiction and I hate that this gets in the way of me enjoying it. Please tell me I&amp;#39;m not the only one and what you do to overcome it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[獻給阿爾吉農的花... 我被擊垮了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我昨天開始讀《獻給阿爾傑農的花》，到今天中午我已經讀完了。完成了
這本書，就這樣結束了。



在整個後半部分，我感覺自己在屏住呼吸，直到我最後讀到
直到我終於讀到了最後一頁上那句決定性的話（這句話將永遠銘刻在我的
記憶中）。) 一旦我讀完了這本書，我就會發現，這本書的內容很豐富。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mze3br/flowers_for_algernon_im_crushed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mze3br/flowers_for_algernon_im_crushed/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:57:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started Flowers for Algernon yesterday and by noon today I was done. Done with the book and done for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The entire second half I felt like I was holding my breath, until I finally read that last fateful line on the last page (which will remain forever etched in my memory). Once I was finished the only thing I could manage to exhale was an uncontrollable barrage of streaming tears. I even went for a walk afterwards to try to make sense of this…experience but it&amp;#39;s been no use. My mind has been numb all day. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That brings me to this post. I haven’t ever written about a book before but I feel that writing this out may help me to fully comprehend it. I&amp;#39;d also love to hear what some of you took away from this masterpiece. I know many people read this book in high school but I wasn’t as lucky. My English teacher was somewhat discouraging and pretty much killed my love for literature… so only now am I getting to read these classics, a decade later. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe the most heartbreaking part of the book to me was that throughout his life Charlie was never able to strike a balance between his intellectual and emotional self. For his entire life leading up to the operation, all he wished for was to be smart. After the operation, he acquired the intellect he’d always wanted but now he found himself emotionally challenged. This process once again reversed itself as his intellect began to deteriorate. He never was able to have both &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can remember two brief moments during which he was somewhat centered: the first during the initial weeks after the operation when he starts falling in love with Alice and still hasn&amp;#39;t come to terms with his genius but this was tainted by his unresolved family issues and confusion about his development. The second was once his intellect began to decline again, when its just him and Alice and he wants to fight to retain his genius, or whatever is left of it at that point. She even tells him, “I’ve just been waiting. You’re about at my level again”. Unfortunately, this moment too, is tarnished by his dread of what is to come. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I felt that he was never able to find true happiness. And that is what broke me the most. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometime around the latter half of the book it became obvious to me that it would not end well for Charlie. But I kept wishing. For something, even the slightest of redemption. It arrived for a moment when the bakery owner and his coworkers accepted him back into their lives but that too was short-lived. Ultimately though, I think we all know that this is how it had to end. I’m glad Keyes decided against a flowery ending - there is nothing about this book that I would change.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to end by quoting some passages I thought were particularly poignant: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he confesses his feelings to Alice after the operation but she turns him down - “How does a person go about learning how to act towards another person” This isn’t a remarkable thought on its own but taken into context I thought it was a very profound take on our social nature and the constructs we have built around that nature. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During his argument with Nemur - “Intelligence and education that hasn’t been tempered by human affection isn’t worth a damn”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His last time at the university, when talking to Burt - “I passed your floor on the way up and now I’m passing it on the way down, and I don’t think I’ll be taking this elevator again.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When he’s with Alice in the end - “And as I lay here with her I could see how important physical love was, how necessary it was for us to be in each other’s arms, giving and taking. The universe was exploding, each particle away from the next, hurtling us into dark and lonely space, eventually tearing us away from each other - child out of the womb, friend away from friend, moving from each other, each through his own pathway toward the goal-box of solitary death. But this was the counterweight, the act of binding and holding.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And last - “please… please don’t let me forget how to read and write”.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我讀了《弗蘭肯斯坦》，我驚喜地發現我對這個故事瞭解得很少。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我從電影或複述中 "知道 "的一切似乎都略有偏差或誇大。
誇大了。我覺得很滑稽的是，小說在如此奇怪的地方介紹了弗蘭肯斯坦和他的創造物，然後從那裏開始倒推。
我覺得很滑稽，小說是在這樣一個奇怪的地方介紹弗蘭肯斯坦和他的創作，然後從那裏開始倒推。我還發現
我還發現一個有趣的現象，那就是這個生物並不是一個傳統的生物。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzcnem/i_read_frankenstein_and_i_was_pleasantly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mzcnem/i_read_frankenstein_and_i_was_pleasantly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 03:35:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything I “knew” from movies or retellings seemed to be slightly off or exaggerated. 
I found it comical how the novel introduced Frankenstein and his creation in such an odd place and then worked backwards from there. I also found it interesting how the creature was much less of a traditional monster than I had expected.
I would HIGHLY recommend. 
What’re your thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[決定不玩電子遊戲，改看書了]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，最近我不玩電子遊戲了，因爲我最近嚴重地沉迷於電子遊戲。
他們最近。我想我將開始在空閒時間看書。I
我非常喜歡奇幻小說，如《繼承人的循環》和科幻小說，如《搭車指南》。
銀河系的搭便車指南》。所有建議都是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz3bro/decided_to_quit_playing_videogames_and_read_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz3bro/decided_to_quit_playing_videogames_and_read_books/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 01:17:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, recently quit playing video games cause I’ve been heavily addicted to them recently. I guess I’ll start reading books instead during my free time. I really like fantasy novels such as the inheritance cycle and sci fi novels like a hitchhikers guide to the galaxy. All suggestions are appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是布里特-班尼特，《母親》和《消失的一半》的暢銷書作者。AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個作家、讀者和故事的愛好者。以前的書包括《母親》和《消失的一半》。
和《消失的一半》。我目前正在寫我的第三本小說，它是關於
一個女孩團體。我的興趣愛好包括播客散步、按字母順序排列我的
播放列表，以及縱容我最糟糕的電視習慣。問我任何問題

證明：...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myzpbz/im_brit_bennett_bestselling_author_of_the_mothers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myzpbz/im_brit_bennett_bestselling_author_of_the_mothers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 22:55:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a writer, reader, and lover of stories. Previous books include The Mothers and The Vanishing Half. I’m currently working on my third novel, which is about a girl group. Pandemic hobbies include podcast-walks, alphabetizing my playlists, and indulging my worst TV habits. Ask me anything!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/sau6q9mv7ru61.png&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/sau6q9mv7ru61.png&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每天晚上的閱讀使我成爲一個整體上更快樂的人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道這個問題以前在本子上已經談過了（在存檔的帖子中），但我
只是想分享一下我最近的個人啓示。

我在成長過程中一直在閱讀，然後在大學期間有點停止了
和進入研究生院的幾年裏，因爲時間有限或其他原因而停止了。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mz1rd7/reading_every_night_has_made_me_an_overall/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mz1rd7/reading_every_night_has_made_me_an_overall/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:13:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know this has been talked about on this sub before (in archived posts) but I just wanted to share this personal revelation I recently had:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used to read all the time growing up and then kind of stopped during college and a few years into grad school because of limited time or other priorities. For the first half of grad school, I was really anxious and would have trouble falling and staying sleeping too. A couple of years ago (halfway into grad school), I was going on a solo trip and decided to pick a book or two to read while alone on this trip. I picked two thrillers and after this trip, I became addicted to reading more mystery/crime/thriller novels, trying to read at least a little bit each night. Not only does it help me fall asleep but every day I feel a pang of happiness about the fact that I get to return to my exciting book at night and this happiness seems to indirectly affect my general mood.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also think the Kindle (or e-reader) and the library&amp;#39;s overdrive are the greatest inventions ever because I can read about a book a week without ever having to leave my bed. I also very recently started checking out thriller audiobooks (that I read separately from but in parallel with my nighttime book) from my library to listen to at the gym and it makes my workouts so much more bearable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read for pure enjoyment and it made me realize that finding the right genre(s) for each individual person is so important. Some people may find it hard to get through a book and get turned off of reading for a while but I believe they are just reading the wrong type of book and that there is a genre out there they will get sucked into like I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(I had a brief hiatus from thrillers last year to re-read the entire Harry Potter series and that contributed the same amount of happiness and excitement.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do others have similar experiences and thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一個非基督徒對《卡拉馬佐夫兄弟》的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近讀完了費奧多爾-陀思妥耶夫斯基的《卡拉馬佐夫兄弟》。
這部小說我已經看了好一陣子了。我很害怕讀它。
部分原因是擔心作爲一個與基督教信仰相距甚遠的人
部分原因是擔心作爲一個在文化上儘可能遠離基督教信仰的人，我不會與其中的一些內容產生聯繫。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myx6sv/thoughts_of_a_nonchristian_on_the_brothers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myx6sv/thoughts_of_a_nonchristian_on_the_brothers/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 19:13:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently finished reading The Brothers Karamazov by Fyodor Dostoyevsky, a novel that I have been toting around for a while now. I dreaded reading it, partly out of fear that being someone who is as far removed from the Christian faith as is culturally possible, I wouldn&amp;#39;t connect with some of the theological discussions that I suspected would make up most of the book&amp;#39;s content. In short, I was wary of it being something that seeks to &amp;#39;convert&amp;#39; or persuade the reader towards Christianity. To be clear, I was born and raised in a Hindu community, and now consider myself an agnostic when it comes to the Divine Question.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, I was very much in the wrong about what the novel is about and what it sets out to achieve, because yes, while it is heavily steeped in Christian imagery and culture (which was inevitable given Fyodor Dostoyevsky&amp;#39;s background), the novel deals with the idea of God and faith in a much more direct, generalized manner, and instead uses the faith merely as a vehicle with which to grapple some seriously troubling existential questions. If you&amp;#39;d permit me, I&amp;#39;d like to start a discussion here about those themes. The two major ideas that the novel seemed to gravitate around were family and faith, and Dostoyevsky intertwined them with each other beautifully, so that the novel essentially asks the question: Is it possible to escape your most base, depraved urges (family), and if yes, then how (faith)? This question is explored in the form of the three titular brothers, and without beating about the bush, I&amp;#39;d like to lay out my thoughts about how the novel accomplishes that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I considered Alyosha and Smerdyakov to be essentially the antithesis of each other. Both of them had (supposedly) the same father, which meant that both of them were equally susceptible to the Karamazovian tendencies of debauchery, hedonism, and reckless self destruction.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Alyosha was a man of faith, and despite his faith being tested multiple times throughout the novel by various characters as well as circumstances, he always &lt;em&gt;chose&lt;/em&gt;, consciously, to take the nobler path and bear the suffering that comes with it. One of my favorite bits of the novel is when, after the demise of Father Zosima, his corpse begins to reek terribly, which causes a temporary crisis of faith for his followers. This was an exhilarating turn of events for me, because, as I mentioned, I expected this novel to be very preachy and stern when it came to religion and faith, but I instead found Dostoyevsky willingly putting his characters in circumstances where their belief is challenged by the universe, and the only reason to keep their faith is their choice to do so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Smerdyakov, on the other hand, was a psychopath. He subscribed to Ivan&amp;#39;s philosophy of &amp;quot;everything is permitted&amp;quot; (a philosophy that, ironically, Ivan himself did not fully believe in), and it led to him completely ruining the lives of at least two of his three half-brothers, as well as of course his father. This seemed to be Dostoyevsky straightforwardly telling us that godless/nihilist individuals can and will succumb to their worst impulses. The most interesting character, then, was someone who lay in the middle of this spectrum: Ivan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ivan was a rational, intelligent scholar who wanted to believe wholeheartedly in faith, but could not bring himself to do so because of all the logical as well as existential inconsistencies that doing so caused him to wrestle with. His qualms with faith are best represented in what are two of the novel&amp;#39;s best chapters: &lt;em&gt;The Grand Inquisitor&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;The Devil&lt;/em&gt;, in which we find the scientific, rational, stripped-down approach of nihilism attacking the more lofty ideas of the Christian faith. Ivan is, however, unable to resolve these issues, causing him to go mad and fall into illness by the end of the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To conclude, I was pleasantly surprised by how intelligent and thought-provoking the story was, and I think that Dostoyevsky wanted us to realize that reconciling faith with logic is a Herculean task that will only cause us misery, and rejecting faith is a surefire way to become selfish, egotistical and misanthropic. The only way is to willingly choose to have faith, to be compassionate and sympathetic towards your fellow human beings irrespective of what tragedy may befall you. This is a highly subjective interpretation of course, and I&amp;#39;m thrilled to find out what you took away from it. What does this novel mean to you? What are some chapters or characters or moments or lines that resonate deeply with you? I&amp;#39;d love to have a discussion!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much for reading!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在海上的暑期工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年夏天我在一艘商業漁船上找到一份工作，沒有電視，沒有手機服務。
沒有WiFi。我打算在到達那裏之前把我的kindle裝上。我正在尋找
與我的情況有關的書。到目前爲止，我的名單中最重要的是《老人與海》和《金銀島》。
和《金銀島》。

任何以公海爲背景的書，都可以。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz111m/summer_job_at_sea/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/mz111m/summer_job_at_sea/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 18:50:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve got a job on a commercial fishing boat this summer, no TV, no cell service, no WiFi. I’m going to load up my kindle before I get there. I’m looking for books that relate to my situation. Top of my list so far are Old Man and the Sea and Treasure Island.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anything set on the open ocean, hopefully not centered around a struggle for my life (ie Life of Pi or Adrift), will make the list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[reddit的書蟲/快速閱讀者，關於非虛構/教育/教科書的閱讀理解/速度的問題]]></title><description><![CDATA[在閱讀非虛構類書籍或教科書時，你是否會用細牙梳梳理每一句話？
你是用細牙梳子讀完每一句話（你還是會很快讀完，因爲你的閱讀理解能力很高/很好），還是理解我的意思？
因爲你的閱讀理解能力很高/很好），還是說你對它的理解是60-90%都不知道？
還是說你能理解它的60-90%（比大意多得多......）？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mynjqz/bookwormsfast_readers_of_reddit_question_about/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mynjqz/bookwormsfast_readers_of_reddit_question_about/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:56:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When reading nonfictional books or textbooks, do you read through each sentence with a fine-tooth comb (and you still go through it pretty fast because you have a high?/good? reading comprehension) or do you understand it like idk 60-90% of what it&amp;#39;s saying (a good amount more than just the gist of it) and move on?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that I pick apart almost every word of the sentence. And I think it&amp;#39;s because I&amp;#39;m mostly detailed oriented and meticulous.  Also, while sometimes getting distracted in the process. Like I&amp;#39;ll be like okay this refers to this thing in this example, this means this, that means that, reread, and oh what&amp;#39;s this thing on my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[對於那些在Goodreads評論中包含破壞者和沒有破壞者警告的人，地獄裏有一個特殊的地方。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這篇文章的標題說明了它需要表達的內容，但是，爲了遵守規則，我將告訴你我爲什麼要發這個帖子。
我將確切地告訴你我爲什麼要發這個帖子。請注意，這篇文章中只有49%的內容是諷刺。
諷刺，雖然我無意冒犯，但我也無意
我無意冒犯，但也無意不冒犯。

事情是這樣的。

我打開了Goodreads的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mywhvu/there_is_a_special_place_in_hell_for_people_whose/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/mywhvu/there_is_a_special_place_in_hell_for_people_whose/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 13:17:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The title of this post says what it needs to say but, in honour of the rules, I will tell you exactly why I came to post this. Be forewarned, only 49% of this post is sarcasm and, while I have no intention to offend, I also have no intention not to offend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it goes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I opened up Goodreads for no particular reason. Just quietly scrolling and harming no one. I am on leave today and I can do whatever I like, and all I want to do is a little nothing. Tomorrow is public holiday here, so I’ve given myself a really long weekend. I figured I’d keep things peaceful. I expect that was too much to ask. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I came across a book trending in the Thriller section - &lt;em&gt;The Moonlight Child&lt;/em&gt; by Karen McQuestion. It’s got a 4.22 rating and that’s quite high, in my estimation, especially for something that probably isn’t literary fiction or destined to be a classic. (But who knows? I haven’t read it, and I could be wildly mistaken.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Rating aside, I was intrigued by the synopsis, so I read the reviews. Well. Of course I read the reviews. Reviews are vital. A public good, written (usually) by the best among us. A well-written review is invaluable, but reading through them is a dangerous business. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See, sometimes reviewers are just parading around as Samaritans when they are much more akin to Satan. They remind us how easy it is for vicious psychopaths to review books on Goodreads. These people are the ones that publish reviews that contain spoilers without including spoiler warnings. There is a special place in hell for them. I truly worry for their friends and family. Villains. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I will now never read &lt;em&gt;The Moonlight Child&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有沒有人有閱讀速度過快的問題？]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我讀我喜歡的書時，我想知道更多故事的熱情迫使我
匆匆忙忙。我有時會自動跳過一些句子，試圖進入故事的下一部分。
下一部分的故事。這裏有沒有人發生這種情況，如果有，你們是如何
阻止它？我覺得我沒有享受到書的樂趣，因爲我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my5cwa/anyone_have_a_problem_with_reading_too_fast/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my5cwa/anyone_have_a_problem_with_reading_too_fast/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 05:13:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I read books I enjoy, my enthusiasm for knowing more of the story forces me to rush. I would sometimes automatically skip sentences and try to get to the next part of the story. Does that happen to anyone here and if so, how do you guys stop it? I feel like I don&amp;#39;t get to enjoy the book as I miss some details by rushing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[請向我推薦你們最溫和的書籍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在默默地閱讀這個分論壇，並經常被你們感動。
富有同情心、聰明的陌生人。因此，儘管我很害羞，我還是想
請大家提供溫和、安慰的書籍，不管是哪種類型的，小說還是非小說。我的
我最喜歡的書是，當我感到生硬和脆弱時，我最喜歡的書是。我最喜歡的書是：《我的世界》（The... The...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myj4id/please_recommend_me_your_gentlest_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myj4id/please_recommend_me_your_gentlest_books/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been silently reading this subreddit and am often moved by you compassionate, intelligent strangers. So I&amp;#39;d thought despite terrible shyness to ask you  all for gentle, comforting books of any genre, fiction or nonfiction. My favorite go to books for when I&amp;#39;m feeling raw and vulnerable are:  The History of Love by Nicole Krauss , The Vulnerable Observer by Ruth Behar, and Salt by Nayyirah Waheed. I know this is a pretty vague request, so I hope my go-tos provide some guidance to what I&amp;#39;m looking for. I am open to anything. Apologies and Thanks in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你對兩本書或對某本書最有爭議的意見是什麼？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在與一個朋友的談話中，這個話題出現了，所以它讓我想到了
思考，現在我很好奇其他人有什麼要說的。我自己的
我個人的觀點是，《安娜-卡列尼娜》是一部糟糕的小說，她應該被火車撞死。
她應該早點被火車撞死，以避免我們所有的謊言。這或者是每一個...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myjw4t/whats_your_most_controversial_opinion_on_either/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/myjw4t/whats_your_most_controversial_opinion_on_either/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Apr 2021 02:50:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Was having a conversation with a friend and this topic came up so it got me thinking, and now I&amp;#39;m curious as to what other people have to say. My own personal hot take is that Anna Karenina is a terrible novel &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;and that she should have been hit by a train earlier to spare us all the BS.  &lt;/span&gt;That or every Dan Brown book is greatly overrated.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[心理恐怖類書籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的很喜歡恐怖的東西，我期待着閱讀有懸念的書籍
和心理學。我還想讀斯蒂芬-金的《嘉莉》等書。
我很喜歡 :)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myg4yv/psychological_horror_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/myg4yv/psychological_horror_books/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 23:30:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really like horror stuff and I’m looking forward to read books with suspense and psychological. I would also like to read books like Carrie by Stephen King, I loved it :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[感謝上帝賜予圖書館]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我是一個狂熱的讀者。小時候，我把書喫得比我父母提供的還快。
提供它們。十幾歲的時候，我慢慢地從閱讀中滑落，到了十幾歲的時候
我沒有拿起過一本書，除非是學校的必修課。現在我已經20歲出頭了
現在我已經20多歲了，重新發現了閱讀，沒有什麼比這更能幫助我了......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4mfa/thank_god_for_libraries/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4mfa/thank_god_for_libraries/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 19:38:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;m an avid reader. As a kid I&amp;#39;d eat up books faster than my parents could supply them. As a teenager I slowly slipped out of my reading and by late teens I hadn&amp;#39;t picked up a book unless it was mandatory for school. I&amp;#39;m in my early 20s now and rediscovering reading and nothing has helped me more than my library&amp;#39;s ebook app. With most libraries being shut or too far away to get to, ebooks have been such a delight. Especially because I&amp;#39;ve realised I read way quicker if it&amp;#39;s an ebook rather than a physical copy (something about not knowing how many pages I have left makes me more likely to not put it down).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve recently read Deeplight by Francis Hardinge, The Authenticity Project by Clare Pooley, Wink by Rob Harrell, Lie With Me by Phillipe Besson, A Bear Called Paddington by Michael Bond and The House With Chicken Legs by Sophie Anderson, all within the past 3 months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s amazing how libraries give us so much for free.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於平行宇宙、時間旅行等的書籍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已經讀過暗物質😅]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my3mfr/books_about_parallel_universes_time_travelling_etc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my3mfr/books_about_parallel_universes_time_travelling_etc/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 18:17:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I already read dark matter 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有人剛剛告訴我，花時間看書 "沒有實際價值"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾回覆過某人的評論，他們說他們對在過去兩天內完成一整本書感到有點內疚。
在過去的兩天裏完成了一整本書，而他們本可以把時間用於
做更多實際的事情。我說閱讀是一件可以投資時間的大事
的事情。有人回覆了我的評論，批評說因爲...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4z95/someone_just_told_me_that_theres_no_real_value_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/my4z95/someone_just_told_me_that_theres_no_real_value_in/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:53:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had replied to someone&amp;#39;s comment where they said they felt a little guilty for finishing a whole book in the last 2 days, when they could have spent their time doing more practical things. I said reading is a great thing to invest your time in. Someone replied to my comment criticizing it because there&amp;#39;s no &amp;quot;investment value in reading fiction novels besides the pure enjoyment factor&amp;quot; and that spending time doing something that has no real value can be detrimental.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t even understand that point of view. Books are incredibly valuable beyond just enjoyment. Most importantly they have helped my mental health in very meaningful, personal ways during times where I was depressed, anxious or heartbroken. They have made me feel less alone, given me empathy for all types of different people, affected me in a genuine emotional way, given me a new perspective, etc. If people don&amp;#39;t think fiction books have value they have been seriously missing out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, what&amp;#39;s with people knocking things for being fun instead of practical. If someone wants to spend their time reading a book &lt;em&gt;just because&lt;/em&gt; it&amp;#39;s enjoyable, that&amp;#39;s still not a waste of time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想了解愛情。]]></title><description><![CDATA[談到愛情，我一直不知道自己在做什麼。我被一個前任（我的初戀）糾纏了4年。
前任（我的初戀）糾纏了4年，而我正試圖駕馭我與現任女友的新關係
和我現在的女朋友。我的父母從未教過我關於愛情的知識，我也從未
我沒有任何愛情故事可以用來理解我自己或我的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my2dj9/i_want_to_understand_love/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/my2dj9/i_want_to_understand_love/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 25 Apr 2021 13:43:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to love I’ve never known what I’m doing. I’ve been haunted by an ex (my first love) for 4 years, and I’m trying to navigate my new relationship with my current girlfriend. My parents never taught me about love and I never had any love stories I could use to understand myself or my relationships growing up. Science and research are helpful (I’m a nerd), but what I really need is a good story that can really touch me and give me ways to think about love. I don’t want any unrealistic, princess in the tower stuff, but something real I can take-in and learn from. I’m a guy, but I’m open to all suggestions. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I appreciate everything anyone has to say.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>