<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 19:26:29 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Jacques Pépin的《學徒》。我在廚房的生活》（2003年）令人驚歎]]></title><description><![CDATA[我非常喜歡讀自傳，這是我讀過的最好的自傳之一。
讀過的最好的作品之一。如果你曾經在電視或YouTube上看過他，哪怕只有幾分鐘，你就會知道他是一個熱情、悠閒、可愛的人。
你就會知道他是一個多麼熱情、悠閒、可愛的人--而這一點在這本書中得到了充分體現。
這一點在本書中體現得淋漓盡致。

本書的很多重點都是關於食物的。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/npbfva/jacques_pépins_the_apprentice_my_life_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/npbfva/jacques_pépins_the_apprentice_my_life_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 22:19:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really enjoy reading autobiographies, and this is one of the best I&amp;#39;ve ever read. If you&amp;#39;ve ever watched him on TV or YouTube even for a few minutes, you know what a warm, laidback, sweetheart of a man he seems to be—and that comes through in spades in this book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of the focus is on food, of course, so if you&amp;#39;re interested in changes in American cuisine in the 20th century, there&amp;#39;s plenty here to whet your appetite. Pépin has been right in the middle of many of the major culinary developments of the last 75 years or so, from cookbook writing, to nouvelle cuisine, to celebrity chefs, and food on TV. Fascinating stuff all around.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the guy has also led a fascinating life, and he&amp;#39;s bright and charming. Definitely one of the best autobiographies I&amp;#39;ve ever read, and I can&amp;#39;t recommend it enough!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲一個14歲的男孩寫的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的想給我的表弟送一本堅振書，但不知道該選哪一本。
不知道該選哪一本。他是一個狂熱的電子遊戲玩家（我不知道他玩什麼遊戲
我不知道他玩什麼遊戲），喜歡幻想類書籍。他更喜歡閱讀英語，儘管這不是他的母語（他的水平很高）。
他喜歡讀英語，雖然這不是他的第一語言（他的英語水平已經很高了）。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/noyq9z/book_for_a_14_year_old_boy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/noyq9z/book_for_a_14_year_old_boy/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really want to give my cousin a book for his Confirmation but don&amp;#39;t really know which one to choose. He is an avid video gamer (I don&amp;#39;t know what games he plays) and likes fantasy books. He prefers reading in English although it is not his first language (he is very advanced in English for his age) but I don&amp;#39;t know if he&amp;#39;s advanced enough to read high fantasy for adults. So my question is: do you know of any fantasy books that could be appropriate for a 14 year old boy that isn&amp;#39;t written in a too complex English?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[根據你的心情尋找書籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

幾個月前，我們發佈了關於我和一個朋友正在從事的一個項目
的項目，叫做librimood（librimood.com）。它是一個由人工智能驅動的搜索引擎，用於
根據你的心情來找書。例如，你可以搜索抽象的查詢
如 "一本會讓我哭的書 "或 "一本有故事的書"。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/np59km/find_books_based_on_your_mood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/np59km/find_books_based_on_your_mood/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi guys,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of months ago we posted about a project me and a friend were working on, called librimood (librimood.com). It is an AI powered search engine for finding books based on your mood. For example you can search abstract queries like “a book that will make me cry” or “a book with a strong female lead” and get relative results! We got a very positive feedback from the community and we decided to keep working on it and improving it. Since then we have added the following features:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;More books&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Improved search results&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fiction / Non-fiction filtering&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;New mode: &lt;strong&gt;Contextual Recommendations&lt;/strong&gt;. Get similar themed books for your favorite book. (click on the icon on the left of the search bar. It will switch recommendation mode, indicated by the blue color. You can then search your favorite title and get some recommendations back!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Feedback mechanism . Help us improve the results by scrolling to the bottom of the results page and suggesting books that you would expect to see based on the query that you typed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would love for you to try it out and tell us what you think, and where we should focus on next!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不認爲我喜歡有聲讀物。我並不專注於]]></title><description><![CDATA[有很多次，我聽了一本書的音頻，然後我覺得我不喜歡它，然後我讀了它，實際上我喜歡它。
不喜歡它，然後我讀了它，其實我喜歡它？我想我是對音頻書籍感到厭煩了
我猜我對音頻書籍感到厭煩，我的思緒開始飄忽不定，所以我認爲這是書籍的錯，而不是音頻的事實。
書的錯，而不是因爲它是有聲書，我有點高興......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/np2zpe/i_dont_think_i_like_audiobooks_i_dont_focus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/np2zpe/i_dont_think_i_like_audiobooks_i_dont_focus/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There&amp;#39;s been so many times I&amp;#39;ve listened to a book on audio and then I think I disliked it and then I read it physically and I actually love it? I guess i got bored of the books on audio and my mind starts to wander so I assumed it was the books fault not the fact its an audiobook, I am kinda glad now that I&amp;#39;ve figured it out. I have Reread the books and I now love them, that&amp;#39;s the thing while I was listening to the audiobook it&amp;#39;s normally something I would love to read but I was getting bored? It&amp;#39;s weird but it makes sense now that it&amp;#39;s the audiobooks fault&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[肉體是溫柔的。誇大其詞，不求甚解]]></title><description><![CDATA[(No spoilers)

我在收到一個非常強烈的推薦後，剛剛讀完這本書。
對這本書的評論是壓倒性的積極，但我真的不知道爲什麼。

如果你不熟悉，《肉體的溫柔》是一部虛構的小說，講述了一個
在那裏，（幾乎）所有的動物都有了。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/np63hm/tender_is_the_flesh_overhyped_and_undercooked/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/np63hm/tender_is_the_flesh_overhyped_and_undercooked/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 20:10:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(No spoilers)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading this book after receiving a very strong recommendation. Reviews for this book are overwhelmingly positive but I really don’t know why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re not familiar, Tender is the Flesh is a fictitious novel about a dystopian future where (almost) all animals have been killed, due to a deadly virus they pass to humans, so the government’s solution is to now breed humans for human consumption. This also has the added benefits of solving homelessness and overpopulation since we now just kill and eat all the “undesirables”. Talk about a diplomatic solution!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now you may be asking yourself, without the necessary animals to support our ecosystems, how will anything grow or survive? If humans are eating humans, what are we feeding the humans that are meant to be eaten? If we’re not feeding them human meat, then why can’t we all just eat the same non-human based diets? Why do we even have to eat meat at all? These questions, and more, will not be answered.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It becomes aggravatingly clear in the first few chapters that the author gave little to no thought about the actual biological or ecological impacts this fantasy future would have on the world. Instead the book sweeps the necessary details under the rug and instead chooses to indulge itself in the treatment (i.e. mistreatment) of these humans who only exist to be eaten, purely for shock value. Even this it does not do well. In the moments where the book attempts to shock and disgust its audience, it merely falls flat and flounders under its ridiculous and unbelievable premise. Like a magician with no sleight-of-hand, there’s no mystery here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story at times teases that it might address broader topics like factory farming, animal abuse, human trafficking, misogyny, drug abuse, addiction, homelessness, overpopulation, or any number of other social issues. Instead we get meaningless characters that show up then are never mentioned again followed by atrocious acts with no redeeming value other than to make you feel sick.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The real shock of this book is how transparent and unlikeable the characters are. I’m not going to spoil anything, despite my recommendation that no one wastes their time reading this book. I will however say that the ending is a real Game of Thrones season 8 slap in the face. If the author thought they were being clever, they weren’t.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only good thing about this book is that is wasn’t longer. I was glad to find this book at my local library. I would have been mad had I paid for this book. I was curious to find my library only had one copy, but now I’m thinking one was too many.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there anyone else who read this book and felt the same way?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: in the spirit of fairness, I’d like to add that I do believe the author has obvious story telling talent. It’s evident in the writing. I don’t however feel like this was a worthwhile story.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿爾伯特-加繆的《鼠疫》是大流行時期的必讀之作]]></title><description><![CDATA[直到現在還沒有讀過阿爾伯特-加繆的任何作品，並決定從《瘟疫》開始。
瘟疫》。這是一部多麼精彩的小說啊！我知道這本書不會有同樣的效果。我知道，如果不是因爲Covid-19大流行病，它不會對我產生同樣的影響。
如果不是因爲Covid-19大流行病，它對我的影響不會太大。強烈推薦。

對於那些讀過它的人，你們覺得怎麼樣？如果你讀過...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/np0edm/albert_camuss_the_plague_is_a_mustread_in_times/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/np0edm/albert_camuss_the_plague_is_a_mustread_in_times/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 15:10:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Haven&amp;#39;t read anything by Albert Camus until now, and decided to start with The Plague. What a wonderful novel it is! I know it wouldn&amp;#39;t have had quite the same effect on me if it weren&amp;#39;t for the Covid-19 pandemic. Highly recommend.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who read it, what did you guys think? If you&amp;#39;d read it before the pandemic started, do you think it influenced how you approached everything that happened in the world?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完泰瑞-普拉切特（Terry Pratchett）的《守衛！守衛！》（Guards! 特里-普拉切特的《守衛！》，我愛上了它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是我讀的第二本普拉切特的書（第一本是《魔法的顏色》）。
而且我完全愛上了它。幽默感很強，但又不至於太過粗俗或過度還原。
過分還原，而且人物形象令人震驚。整隻手錶是這樣一個
可愛的一羣不合羣的人，其中胡蘿蔔（很容易就成爲我的最愛）...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nos4oh/i_just_finished_reading_guards_guards_by_terry/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nos4oh/i_just_finished_reading_guards_guards_by_terry/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 07:05:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second Pratchett book I&amp;#39;ve read (the first being The Color of Magic) and I am absolutely in love. The humor is playful without being really crude or overly reductive and the characters are astounding. The entire watch is such a lovable gaggle of misfits with Carrot (easily my favorite) to add a wonderful contrary flavor. I&amp;#39;m going to be reading more of Pratchett, but if anyone like me held off reading his works for whatever reason I implore you to get started reading immediately!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[人們喜歡聲稱自己讀過的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在尋找那些人們喜歡說他們讀過但大多數人沒有讀過的長篇/難懂的書。
到目前爲止，我的閱讀清單上有《無限的玩笑》、《伊甸園之東》、《罪與罰》和《萬有引力之虹》。
懲罰》和《萬有引力的彩虹》在我的閱讀清單上。

我真的想挑戰自己，並在結束時能夠說 "是的......我
我真的讀了......"。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nojquz/books_that_people_love_to_claim_theyve_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nojquz/books_that_people_love_to_claim_theyve_read/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 31 May 2021 00:07:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m looking for long/difficult books that people love to say they’ve read but most haven’t... so far I’ve got Infinite Jest, East of Eden, Crime and Punishment, and Gravity’s Rainbow on my to read list.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Really wanted to challenge myself and be able to say at the end of it “yeah... I actually read those!” To myself :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你喜歡瀏覽自己的書架嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我看來，擁有一個家庭圖書館的小樂趣之一是，當我無事可做，只想瀏覽我的書架時，那一刻
我無事可做，只想瀏覽我的書架。有時我在
有時我在尋找要讀的東西，但有時我是爲了瀏覽而瀏覽。
這種感覺很奇怪，很滿足。從書架上抽出書來...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/noiwur/do_you_like_browsing_your_own_bookshelves/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/noiwur/do_you_like_browsing_your_own_bookshelves/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:58:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the small joys of having a home library, in my view, is that moment when I have nothing to do and I just want to browse my bookshelves. Sometimes I&amp;#39;m looking for something to read, but sometimes I browse for the sake of browsing. It feels strangely good and satisfying. Pulling out books from the shelves, flicking through it, maybe read extracts for a few minutes, especially if I&amp;#39;ve read it before. Touch it, feel it, admire its cover and design if it looks good. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I browse a library, a bookstore or a bookcase in someone else house, I do feel like I am intruding upon someone else&amp;#39;s shelves. But the difference is at home, the shelves and the books are mine, built and cultivated by me, composed for my eyes to gaze upon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I gain some pleasure in doing this whether or not it leads me to picking off a book to read for that day. The search can be as enjoyable as the discovery.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[恐怖故事]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天我和我的岳父岳母聊天，我的父親告訴我關於他的
的母親。她是一個狂熱的讀者，會不斷地買書，大多是打折或在舊貨市場買的。
因爲她很節儉。然後他告訴我一件事
我還沒有回過神來；她不使用書籤，而是......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/noagew/horror_story/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/noagew/horror_story/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 15:03:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was talking with my in laws yesterday and my fil was telling me about his mother. She was an avid reader, and would buy books constantly, mostly on discount or at yard sales because she was frugal. And then he told me something so shocking I still haven’t recovered; instead of using bookmarks, she would rip out the page she was on. I’ve never heard of anybody doing something so crazy like that! I had to share because I can’t stop thinking about it 🥲&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼圍繞薩利-魯尼的《正常人》一書有這麼多的噪音？]]></title><description><![CDATA[泰晤士報》說--"我讀完這本書，決心以不同的方式看待這個世界。
不同的方式。我不知道你能給一部小說什麼更高的讚譽。" 所以
自然，我有難以置信的高期望。它還入圍了
曼布克獎？我是不是錯過了什麼？

我翻了一頁又一頁，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/no5bkr/why_is_there_so_much_noise_around_the_book_normal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/no5bkr/why_is_there_so_much_noise_around_the_book_normal/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 11:26:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;strong&gt;Times&lt;/strong&gt; said - &amp;quot;I finished the book determined to look at the world differently. I am not sure what higher compliment you can pay a novel.&amp;quot; So naturally, I have unbelievably high expectations. And it was longlisted for the Man Booker Prize? Am I missing something?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I flipped page after page, cursing, and grumbling, hoping to feel it. Feel what the rest of the world is feeling about this book. I was hoping that this book was going to be a new age The Catcher in the Rye or The Perks of Being a Wallflower. I had no idea how wrong I was going to be proven.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What struck me as I read the first few chapters was how this book was a culmination of age-old cliches stacked on top of each other so meticulously. The girl is rich. The boy is poor. The girl has issues with her father. The boy plays football and also likes reading books. The girl does not wear make-up or care about what anyone thinks. The boy wants to be a writer. It was so uncomfortable to read. Also, the writing style was difficult to get through but that is a personal preference and not a criticism of the book itself.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Every chapter was a mini-story with the same plot with different characters. Marianne and Connell start talking, fight because of reasons that I honestly do not understand, get involved with other people, and part ways. The next chapter brings them together in a different setting with different people. It was so difficult to care for these characters.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It seemed like the author googled a bunch of topics on world&amp;#39;s issues and sprinkled them throughout, forced social issues such as depression, suicide, and mental health into the mix almost like a second thought, and tried really hard to push the readers into believing that these characters are intellectuals with important world views. It was all too convenient to be true. And it did not seem like the story went anywhere.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am picking my brain to come up with one great thing about this book but I am at a loss. Oh wait, the cover design is beautiful. The fact that the only good thing about this book is a judgment on its cover says a lot in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我剛剛開始讀《黑暗塔》系列]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在用有聲讀物夾，我丈夫一直催促我讀這個系列。
這個系列。我已經讀了《神槍手》（第一本）的一半，它是如此的
到目前爲止很奇怪。這裏有誰讀過它，你覺得怎麼樣？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nnn3iy/i_just_started_the_dark_tower_series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nnn3iy/i_just_started_the_dark_tower_series/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 22:41:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been on an audiobook binder and My husband has been bugging me to read this series. I’m about half way through The Gunslinger (1st book) and it’s so strange so far. Who here has read it and what did you think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛剛完成我的第一本科幻小說]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道爲什麼我等了這麼久。也許我認爲它在某種程度上是低劣的。
儘管我無法追溯這種想法的起源。或者也許它太小衆了
只適合於 "太空書呆子"。我想我太固執了，對我自己有利。
簡直是無知。

在我生活的大部分時間裏，我一直在閱讀經典...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nnr7gx/just_finished_my_first_scifi_novel/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nnr7gx/just_finished_my_first_scifi_novel/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 21:56:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know why I waited so long. Perhaps I thought it&amp;#39;s somehow inferior, though I can&amp;#39;t trace the origin of that thought. Or maybe it&amp;#39;s too niche - suitable only for &amp;quot;space nerds&amp;quot;. I guess I&amp;#39;ve been too stubborn for my own good. Simply ignorant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For most of my life I&amp;#39;d been reading classic literature (plus non-fiction), and you rarely can find sci-fi books on those type of lists. Thought classic novels are safe, proven, significant. You can&amp;#39;t go wrong with &amp;#39;em.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then I had a revelation. I&amp;#39;d never say reading is worthless, but my enthusiasm for books was built on crooked foundations. My reasons for reading were juvenile, harmful even. I realized it way too late. I developed aversion for literature which lasted 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I came back. I&amp;#39;m hoping I&amp;#39;ve grown a bit - and I can enjoy literature with a new set of eyes. I&amp;#39;ve never been a fan of &amp;quot;page-turners&amp;quot;. All I want is to feel, to think, and to enjoy the language. And it looks like sci-fi can provide all of that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My first novel was Do Androids Dream of Electric Sheep? I liked it a lot. It gave me a glimpse of what sci-fi genre can be: well-written, thought-provoking and wildly imaginative. In fact, I ordered over a dozen sci-fi books from different authors. I&amp;#39;m gonna read Childhood&amp;#39;s End by Clarke next.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feels like a beginning of a new chapter. It&amp;#39;s not a new job, new country or new relationship. It&amp;#39;s just books. But it matters to me, so I felt the need to share. Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼書籍不像電影那樣被宣傳或炒作？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果一部電影的預告片被刪除了，它將在Twitter和YouTube上到處流行。
然而，我沒有看到這種情況發生在書籍上。
事實上，我唯一能想到的是，一本書被當作電影對待的情況是《哈利-波特》。
在《死亡之丘》中。我還記得在新聞中看到它。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nnq8rt/why_arent_books_advertised_or_hyped_like_movies/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nnq8rt/why_arent_books_advertised_or_hyped_like_movies/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 20:52:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If a movie trailer is dropping off it will trend everywhere from Twitter to YouTube yet  I don&amp;#39;t see this happening for books ever in fact the only time I can think of where a book was being treated like a movie was with Harry Potter in the deathly hollows.  I still remember seeing it on the news a week before the book came out of fans anticipating the release, it was super hyped but I can&amp;#39;t save say I&amp;#39;ve seen  that happen again for any type of book. Why is that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[年輕的約翰-斯坦貝克未發表的狼人小說不打算印刷了]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nn6fen/a_young_john_steinbecks_unpublished_werewolf/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nn6fen/a_young_john_steinbecks_unpublished_werewolf/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 22:55:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[說實話，我對閱讀《霍比特人》如此簡單和容易感到驚訝]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，我多年來一直是一個狂熱的讀者，我知道閱讀《魔戒》是必須的。I
我甚至向自己保證，在讀完書之前不看任何電影。
不幸的是，生活阻礙了我的閱讀習慣，所以這套書就在我的書架上放了好幾年。
我的書架上好幾年了。

直到這次大流行開始，我纔開始閱讀。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmxlc1/im_honestly_surprised_at_how_simple_and_easy_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmxlc1/im_honestly_surprised_at_how_simple_and_easy_it/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:50:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;ve been an avid reader for years and I knew that reading LoTR was a &lt;em&gt;must.&lt;/em&gt; I even promised myself not to watch any of the movies until I read the books. Unfortunately, life got in the way of my reading habit so the series just sat in my shelf for years. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Until this pandemic thing started and I finally got to pick up The Hobbit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I really thought I knew what to expect: intense world building here, long-a** history there. But nope. There were sentences that really said &amp;quot;now&amp;#39;s not the time to talk about this&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no one knows what Gollum is&amp;quot; or stuff like that. And the plot was really just a bunch of dwarves, a hobbit, and a wizard going from place to place like Dora (I don&amp;#39;t mean this in an insulting way haha just stating the immediate comparison that came to mind!). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still, I enjoyed it a lot and can&amp;#39;t wait to get into the rest of the series!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你們有人在想象人物的臉時有困難嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直都有這個問題。但我在想象其他東西，如房屋、風景等方面從來沒有遇到過任何問題。
其他東西，比如房子、風景，任何東西。

大多數時候，我把我認識的人或著名的演員/女演員想象成
根據他們的性格，然後我就沒有任何問題了。
但我不能只...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmtqeq/do_any_of_you_guys_have_trouble_imagining/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmtqeq/do_any_of_you_guys_have_trouble_imagining/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:11:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always had this problem. But I&amp;#39;ve never had any problem with visualising anything else like houses, the landscape, anything. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most of the time I imagine people I know or famous actors/actresses as characters depending on their personalities and then I have no problem at all. But I can&amp;#39;t just make up faces. These faces that I conjure up just keep changing constantly or just generally look like a blurry picture. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is there a name for this condition? I&amp;#39;d really like to know.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我向一個遊戲同伴/朋友解釋了我的在線角色的名字，他繼續解釋作者是厭惡女性和同性戀者，這讓我很受打擊。唉。當你聽說你最喜歡的藝術家/作家是個壞人時，你是怎麼處理的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的角色叫埃德爾，來自奧森-斯科特-卡德的《埃德爾的遊戲》。

我很喜歡這個系列的前兩本書（實際上我更喜歡《安德的陰影》）。
我有這些書的音頻書，並經常回去聽，不時地聽。
時間。我也聽過這個系列的其他幾本書，但沒有一本是我的。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmuxv4/i_explained_my_online_characters_name_to_a_fellow/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmuxv4/i_explained_my_online_characters_name_to_a_fellow/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:11:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My character&amp;#39;s name is Ender, from Ender&amp;#39;s Game, by Orson Scott Card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve loved the first two books in the series (I actually prefer Ender&amp;#39;s Shadow). I have them on audio book and often go back and listen to them from time to time. I&amp;#39;ve listened to a few of the other books in the series, but none really stood out like those first two. Oh, and I watch the movie sometimes, too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So like I said, I was telling my friend (who I haven&amp;#39;t found to be a liar) about my character&amp;#39;s name&amp;#39;s origin and he dropped the aforementioned bomb and ugh. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know if it&amp;#39;s true. A part of me doesn&amp;#39;t want to look it up. I want to keep a pure image of the books...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So now I&amp;#39;m worried if go back and listen to them again, it&amp;#39;ll skew the experience. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Does anyone have any similar experiences? How have you dealt with them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[唐娜-塔特的《祕史》--可能是我今年讀過的最好的書。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜歡這本書的三件事。

 1. 謀殺案發生前逐漸形成的緊張氣氛。我可以感覺到他們中的一些人（尤其是亨利）是如何達到他們的崩潰點的。
    他們中的一些人（尤其是亨利）達到了他們的崩潰點。

 2. 2. 人物的發展。這本書讓我覺得我認識這些
    人物。這些人物是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmvy8n/the_secret_history_by_donna_tarttprobably_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmvy8n/the_secret_history_by_donna_tarttprobably_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 14:11:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three things I love about the book:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gradual tension created leading up to the murder. I could feel how some of them (especially Henry) reached their breaking point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The character development. The book made me feel like I knew these characters personally. The characters were so incredibly complex people (especially Bunny and Henry) who have their own principles and stick to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obsession with beauty and aesthetics in the book. The book is filled with lovely quotes and made me fall in love with Ancient Greece.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another great thing about this book is its straightforward writing style. It makes it easier to follow the complicated ideologies and rituals mentioned. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would 100% recommend it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[能讓我意識到99%的生活是多麼無意義的書，以一種好的方式]]></title><description><![CDATA[基本上只是想要一些能喚醒我的書，讓我意識到絕大多數人的無意義。
喚醒絕大部分的生活和世界。我花了很多時間來擔心
荒謬的、細微的、良性的事情，這些事情顯然不值得花任何時間
擔心的時間。想克服這個問題，希望有...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nmu6ka/books_that_will_make_me_realize_how_meaningless/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nmu6ka/books_that_will_make_me_realize_how_meaningless/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 13:09:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Basically just want some books that will awaken me the the pointlessness of the vast majority of life and the world. I spend a lot of my time worrying about ridiculous, minute and benign things that are clearly not worth spending any time stressing over. Would like to get over this and hope there’s a book that can help. Not really looking for self help books but I’m open to it if it’s &lt;em&gt;exceptionally&lt;/em&gt; good, philosophy is fine but more so looking for something fictional that really brings the meaninglessness of life to the forefront of your mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[老人與海》--賞析線]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是我讀的第一本海明威的書，我很後悔我把它推遲了這麼久。
這麼久。

我知道可能還有很多意義更深一點，我需要重讀。
但這不是一個完美的寓言嗎？我們必須忍受的不斷的代價，對我們和
爲他人付出的代價？

如果你還沒有讀過這本書，請...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmpsvk/the_old_man_and_the_sea_appreciation_thread/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmpsvk/the_old_man_and_the_sea_appreciation_thread/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 13:09:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the first book of Hemingway I&amp;#39;ve read and I regret I&amp;#39;ve put it off for so long. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know there might be a lot more meaning a bit deeper, I will need to reread it, but isn&amp;#39;t this a perfect parable? The constant toll we must endure, for us and for others? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you haven&amp;#39;t read this book, please do. And I hope it gives you strength to fight anything you need to face:  &amp;quot;But man is not made for defeat. A man can be destroyed but not defeated&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是大衛-艾本巴赫，《如何到火星》一書的作者，這是一部全新的小說，講述了火星上的真人秀節目，報道了有史以來第一次離地懷孕的情況，令人相當興奮。AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，大家好！我的名字是大衛-艾本巴赫，我的特點是
全神貫注於人類的狀況。這就是說，我是八本小說、詩歌和非小說的作者。
八本小說、詩歌和非小說。這包括我的新小說《如何
到火星[https://tachyonpublications.com/product/how-to...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nm9fyz/im_david_ebenbach_the_prettydamnexcited_author_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nm9fyz/im_david_ebenbach_the_prettydamnexcited_author_of/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 23:11:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey, everybody! My name is David Ebenbach and the deal with me is that I&amp;#39;m preoccupied with the human condition. Which is to say that I&amp;#39;m the author of eight books of fiction, poetry, and non-fiction. That includes my new novel &lt;a href=&quot;https://tachyonpublications.com/product/how-to-mars/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;How to Mars&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (Tachyon Publications)*—*my debut in the world of science-fiction. So, as far as writing goes, I&amp;#39;ve been at it for a little while, and, as far as sci-fi goes, I&amp;#39;m new around here. Either way, I&amp;#39;m looking forward to talking! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started writing &lt;em&gt;How to Mars&lt;/em&gt; in 2015, inspired by news stories about the kind of bonkers &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mars-one.com/&quot;&gt;Mars One Project&lt;/a&gt; (like the fictional organization in my novel, their plan was to send a bunch of folks on a one-way mission to the red planet and fund the whole thing via a reality TV show—but my (fake) organization actually did it!), and I was also inspired by that ongoing preoccupation with the human condition of mine. (Kirkus Reviews calls the book &amp;quot;A poignant examination of what it means to be human.&amp;quot; Which is very nice of them. The equally kind folks at Publisher&amp;#39;s Weekly call the novel &amp;quot;funny, fresh, and winsome.&amp;quot;) Crucially, Mars One and my organization both had the same ironclad rule: No sex on Mars. But my novel begins &amp;quot;This is how I find out Jenny is pregnant on Mars,&amp;quot; so you can see how that rule worked out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beyond the writing, I also teach creative writing and literature at Georgetown University, and live with my family in Washington, DC. You can find out more about me at &lt;a href=&quot;http://davidebenbach.com/&quot;&gt;davidebenbach.com&lt;/a&gt; or on social media; I&amp;#39;m on Facebook (@DEbenbach), Twitter (@debenbach), and Instagram (@davidebenbach). In the meantime, though, ask me anything here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/glba7lyopo171.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/glba7lyopo171.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[當你在一本奇幻書中讀到10章時，你仍然不明白髮生了什麼，你會怎麼做？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像我們有一對有趣和可愛的人物在冒險，但由於某種原因
幻想世界的行話對我來說就像它在第一章中那樣令人困惑。
第一章中的那樣

幾乎每一次對話都會使用這些特定於特定幻想世界的行話

"但是，Jodiea，那Shrokai呢？"

"我們...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmffcz/what_do_you_do_when_you_are_10_chapters_into_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nmffcz/what_do_you_do_when_you_are_10_chapters_into_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 22:46:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like we have a couple funny and likeable characters on an adventure for some reason and the fantasy world lingo is just as confusing as it was to me as it was in Chapter 1&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Almost every conversation uses these jargon specific to the given fantasy world&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;But, Jodiea, what about the Shrokai?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;We can just wutis the Shrokai, don&amp;#39;t worry about that, young Insrei.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like the &amp;quot;wow, that&amp;#39;s so cool&amp;quot; factor of fantasy books and hate the &amp;quot;what&amp;#39;s going on&amp;quot; question popping up in my head every 2 minutes &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes the lore of a fantasy book is like 20 reading levels above you&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[非常飢餓的毛毛蟲》的作者Eric Carle去世了]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nlte9h/eric_carle_creator_of_the_very_hungry_caterpillar/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nlte9h/eric_carle_creator_of_the_very_hungry_caterpillar/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 23:08:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲19/20歲的人編寫的成長/青年書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我今年19歲，下週將滿20歲，我想重新開始閱讀。我現在不在
我現在不在學校，我只是在工作，並試圖弄清楚我想做什麼
我的生活。我一直很鬱悶，我想逃避它。我的腦袋曾經
一直埋頭於書中，我想重新獲得這種愛....。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nllpil/coming_of_ageya_book_for_1920_year_old/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nllpil/coming_of_ageya_book_for_1920_year_old/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 22:46:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m 19 turning 20 next week and I want to get back into reading. I&amp;#39;m not in school right now, I&amp;#39;m just working and trying to figure out what I want to do with my life. I&amp;#39;ve been depressed and I want an escape from it. My head used to constantly be buried in a book and I want to regain that love. It&amp;#39;s hard to find anything that really captures me anymore. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was younger (like middle school/early highschool age) I used to love reading books where I could relate to the main characters. I want to find a book like that again but for my current age. So my question is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are some good coming of age/ young adult books for a girl in her early 20s?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於閱讀艾薩克-阿西莫夫的 "基金會 "傳奇和2000年以前的一般科幻作品]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近開始閱讀阿西莫夫的 "基礎 "傳奇，因爲我找到了一本《基礎》的副本。
在我的書架上發現了一本 "基金會的前奏"。這是一本很久以前在高中時有人借給我的書。
但我當時正在讀別的書，所以我 "把它放在清單上"，然後忘記了。
所以我把它放在清單上，然後把它忘了（混蛋的舉動，我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nlgd6o/on_reading_the_foundation_saga_by_isaac_asimov/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nlgd6o/on_reading_the_foundation_saga_by_isaac_asimov/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 15:42:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve recently started reading Asimov&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;Foundation&amp;quot; Saga after finding a copy of &amp;quot;Prelude to Foundation&amp;quot; on my bookshelf. It was a book someone lent me a long time ago in High School but I was reading something else at the time, so I &amp;quot;put it on the list&amp;quot; and forgot about it (dick move, I know).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While &amp;quot;Solaris&amp;quot; by Stanislaw Lem is still my favorite work of science fiction to date, through Asimov&amp;#39;s books I&amp;#39;ve discovered the joy of looking at how some aspects of technology are already far better than what the author thought would be 12.000 years into the Galactic Era (after the colonization of the entire galaxy). In Asimov&amp;#39;s world, there are multiple separate machines and computers for specific tasks, while most of our daily tasks can be done on a single computer that fits in the palm of our hand. Books are stored on &amp;#39;microfilms&amp;#39;, whereas we have PDF-s and e-books nowadays. To put the difference into perspective, back in 1950-70, a &amp;quot;well-read&amp;quot; person&amp;#39;s personal library could take up an entire room, with shelves sagging under the weight of all that paper. In Asimov&amp;#39;s world, that would be about a shoebox&amp;#39;s worth of microfilms. In our modern day, all of that can be stored on a piece of plastic the size of a fingernail called a MicroSD card.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So yeah... 1940s sci-fi is amazing and I highly recommend reading Asimov&amp;#39;s works&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不記得兩三年前讀過的書中的細節了]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的很煩惱，因爲我無法記住一本書的某些細節，比如說
人物的名字，情節的轉折點和整體結構等。
情節。我能夠記住的是在閱讀時讓我印象深刻的事情，以及故事的總體背景。
故事的一般背景。我可能還能告訴你...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nl6g9d/i_cant_remember_details_from_books_i_read_23/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nl6g9d/i_cant_remember_details_from_books_i_read_23/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 14:50:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It really bothers me that I can&amp;#39;t remember certain details of a book, like the names of characters, plot points such as twists and the overall structure of the plot. What I can remember are things that stuck out to me while reading, and the general context of the story. I can also probably tell you what some of these characters where, like this is guy was a doctor, lawyer, etc. What is strange that if a novel has a film adaptation then I have a much easier time remembering it. For example, after reading the novel, Congo, I decided to watch the movie version. I can remember most of the main characters and their names, but some plot elements are hazy. Ive been having dark thoughts recently, like what is the point of reading a book if I&amp;#39;m just going to forget most of it in 2 or 3 years? Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong reading many of Michael Chricton&amp;#39;s novels pretty much got me through high school, it just irritates me that a lot of it just feels like a blur in my mind.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[貝爾丁學校在暑期爲所有K-4年級學生提供免費書籍。"該計劃不僅允許學生借書，而且還爲他們提供了九種不同的小說，他們可以保留"]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nlfhbg/belding_schools_offer_free_books_for_all_k4/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nlfhbg/belding_schools_offer_free_books_for_all_k4/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 14:14:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不想看書的結局，假裝它沒有結束，這很常見嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在過去的幾個月裏，我很難讀到書的結尾，這意味着我通常會在高潮前後或緊接着 "放棄 "它們。
這意味着我通常會在高潮前後或緊接着 "放棄 "它們。這是某種
不合理的恐懼或不願意讓事情過去？我也一直在處理
這些奇怪的懷舊哭訴，我花了好幾個小時哭......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nl5exm/is_it_common_to_not_want_to_read_the_ending_of_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nl5exm/is_it_common_to_not_want_to_read_the_ending_of_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 10:59:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past few months I’ve had a hard time reading the ending to books, which means I usually “drop” them around the climax or right after. Is this some sort of irrational fear or reluctance to let things go? I’ve also been dealing with these weird nostalgia crying spells where I spend hours crying over the smallest or weirdest things about my childhood - I made another Reddit post about that actually. But I don’t know if I’m just weird and I don’t know if there’s some underlying things that make me do this, but it’s like I unconsciously “lose interest” when I feel like the end is near. It’s like my mind won’t let me accept that all good things must come to an end.. is this common?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我們是r/ClassicBookClub。從5月31日開始，加入我們的《多裏安-格雷的畫像》閱讀活動。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你好，r/Books [https://www.reddit.com/r/Books/]! 我們是一個小型的閱讀
社區，名爲r/ClassicBookClub [https://www.reddit.com/r/ClassicBookClub/]。
我們每天閱讀並討論一本經典書籍的一個章節，在一個專門的
我們每天閱讀和討論一章經典書籍，並在一個專門的無破壞性的討論主題中。

我們的讀者提名並投票選出...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkzf3c/we_are_rclassicbookclub_join_us_for_a_reading_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkzf3c/we_are_rclassicbookclub_join_us_for_a_reading_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 May 2021 00:00:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/Books/&quot;&gt;r/Books&lt;/a&gt;! We are a small reading community called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/ClassicBookClub/&quot;&gt;r/ClassicBookClub&lt;/a&gt;, and we read and discuss a chapter of a classic book each day in a dedicated spoiler free discussion thread.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our readers nominate and vote on the books we read, and the winning book for our next read is The Picture of Dorian Gray by Oscar Wilde. We are coming to the end of our current reading and will begin The Picture of Dorian Gray on May 31st.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pinned at the top of our subreddit is the Announcement post for the Dorian Gray reading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our first rule for books that we read is they must be in the public domain and we provide links to free versions from Project Gutenberg, Standard Ebooks, and audiobooks from Librivox. We also have a link to a dramatic reading from Librivox which should be fun!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Readers are free to choose whichever medium they want, and read in any language they are comfortable with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our sidebar you’ll find links for our current book, our rules, a link to our discussion archive, and links to our family of subreddits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We just hit 1300 subscribers and would love to keep growing. So if reading one chapter of classic literature a day and discussing it with a group of fellow readers interests you, then come check us out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any questions please let me know, and I wish you all happy reading!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[女同性戀的愛情書籍建議？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的想讀一些有兩個女同性戀戀人的書，最好是一些有幻想或行動的書。
有一些幻想或行動的東西 💗]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nkyqut/a_lesbian_love_book_suggestion/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nkyqut/a_lesbian_love_book_suggestion/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really want to read something with two lesbian lovers preferably something with some fantasy or action in it 💗&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是克里斯蒂安-坎特雷爾，一個軟件開發人員，他寫了一個短篇小說，被福克斯公司選中，現在是一部小說，名叫《天蠍》。AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[十一年前，我寫了一個短篇小說，並自行出版，名爲《EPOCH》。
索引。我幾乎忘記了它，直到2018年，我接到一個電話，來自一個
製片人的電話。今天，這個故事已經被福克斯公司選中。
[https://deadline.com/2018/03/epoch-index-brad-peyton-matt-reeves-justin-rhodes-fox-christian...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkrt2g/im_christian_cantrell_a_software_developer_who/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkrt2g/im_christian_cantrell_a_software_developer_who/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eleven years ago, I wrote and self-published a short story called THE EPOCH INDEX. I&amp;#39;d almost forgotten about it until, in 2018, I got a call from a producer. Today, the story has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://deadline.com/2018/03/epoch-index-brad-peyton-matt-reeves-justin-rhodes-fox-christian-cantrell-1202311973/&quot;&gt;optioned by FOX&lt;/a&gt; and is a full-length novel called SCORPION &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Scorpion-Novel-Christian-Cantrell-ebook/dp/B08817L618/&quot;&gt;(launching today)&lt;/a&gt;. Although I&amp;#39;m a software developer, I studied literature and creative writing in college, and for almost twenty years, I&amp;#39;ve spent my mornings writing fiction and my days &lt;a href=&quot;https://christiancantrell.com/#employment&quot;&gt;writing code&lt;/a&gt;. SCORPION is my fourth novel, and I&amp;#39;ve also sold work to &lt;a href=&quot;https://deadline.com/2020/07/brainbox-series-hulu-christian-cantrell-fox-21-david-kajganich-showrunner-1202990418/&quot;&gt;Hulu&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://deadline.com/2019/04/tristar-escape-artists-female-thriller-daniel-kunka-screenplay-1202588720/&quot;&gt;TriStar&lt;/a&gt;. Ask me anything!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/p8wmvodh44171.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/p8wmvodh44171.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我看了《沙丘》大約100頁，感覺很費勁。是什麼吸引你看這本書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在努力讀完弗蘭克-赫伯特的科幻小說經典。
主要是爲了準備即將上映的電影。然而，儘管它
儘管它具有傳奇性的聲譽，但我覺得要想繼續閱讀每一章都是一種掙扎。
下一章。人物感覺很平淡，情節似乎是故意的。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nksyrc/im_about_100_pages_into_dune_and_it_feels_like_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nksyrc/im_about_100_pages_into_dune_and_it_feels_like_a/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:34:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been trying to read through Frank Herbert’s science fiction classic, primarily in preparation for the movie coming out. However, despite its legendary reputation, it feels like a struggle to even want to move on to each next chapter. The characters feel flat, the plot seeming intentionally obscured to the point where I can’t seem to care about what is happening, and the dialogue is rough to say the least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But I know that there must be something that makes this novel have so much hype to it. What am I missing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[夜間馬戲團》是我讀過的寫得最好的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我的生活中，我從來沒有讀過一本感覺如此複雜而又不至於過於複雜或花哨的書。
複雜的或花哨的。每一個場景都有一種重要的感覺
並在我腦海中描繪出一幅生動的畫面。這很難描述。我不知道如何
做到的，但它現在是我寫作的黃金標準......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkz81t/the_night_circus_is_the_most_well_written_book_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkz81t/the_night_circus_is_the_most_well_written_book_i/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 22:34:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have never in my life read a book that felt so sophisticated without being overly complex or flowery. Every scene felt like it had a sense of importance and painted a vivid picture in my head. It’s hard to describe. I don’t know how It was done, but it is now my gold standard for how writing should be done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲我的山莊核心幻想提供的書籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想讀的是，有人拋棄公司/城市生活，在鄉村或沉睡的小鎮定居下來
在鄉下或沉睡的小鎮上定居。或者，過着數字遊民的生活。A
回憶錄將是一個加分項。

如果你看過吉卜力工作室的電影《只有昨天》--這基本上就是我想要的，但要以書的形式出現。
我想要的東西，但要以書的形式。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nkhvy1/books_for_my_cottagecore_fantasy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nkhvy1/books_for_my_cottagecore_fantasy/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 11:07:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to read about someone ditching the corporate/city life and settling down in the countryside or a sleepy town. Or else, leading the digital nomad life. A memoir will be a plus!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have seen the movie Only Yesterday by Studio Ghibli - that is basically what I want but in a book form.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊尼德-布萊頓的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，我想知道是否還有人記得伊尼德-布萊頓的系列圖書
印象深刻。我仍然有一個收藏品--甚至還增加了幾本精美的帶封皮的古籍
我仍然有一套書--甚至還增加了幾本帶防塵套的精裝古董書--偶爾也會翻翻看，很高興。

你對近年來 "淨化 "文本的舉措有何看法？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkioyo/enid_blyton_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkioyo/enid_blyton_books/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:03:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, I was wondering if anyone else still recalls the Enid Blyton book series fondly. I still have a collection - and have even added a few fine antique hardback copies with dust jacket - and dip in occasionally, with delight. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think about moves in recent years to &amp;#39;sanitise&amp;#39; the texts and change wordings to reflect contemporary sensitivities? For e.g. omitting all mention of spanking?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you think it&amp;#39;s ever okay to change words in a writer&amp;#39;s work, without their approval, when they&amp;#39;re no longer around to give it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[從杜氏家族的角度看《哈利-波特》是一個恐怖故事。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直很喜歡《哈利-波特》系列中與蛇對話的想法。
當羅恩在最後一本書中用它來進入密室時，我比我應該做的更興奮。
我比我應該做的更興奮。儘管如此，我認爲這一點在書中實現得很差。
除此以外，它在書中的應用也很差。我正在重新觀看...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkisgg/harry_potter_is_a_horror_story_from_the_dursleys/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nkisgg/harry_potter_is_a_horror_story_from_the_dursleys/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:35:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve always enjoyed the idea of speaking to snakes in the Harry Potter series. When Ron uses it to get into the Chamber of Secrets in the final book I was more excited than I should have been. That being said I think that it was poorly implemented in the books aside from that.
I&amp;#39;m rewatching the first movie and I got to the scene of Harry in the reptile room at the beginning. I began to think of how strange he must have looked speaking this language to the people around them. Then I realized that he seems to switch between parseltounge and English without conscious thought. This is evident in the dualing scene with Draco in the second book.
This would paint the Dursleys in a slightly more sympathetic light, not by much but at least a little. While I would never treat a child that way I can see how it might be concerning if not out right concerning. Imagine you were at a family function and your adopted son started speaking in tounges, in this case hissing like a black metal singer, and stuff starts exploding. This would be horrifying and written with a different tone and a change of narrator we could have something straight out of a horror movie.
Now imagine you are the Dursleys and your adopted nephew is walking around hissing and blowing shit up with his mind. You hadn&amp;#39;t talked to your relatives for years and now you are in charge of their son. He shows up on your doorstep in the middle of the night one night along with a letter that literally screams at you. This is all before you even know your relative is dead. You raise this child of your estranged relative reluctantly. As he gets older it becomes apparent that when he is upset that your nephew is capable of things that defy explanation of natural law. You have no idea what these powers are capable of or how dangerous to you, or your child, they are.
This all makes the Dursleys dislike of Harry Potter a little more sympathetic, at least to me.
TL;DR: Harry Potter is a Horror Movie from the Dursleys perspective.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尋找類似於2016年艾米-亞當斯主演的電影《降臨》的推薦。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在幾年前看過這部電影后，我第二次觀看了這部電影。
我真的很喜歡它，就像第一次觀看時一樣。我知道這部電影改編自
我知道這部電影是根據泰德-蔣的短篇小說《你的生活的故事》改編的，我打算讀一讀這個故事。
閱讀。我想看看是否有人對這部電影有什麼建議。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nkcq4f/looking_for_a_recommendation_similar_to_the_2016/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nkcq4f/looking_for_a_recommendation_similar_to_the_2016/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 07:19:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I watched this movie for the second time after seeing it a couple years ago and I really loved it as much as the first viewing. I know this film is based off of a short story called &amp;quot;Story of Your Life&amp;quot; by Ted Chiang, which I plan on reading. I wanted them see if anyone has any suggestions for something similar, whether that be the science fiction aspects, the unique use of language, or the &amp;quot;plot twist&amp;quot; of the movie (don&amp;#39;t wanna post any spoilers).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[維克多-弗蘭克爾（Viktor Frankl）的《人類對意義的探索》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近讀完了這本書。它帶領你瞭解了在奧斯威辛集中營生活的人所面臨的艱難困苦和只是
那些生活在奧斯威辛集中營的人所面臨的精神折磨。
我喜歡他強調是什麼讓他不顧自己的處境而堅持下去。他如何
他沒有像其他大多數囚犯那樣神志不清。他...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njws6h/mans_search_for_meaning_by_viktor_frankl/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njws6h/mans_search_for_meaning_by_viktor_frankl/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 04:30:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finished reading this recently. It walks you through the hardships and just the mental torture faced by those who lived in concentration camps in Auschwitz. I loved how he emphasized on what kept him going despite his circumstances. How he didn&amp;#39;t go delirious like most of the other prisoners. He says this beautiful quote &amp;quot;I dread not being worthy of my suffering&amp;quot;. The book talks about how you should rise above your circumstances and how despite the same one always has spiritual freedom where he can find his solace in. And, I love how he said just proving to be useful does not give meaning to your life and how people these days only like successful,young and happy people. I love how he also said old people shouldn&amp;#39;t be pitied . You can find meaning in loving someone and other ways which help you be beyond yourself.I thoroughly enjoyed it and would recommend it to anyone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我開始用閱讀器閱讀，我以前很討厭它，現在我絕對喜歡它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直認爲，閱讀器是愚蠢的。我沒有讀過那麼多書，而且爲數不多的幾次
我讀過幾次書，我寧願買一本。但現在我借了別人的閱讀器
因爲上面有一本我想讀的特定的書，我就愛上了它。
我愛上了這個閱讀器! 它拿起來舒服多了，很容易...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njv769/i_started_reading_on_an_ereader_which_i_used_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njv769/i_started_reading_on_an_ereader_which_i_used_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 03:53:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I always thought that ereaders were stupid. I didn&amp;#39;t read that much, and the few times I read a book I rather buy one. But I now borrowed someone&amp;#39;s ereader because there was a specific book on it that I wanted to read, and I fell in love with the ereader! It is so much more comfortabel to hold, easy to take with you and you can easily access multiple books. I now read way more than I used to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So to anyone who is against ereaders, it is really not that bad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[嗨，我是暢銷書作家大衛-尹，有一部新的驚悚片（零版），問：互聯網到底值不值得？AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好! 我是紐約時報的暢銷書作家。我寫了驚悚片《零》，即將出版的世界末日懸疑片《橘子之城》，以及年輕的《我的世界》。
零》，即將出版的世界末日懸疑小說《橙城》，以及青少年小說《坦誠的愛》和《超級假情歌》。
以及青年小說《坦誠相見》和《超級假情歌》。我是威廉-C-莫里斯
獎的入圍者，也是美國亞太青年獎的獲獎者。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nk5gwn/hi_im_bestselling_author_david_yoon_with_a_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nk5gwn/hi_im_bestselling_author_david_yoon_with_a_new/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 21:54:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there! I’m a New York Times bestselling author. I wrote the thriller Version Zero, the upcoming apocalyptic mystery City of Orange, as well as the young adult novels Frankly in Love and Super Fake Love Song. I&amp;#39;m a William C. Morris Award finalist and an Asian/Pacific American Award for Young Adult Literature Honor book recipient. I’m also co-publisher of Joy Revolution, a Random House young adult imprint dedicated to love stories starring people of color. I live in Los Angeles with my wacky daughter and super awesome wife, novelist Nicola Yoon. My internet source of truth is at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.davidyoon.com&quot;&gt;www.davidyoon.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/w082ehy3tb071.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/w082ehy3tb071.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果你喜歡《火星人》，你應該讀一讀《聖母計劃》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[安迪-威爾的第一部小說《火星人》獲得了巨大的成功。雖然它
可能沒有很多純粹的文學價值，但它是不折不扣的怪胎。
驚險、有趣，完全配得上所有的讚譽和它對當前科幻領域的影響。
它對當前的科幻景觀產生了影響。

他的下一部小說《阿耳特彌斯》，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nk2ghm/if_you_liked_the_martian_you_should_read_project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nk2ghm/if_you_liked_the_martian_you_should_read_project/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 20:32:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Andy Weir had a smash success with his first novel, The Martian. While it probably didn&amp;#39;t have a lot of pure literary merit, it was unabashedly geeky, thrilling, fun and entirely deserving of all the accolades and the impact it made on the current sci-fi landscape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His next novel, Artemis, magnified all the faults of the first while retaining none of the charm. Attempts to write a more complex plot left it a heavy, jumbled mess. The lack of real characters or character development in The Martian was excusable. In Artemis all attempts at it were forced and cringey. The science and long technical explanations went from seamlessly driving the narrative in The Martian to hampering it to the extent where you get actively frustrated by them. In short – nothing worked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Project Hail Mary is, in a sense, a return to the author&amp;#39;s roots. Like in The Martian, the protagonist is a genius and witty scientist caught alone in a bad situation who must use his knowledge to fix things. The stakes are a lot higher. Instead of Mars, this time he is on a spaceship far away from Earth. Instead of saving just himself this time all of humanity is on the line. Oh and he has amnesia, so isn&amp;#39;t able to remember the ship, his mission or even his own name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What follows is a saga of exploration, trial and error, mess ups, fixes, near deaths etc. as he inches closer to his goal. It&amp;#39;s The Martian on steroids, and the author makes no excuses for it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the author&amp;#39;s faults still stood this time around. I&amp;#39;m putting some of them in spoiler tags to be safe, but they aren&amp;#39;t really spoilers so read them if you&amp;#39;d like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;At 500 pages, it is a bit of a slog. There are a lot of repetitive parts and could have been easily edited down another 100 pages at least.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I found it harder to excuse the juvenile writing this time around considering the author is on his &lt;em&gt;third&lt;/em&gt; bestselling novel. There is so much wrong with pacing, narrative structure, characters, exposition etc. that &amp;quot;yeah, science!&amp;quot; won&amp;#39;t magically fix.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The science stuff – &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;While the scientific explanations and overall plot in The Martian made some amount of sense, Project Hail Mary makes you take one too many massive leaps of logic. That isn&amp;#39;t a deal breaker for a sci-fi book by any means, but the author&amp;#39;s writing style emphasizes the &amp;quot;science&amp;quot; side while giving you a story which would fit better in The Expanse.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The protagonist – &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;For both better and worse, the protagonist is Mark Watney 2.0. He is a genius at every possible science, has all the knowledge of the world at the tip of his tongue, is witty, commanding when he needs to be, selfless, empathetic...Oh and he has six pack abs of course. While Mark Watney came off as charming, this one is just..dull.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With sci-fi tastes as varied as they are, it&amp;#39;s hard to predict how the average reader will feel about Project Hail Mary. There are a lot of fun moments, some thrills and a lot of faults. So I will simply say that if you liked The Martian, you will probably like this one as well.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[將閱讀視爲一種苦差事，即使你喜歡這本書，這正常嗎？我不明白爲什麼有些人可以在一次飛機飛行中讀完一整本書。這不是精神上的疲憊嗎（即使是一本好書）？我很難一次閱讀超過45分鐘......]]></title><description><![CDATA[獲取信息（或爲休閒而閱讀）感覺是件苦差事，即使是一本令人愉快的書（甚至在我沒有睡眠不足或其他原因的情況下）也是如此。
當它是一本令人愉快的書時（甚至當我沒有睡眠不足或任何事情時）。
我想這與在Netflix上觀看電視節目的經歷非常相似--有些人可以在一整季中狂歡。
有些人可以在一天內狂歡一整季；而我只能坐在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njxfts/is_it_normal_to_view_reading_as_a_chore_even_if/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njxfts/is_it_normal_to_view_reading_as_a_chore_even_if/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 19:03:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It just feels like such a chore to obtain information (or read for leisure) even when it’s an enjoyable book (and even when I’m not sleep-deprived or anything). I guess it’s a very similar experience to watching a TV show on Netflix — some people can binge whole seasons in one day; I can only sit through like 3, or maximum 4 episodes, per day even if I’m addicted to the show. At that point, mentally I’m pretty fried.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To those of you who read a lot — at which point do you generally start to feel exhausted by reading? The 1-hour mark? 1.5? 2? 4? Etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’ve also heard that your reading tolerance is a muscle — that the more you read and build a tolerance to the exhaustion, the less easily you’ll find yourself exhausted (i.e. the muscle will grow).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even as a kid in Elementary School (with normal sleeping habits), I remember enjoying good books, but being left mentally exhausted after reading for like an hour (which we were forced to record onto a sheet, signed daily by our parents, for daily school homework).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[向我推薦你讀過的最好的書和最差的書，你不會向任何人推薦*不要告訴我哪個是哪個*。]]></title><description><![CDATA[(流派並不重要)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/njvs70/suggest_me_the_best_book_youve_ever_read_and_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/njvs70/suggest_me_the_best_book_youve_ever_read_and_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 16:02:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Genre Doesnt Matter)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國國家航空航天局定期出版電子書，可供免費下載。美國航空航天局的新電子書名爲《哈勃聚焦》。恆星的生活 - 關於哈勃太空望遠鏡。這本新的電子書提供了美國宇航局所說的 "深入研究天文學中的特定主題"，哈勃任務改變了這些主題。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njnk8z/nasa_regularly_publishes_ebooks_that_are/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njnk8z/nasa_regularly_publishes_ebooks_that_are/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 03:50:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[每當我提前歸還一本電子書時，我就會有一種滿足感。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的圖書館使用Overdrive圖書館系統。我不知道它到底是如何運作的。
但我的州（和我的稅款）爲它支付了費用，我的當地圖書館讓我可以免費獲得絕對大量的電子書。
我的當地圖書館讓我免費獲得了大量的電子書。我相信你們中的許多人都有類似的
的系統。

總之，當我看完一本電子書後，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njfjed/i_get_a_kick_of_satisfaction_whenever_i_return_an/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/njfjed/i_get_a_kick_of_satisfaction_whenever_i_return_an/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 01:58:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My library uses an Overdrive library system. I don&amp;#39;t know exactly how it works, but my state (and my tax dollars) pays for it and my local library gives me access to an absolute ton of ebooks for free. I&amp;#39;m sure many of you have similar systems available to you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, when I&amp;#39;m done with an ebook, especially one I had on hold, I don&amp;#39;t like to let it expire on it&amp;#39;s own. Now, for those of you who don&amp;#39;t know, you can check out a book and keep it for the whole loan period, and when it&amp;#39;s up the book is automatically returned for you - no interaction required. But the neat thing is, the system is able to estimate how long you&amp;#39;ll have to wait to receive that book, based on the standard loan period. So, if three people are waiting in line for one book and the standard loan period is two weeks, it&amp;#39;ll be six weeks before I&amp;#39;ll get to check out the book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, when I have a book to return, I have this little ritual I do where I click into the book&amp;#39;s page and I double check how many people are in line behind me waiting for that book. Then, when I go to my Loans page to return it, I get a little charge out of the fact that someone else, perhaps hundreds of miles away, is getting an email informing them that the book they&amp;#39;ve been waiting for is now available to check out. I imagine their surprise and excitement at being able to read this book a week (or more!) earlier than expected. It&amp;#39;s a little, random act of kindness I can do once every few days that makes me feel a little better about myself, and a little more connected to my community in general and the fans of that book in specific.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this to say, if you&amp;#39;re in Wisconsin and you have Brandon Sanderson&amp;#39;s Mistborn series on hold, please return it early when you&amp;#39;re done with it! I have to wait six months for each book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Robert Ludlum的《伯恩的身份》是我讀過的最好的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果這不是你的類型，請原諒我，但如果是的話，我懷疑是否有更優秀的書
寫的。我已經讀了幾十本盧德勒姆的小說，當他寫第一本伯恩的書時，他就像在一個完全不同的層面上。
他在寫第一本《伯恩》的時候，就像是在另一個層面上。我仍然記得在
我還記得在我的大學宿舍裏，和一半的人一起看馬特-達蒙的電影......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nj12f3/the_bourne_identity_by_robert_ludlum_is_the_best/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nj12f3/the_bourne_identity_by_robert_ludlum_is_the_best/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 01:58:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excuse me if this isn&amp;#39;t your genre, but if it is, I doubt there is a finer book written. I&amp;#39;ve read dozens of other Ludlum novels, it&amp;#39;s like he was on a whole other plane when he was writing the first Bourne book. I still remember being in my college dorm and watching the Matt Damon movie with half a dozen other guys and feeling so disappointed in the movie at the end (when the other 6 were going ga-ga)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are obviously other great books out there, and &amp;#39;best&amp;#39; is very subjective, but I have a lot of Alistair Macleans, Fred Forsyth, Tom Clancy (very average imo) and while there have been a couple of books that maybe in the league of Bourne Identity, none have equaled or surpassed it&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Alright, peace out fam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS - Love this sub to much!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你所讀過的寫得最漂亮的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛在kindle上讀完《阿基里斯之歌》，文章寫得很好。
我買了一本實體書，這樣我就可以回去做批註了。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/njhj27/the_most_beautifully_written_book_youve_ever_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/njhj27/the_most_beautifully_written_book_youve_ever_read/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 01:58:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished The Song Of Achilles on kindle, and the writing was so incredible I bought a physical copy so I can go back and do annotations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[綠野仙蹤》真的值得大肆宣傳]]></title><description><![CDATA[我聽說這本書和電影都很精彩，但哇，它們真的是。我去年看了
我去年看了這部電影，然後抓住機會讀了這本書。起初，我很驚訝
驚訝於兩者之間的吻合程度。特別是考慮到斯蒂芬-金的改編作品的跟蹤記錄
特別是考慮到斯蒂芬-金改編作品的記錄，我沒有想到會有近乎一比一的吻合。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nj6b5y/the_green_mile_really_is_worth_the_hype/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nj6b5y/the_green_mile_really_is_worth_the_hype/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 16:06:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d heard that the book and movie were amazing, but wow, they really are. I saw the film last year, and jumped on the chance to read the book. At first, I was surprised at how closely the two matched. Especially given the track record of Stephen King adaptations, I didn&amp;#39;t expect a near one-to-one in some sections.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Much as I adore the film, the book got deeper under my skin. We see the beauty of little moments and small &amp;quot;miracles&amp;quot; contrasting a bleak setting. This is death row, so maybe anything can seem light when compared to what&amp;#39;s coming next. Still, I found myself laughing and smiling at the descriptions of Mr. Jingles&amp;#39; antics. I had to, otherwise the rest of the book would&amp;#39;ve overwhelmed me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The senseless and random tragedies of life fill most of the pages. The intense focus on Paul&amp;#39;s experience keeps it manageable, but man, it still hurts. Percy Whetmore is a brilliant character, and I hate him. I loathe him with every fiber of my being, because I recognize him. The description of juvenile malice, the people who can&amp;#39;t laugh at a joke unless it&amp;#39;s mean, made me think of a few real world Percys.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet, it&amp;#39;s a beautiful story. Even if the book-only conclusion is one of the most pensive and melancholic things I&amp;#39;ve read in a while. So many of the events and choices are drenched in a palpable uncertainty. Was this the right thing? Did any of it matter? This was the story I needed right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Despite it&amp;#39;s bluntness, it remains life-affirming. Even something as minor as a mouse doing tricks can be cause for celebration. A companion can make help ease that walk down the Mile. Part of me wants to be mad because I&amp;#39;ll never write anything this good, but hot damn, Stephen King, you made a masterpiece. Thanks for breaking me down and building me back up. I loved every page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[封面確實很重要]]></title><description><![CDATA[作爲一個經常買書的人，我經常被漂亮的封面所吸引。
如果封面漂亮，我就會傾向於查看該書的簡介。在
在我已經決定購買的書中，我總是選擇封面最漂亮的版本。
而且我願意爲它多付一些錢。這讓我很不爽...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nj2hq3/the_cover_does_matter/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nj2hq3/the_cover_does_matter/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 23 May 2021 10:58:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As someone who buys books all the time, I am often attracted by a pretty cover. If the cover is pretty, I am inclined to check out the book&amp;#39;s synopsis. In the cases of books I am already decided on, I always pick the edition with the nicest cover and I am willing to pay some extra for it. It bugs me that so many books have ugly, unattractive covers. Those I buy used, at the cheapest prices available. There is a special delight to look at a beautiful colored novel while reading it and later admiring among the others, on the shelf.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>