<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 04:37:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[2021年最值得阅读的21本恐怖小说]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pyq3s3/the_21_best_horror_books_to_read_in_2021/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pyq3s3/the_21_best_horror_books_to_read_in_2021/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 23:55:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[书籍中的女主角和其他女孩一样，都是真正的现实中的正常人？(没有悲惨的背景故事，没有虐待父母，没有使她无法做出基本逻辑决定的严重焦虑）。)]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道是我运气不好，还是现在的书都是以同样的女主角为主题。
现在的书都有相同的女主人公，但我最近读的几乎每本书都有相同的女主人公，至少有两个或更多的以下特征。
都有相同的女主人公，至少有两个或更多以下特征。

-不像其他女孩（因为她们知道如何看书，或者是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pylxko/books_with_heroines_that_are_just_like_other/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pylxko/books_with_heroines_that_are_just_like_other/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 21:22:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t know if I&amp;#39;ve just been down on my luck or books are actually all featuring the same heroine nowadays, but literally almost EVERY book I&amp;#39;ve read recently have the same heroine with the at least two or more following traits:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Not like other girls (because they know how to read books or is capable of a clap back WOW)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Tragic backstory&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Whole world hates them for no reason&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-abusive family, because of above trait, everyone is a jerk to them and poor them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Offhandedly mentioned that they&amp;#39;re actually very pretty, they don&amp;#39;t need to make an effort like other girls do though, it&amp;#39;s just that every guy (even though they hate her) agree that she&amp;#39;s pretty but she&amp;#39;s the only one who doesn&amp;#39;t know that (*GAGS*)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me this is just lazy writing to add pity points, I get that authors want their characters to be liked and rooted for but still &amp;quot;complex&amp;quot; and relatable, and these traits are just the easy way to do so. I&amp;#39;m not saying people with these issues don&amp;#39;t exist, I&amp;#39;m just so TIRED of reading about these girls?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve noticed that these traits are all primarily in heroines in contrast to heroes, like a girl is only &amp;quot;heroine worthy&amp;quot; if they&amp;#39;re quirky and hated by the world. Or they&amp;#39;re only allowed to have mental-healthy issues because literally they&amp;#39;re cursed and whole world is downright comically vile to them on the daily. Where as there are plenty complex and well written heroes out there without a need for these traits to help their likability. Maybe it&amp;#39;s just my luck though, I can&amp;#39;t generalize.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS. I&amp;#39;ve seen other people who have answered to requests for &amp;quot;NOT not like other girls heroine&amp;quot; to mean heroines who are girly and feminine, but I don&amp;#39;t mind if the heroine is introvert/shy/tomboyish (or all those traits that make up a typical &amp;quot;not like other girls girl&amp;quot;), as long as the author doesn&amp;#39;t continually use this to wax poetry about how the heroine&amp;#39;s not like other girls or &amp;quot;unique&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;special&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;a breath of fresh air&amp;quot; purely because they possess these completely average traits seen in plenty other people of all genders.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在邪教中长大的人，刚刚被大学录取]]></title><description><![CDATA[什么书能帮助我]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pyp7h2/just_got_accepted_in_college_after_growing_up_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pyp7h2/just_got_accepted_in_college_after_growing_up_in/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 20:48:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;what books will help me&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有鬼屋/哥特式黑色幽默感的书？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在寻找长长的黑暗走廊，一个巨大的图书馆，令人毛骨悚然的人物，一个家庭墓地，也许还有一个隐藏的地牢或其他东西。
家庭墓地，也许还有一个隐藏的地牢或其他东西。幽灵和哥特式
鼓励维多利亚式的审美。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pyhfvi/books_with_a_haunted_mansiongothic_noir_vibe/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pyhfvi/books_with_a_haunted_mansiongothic_noir_vibe/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 17:44:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for long dark hallways, a massive library, creepy characters, a family cemetery, and perhaps a hidden dungeon or something. Ghosts and gothic Victorian aesthetic encouraged.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不要再依赖史翠珊效应来拯救你的审查制度了]]></title><description><![CDATA[对不起，这可能有点咆哮，但在这个子里有许多关于
书籍审查制度的帖子，而且在这些帖子下有一些一贯的评论，我认为
应该有一个普遍的回应。

它们通常是这样的。

"LMAO，学校禁书？孩子们实际上只是在寻找任何东西......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pyj6be/stop_relying_on_the_streisand_effect_to_save_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pyj6be/stop_relying_on_the_streisand_effect_to_save_you/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 14:22:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry, this might be a bit of a rant, but there are many posts in this sub about book censorship, and there are consistently comments under them that I feel deserve a general response. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They usually go something like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;LMAO, schools banning books? Kids will actually just seek out anything taboo, this is just free advertising!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Don&amp;#39;t they understand the Streisand effect? This is guaranteed to just blow up as news and backfire on them!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even at their best, comments like these are coping mechanism based on a just world fallacy, desperately wanting to believe that all will be well in the end, that human nature tends towards freedom, that censorship just simply &lt;em&gt;doesn&amp;#39;t work&lt;/em&gt; at accomplishing it&amp;#39;s goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The thing is... it obviously does work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We can all look at dictatorships that successfully prop up the regime&amp;#39;s support rates, by denying negative information to their population. We can all look at school systems that provide more info on, for example, safe sex, will have will have measurably different outcomes in teenage sexual health.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More generally, the entire conceit of having a school system, is that &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;obviously&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; it can influence what kind of next generation we are raising. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Even stepping away from the legal issue of censorship and free speech, to the realm of platforming, this applies. Big publishers &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; blacklist an author, stifle a genre, or promote a certain aesthetic style or even a political value. It happens all the time. Everyone who ever complained about &amp;quot;cancel culture&amp;quot;, deeply understands this. And of course so does anyone who advocated for boycotting or deplatforming something. (watch out, the two are sometimes the same people). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;The Streisand Effect&amp;quot; is not a scientifically proven pattern, it is an internet meme. Once under a blue moon, some really random incident goes viral, because someone screws up the optics of what book to burn, what book to legally ban, what book to blacklist, or even just what book to criticize, and gets an unintended effect. This doesn&amp;#39;t mean that you can relax secure in the knowledge that this will always reliably happen. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Relying on kamic justice to sort out what books people do and don&amp;#39;t get to access, leads to apathy at best, and at worst you are being led on by somebody whose interest it is for you not to worry too much about &lt;em&gt;a certain type of book&lt;/em&gt; getting banned, but still get worked up about their own favorite type of book facing the mildest possible forms of pushback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[盗版书籍的道德性。]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，生活在黎巴嫩的青少年（17岁），正在经历近代史上最严重的一次
经济危机。

我每天都在阅读中长大。在家里，我们几乎每个房间都有书架。
都摆满了各种文学作品，英文、法文、阿拉伯文。对阅读的需求
阅读的需求在我心中是根深蒂固的......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pyflvz/the_morality_of_pirating_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pyflvz/the_morality_of_pirating_books/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 13:30:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey, teenager (17) living in Lebanon, that is going through one of the worst economic crisis in recent history. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I grew up reading everyday. At home, we have bookshelves in almost every room, all full with all sorts of litterature, english, french, arabic. The need to read is kind of engrained in me at this point. And groing up pre-crisis, I went through phases where I would buy up to eight books a month (which my mom thought was excessive, looking back, i do understand that), devour them all, mainly fantasy and YA books. As a hobbyist writer myself, the idea of &amp;quot;stealing&amp;quot; a book by downloading it online seemed scandalous. However, the recent economic recession kinda shifted my morals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At first, honestly, I just dropped reading all together, I didnt see the point of saving three or four months to buy a book I would read in two weeks, I would rather spend my money on other hobbies, like art, even though, it is also expensive (I dropped art classes, and my desire to learn oil painting, going digital or some other pricey mediums) but I&amp;#39;m not gonna use up pencils and paints as as quickly as I&amp;#39;m gonna read a book. But with time, I started craving reading, creative hobbies take a lot more energy than passive ones, especially for someone with hectic schedules and struggling with mental health, and I got sick of spending 20k lebanese pounds on each pencil. I could reread old books; but taste shifts, I got bored of YA and fantasy, as much comfort as it brought me, growing out of things is inevitable. Yet, it still seemed nonsensical to spend a quarter of my mother&amp;#39;s income on a single book. So I caved, downloaded Sylvia Plath&amp;#39;s The Bell Jar, which moved me. And it didn&amp;#39;t seem wrong, how could a dead Sylvia care more about me not paying for her book than how much this book helped me understand and navigate the world a little better?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I stuck to reading books by dead writers, Oscar Wilde, Charles Bukowski, Jane Austen, but eventually, my reading list got full of books by well alive writers, more relevant to the world right now, and it&amp;#39;s not like these books were getting any cheaper, of course, I still bought some of them, mainly the ones printed in lebanon, much cheaper, but less diverse room for choice. Same for libraries, cheaper, but I had trouble finding exactly what I wanted, and thrift stores not being available in my area, I gave in to the temptation and downloaded A Splendid Thousand Suns by Khaled Hosseini, which is probably one of my favourite books of the year, but I can&amp;#39;t seem to decide how I feel about pirating books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve often heard, &amp;quot;If you can afford a phone, a laptop, or an internet connection, you can afford a book&amp;quot; but this is ridiculous to me, in our current world, not having a phone or a laptop is not an option, 80% of my schooling is done online, more due to fuel prices than covid, I&amp;#39;m majoring in engineering, I &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;need&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; a good laptop, I wouldn&amp;#39;t have spend all my savings on one otherwise. Then, whatever money I have left, I spend on ubers to go to uni, because we do not have good public transport, and I don&amp;#39;t have the guts to ask my parents for more money to spend on books when they are partially paying for my expensive private university (the public education sector is screwed), my medication, food, clothing. I don&amp;#39;t really have a disposable income to spend on entertainment and leisure. And it&amp;#39;s probably similar for a lot of people above the poverty line in western countries. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet it&amp;#39;s still not right, this is essentially stealing, not food, or clothing or a necessity, but stealing for leisure. It wouldn&amp;#39;t be different than shoplifting a book. Except it&amp;#39;s easier and doesn&amp;#39;t hold as much guilt, maybe cause it&amp;#39;s not physical and no employee or small business is getting directly harmed. Except the author and the publishing company. But do authors really care about people that do not have a dime to spare, let alone the equivalent of the minimum wage in the country, downloading their book from z library instead of paying for it ? Maybe it&amp;#39;s not that different from buying a thrifted copy, either way, they don&amp;#39;t get a cut. I don&amp;#39;t know. Maybe I&amp;#39;m just being selfish. I hope someone enlightens me on that one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于抑郁症的虚构书籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在许多人建议下，我阅读了《午夜图书馆》，了解它如何处理精神疾病。
应对精神疾病，但我感到非常失望。这本书开始的时候
很好，但却变成了一个青少年的胡言乱语的聚会。不是很糟糕，只是超级讨好和
明显的结局。

我很想看一本专注于有心理疾病的人物的书。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/py7wno/fictional_books_about_depression/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/py7wno/fictional_books_about_depression/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 12:35:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read &amp;quot;The Midnight Library&amp;quot; after many people&amp;#39;s suggestions about how it tackles mental illness, and I was &lt;strong&gt;severely disappointed.&lt;/strong&gt; The book started off great but turned in to a YA drivel-fest. Not awful, just super pandering and obvious ending.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love a book that focuses on a character with depression, it could be a biography or something from the first person as well, just really wanting to read a book with someone I heavily relate to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[不读书的丈夫：帮助我们开始一个家庭时间的阅读习惯]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在与一种沮丧的感觉作斗争......。

我一直在祈祷并努力提高我的时间效率，这样我就可以
我一直在祈祷，并努力提高我的时间效率，以便我能够找到时间，坐在我的孩子面前看书，而不是一直拿着设备。
而不是手里拿着一个设备。我需要以身作则，我在这里寻求你们的帮助。
帮助，因为...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pyaha9/non_reading_husband_help_us_start_a_family_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pyaha9/non_reading_husband_help_us_start_a_family_time/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 11:31:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been struggling with a feeling of dismay . . .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been praying and working on being more efficient with my time so that I can find a moment and sit with a book in front of my children instead of always have a device in my hand. I need to lead by example and I am here to solicit your help as I feel fully convicted that I am failing them in this regard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for myself, having received by bachelor&amp;#39;s degree (major: psychology; minor: sociology) over 16 years ago and never using it, and getting 90% of the way through my masters (criminal justice) having never completed it, reading (really reading, books WITH PAPER)  seems to be a thing of the past for me. I&amp;#39;d love some inspiration, though I do already have a pile books to start with.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As for my husband, having never completed his formal schooling, reading has never been on his radar. I would be in my glory for myself and my children to witness him enjoying and completing a book.  I don&amp;#39;t have a clue where to start with him. He&amp;#39;s a man&amp;#39;s man of Greek American heritage. He has a very tough exterior but was born with a heart to help and serve. A hard working man of integrity who has suffered many losses over the past 3 years (both parents, a brother, and 3 close friends). He became a dad later in life, 42 and we share 2 children (9 and 11 years old). He&amp;#39;ll be 53 this year. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I give you this background in hopes it may help someone offer some insight on books that may speak to a man of his sort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I thank anyone and everyone who can offer some insight. I would be truly grateful 🙏&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[田纳西州的家长说有些书让学生 "感到不舒服"，因为他们是白人。他们说一项新的法律支持了他们的观点]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py5epd/tennessee_parents_say_some_books_make_students/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py5epd/tennessee_parents_say_some_books_make_students/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 02:14:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚完成了安迪-威尔的 "万福玛利亚计划"，完全是盲目进入。我相信我的经历因为没有阅读简介而得到了极大的提升。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果这本书在你们的阅读清单上，我强烈建议你们不要听任何评论，甚至不要读这本书。
聆听任何评论，甚至在开始之前阅读书籍本身的简介，因为它真的有助于增强故事的神秘感。
它真的有助于增强故事的神秘感。我觉得现在有太多的书为了吸引读者，给了太多
为了吸引观众，现在有太多的书给出了太多的信息。

对于...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py3swg/i_just_finished_project_hail_mary_by_andy_weir/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py3swg/i_just_finished_project_hail_mary_by_andy_weir/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 01:16:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this book is on any of your reading lists I would highly encourage you not to listen to any reviews or even read the books own blurb before beginning as it really helped enhance the mystery of the story. I feel too many books give too much away these days in order to hook their viewers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those who have read the book, I will post Audible&amp;#39;s blurb below in spoiler marks : &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blurb Spoilers &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;Ryland Grace is the sole survivor on a desperate, last-chance mission - and if he fails, humanity and the Earth itself will perish. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;Except that right now, he doesn&amp;#39;t know that. He can&amp;#39;t even remember his own name, let alone the nature of his assignment or how to complete it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;All he knows is that he&amp;#39;s been asleep for a very, very long time. And he&amp;#39;s just been awakened to find himself millions of miles from home, with nothing but two corpses for company.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;His crewmates dead, his memories fuzzily returning, he realizes that an impossible task now confronts him. Alone on this tiny ship that&amp;#39;s been cobbled together by every government and space agency on the planet and hurled into the depths of space, it&amp;#39;s up to him to conquer an extinction-level threat to our species.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;And thanks to an unexpected ally, he just might have a chance &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My thoughts : &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;I can&amp;#39;t believe how much of the mystery they take out of the book with just these few lines! First off, finding out that he is on a suicide mission, even that he&amp;#39;s in a space ship is a gradual realization; one which makes you wonder if he could be on another planet somewhere instead of on an accelerating space ship. While I assumed he was on a space ship, having some doubt was exciting. Also I can&amp;#39;t believe they mentioned the unexpected ally. It is vague enough to not understand that it&amp;#39;s an alien, but the reveal is done so fantastically. Am I being too picky here? Figuring out all of these things at the slow pace the book feeds them to you was much more enjoyable than knowing even the slightest bit about it.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[仇恨邮件 "Freakonomics]]></title><description><![CDATA[我年轻的时候很喜欢这个播客，所以我终于拿起了一份
这本书。我读了几章，惊讶地发现我无法忍受
它! 在我看来，这些作者就像狂妄自大、想当摇滚明星的人，认为他们
他们认为可以说服你有一个黑白分明的简单答案来解决所有问题。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py0pxf/freakonomics_hate_mail/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py0pxf/freakonomics_hate_mail/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 23:12:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to love the podcast when I was younger, so I finally picked up a copy of the book. I read a few chapters and was surprised to realize I could not stand it! The authors come across to me as cocky, wannabe rock stars who think they can convince you there&amp;#39;s a black and white easy answer to all of society&amp;#39;s issues, that the rest of us were all just too stupid to think of. They act like they are pulling back the curtain and revealing life&amp;#39;s greatest mysteries to you and you&amp;#39;re lucky to be in their all-knowing presence, then proceed to dictate a hastily devised solution with poor supporting evidence. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry, I like to normally post positive reviews, but something about this book just really grinded my gears and I needed a place to vent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么书或作者真正很好地描绘了 "安静的绝望 "的生活？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不需要宏大的设置或情节。它可以是关于一个收银员或CEO
过着平静的绝望的生活。在您看来，哪些书或作者真正抓住了
在你看来是什么？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pxxjao/any_books_or_authors_really_portray_the_life_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pxxjao/any_books_or_authors_really_portray_the_life_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 21:21:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t need grandiose settings or plots. It can be about a cashier or CEO living the life of quiet desperation. What books or authors who really capture that in your opinions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[个人图书馆的意义何在？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我并不是说这个问题不真诚，这是个合理的问题。

我有一个引以为豪的大型个人图书馆，但我的女朋友一直在劝我卖掉它，因为我不需要。
劝我把它卖掉，因为我不需要那些书。而我越是
我就意识到，我没有任何回应。有...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py1hc0/whats_the_point_of_a_personal_library/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py1hc0/whats_the_point_of_a_personal_library/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 20:48:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t mean to be insincere with the question; it&amp;#39;s a legitimate one.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a large personal library I&amp;#39;m quite proud of, but my girlfriend has been urging me to sell it off because I don&amp;#39;t need all those books. And the more I thought about it, I realized I didn&amp;#39;t have a response to that. There&amp;#39;s no real point to holding onto things years after you&amp;#39;ve read them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what&amp;#39;s your take?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[史蒂芬-金的《痛苦》（Misery）一书]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚读完《痛苦》。这是我第一次读恐怖书，而且
也是我读过的第一本斯蒂芬-金的书。而且我绝对喜欢它。它是如此
它写得很好，即使只有两个人物，故事发生在一个地方，但总有一些有趣的事情发生。
故事发生在一个地方，但总有一些有趣的事情......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py0ggr/misery_by_stephen_king/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/py0ggr/misery_by_stephen_king/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 20:21:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading Misery. This was the first time I read a horror book and the first book I ever read by Stephen King. And I absolutely loved it. It is so well-written and even through there are just two characters and the story takes place in one location, something interesting is always happening. There were so many moments when I was literally on the edge of my seat and scared out of my mind. Some of those were when Annie squeezes the life out of the rat, the hobbling scene of course and when she kills the cop. These just sent my heart racing. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Annie Wilkes is horrific and the way her actions, manners and thoughts are described, the way she keeps getting worse and worse gradually, it&amp;#39;s just brilliant. I thought that it was a really interesting choice to tell the readers the story of Annie&amp;#39;s past through Paul reading her Memory Lane book. It added to the horror and tension of the book and made it impossible to stop reading without getting to know the extent of Annie&amp;#39;s horrific past. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was so good. No book has made me feel how this one did and I am looking forward to reading more of Stephen King.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;P. S. The reference to the Overlook hotel was so smooth man.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[还有人用亚马逊Kindle失去了数字内容的权利吗？我前一阵子失去了近50万美元的内容，才发现一个无故障的故障不会让我打开我的书。今天我收到一张图片，是非常昂贵的学者文本，又是刚过5年的--亚马逊的服务条款。]]></title><description><![CDATA[简而言之，亲爱的亚马逊Kindle用户要警惕了。你的电子权利是
只有五年，之后你就没有权利访问他们的书了。

长的故事和你们这些优秀的窥视者的挫败感的兔子洞将是一个
当我试图打开我的书时，我收到的评论中的图像......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxxy4a/anyone_else_with_amazon_kindle_lost_rights_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxxy4a/anyone_else_with_amazon_kindle_lost_rights_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 18:25:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The short story is Dear Amazon Kindle users be wary.  Your electronic rights are only five years and after that you have no right of access to THEIR books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The long story and a rabbit hole of frustration for you fine peeps will be an image in the comments I received when I tried to open my books several months ago.  I don’t mess with my devices and so such messages just seem bizarre.  I’m not sure what I did back then but I’m sure I did a lot of personal trouble shooting including removing devices and reinstalling.  When I exhausted myself I contacted Amazon Customer service both online chat then in person.  This was a long process of jumping through hoops and basically rolling out all possibilities (including what I did) and saying it was my fault for deleting the books.  I can guarantee I never did before seeing the image in the comments.  The image that prevents access to the books.  An image I see again which I have touched NOTHING with any of my devices nor added any new devices.  Nothing has changed except time itself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I got the message for a very expensive scholar book and I have no reason to believe contacting them will come with any different result than last time.  That is unless some of you people have some insight you can give me.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, it would be great if you have insight to prevent these messages.  I sincerely have no idea why they are coming up.  If I am being treated normal then Kindle as business would drop off tremendously.  It is ridiculous.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[下一个泰瑞-普拉特切特]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道在我心里不可能有另一个特里-普拉切特。现在有，将来也会有
的伟大人物，也许，在充分的时间里，甚至可能是伟大的人物，但有
但不可能有第二个普拉切特。每当我拿起一本《碟形世界》的书时，我都会感到一种
知道不会再有任何 "第一次 "了。

德鲁...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxnfwn/the_next_terry_pratchett/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxnfwn/the_next_terry_pratchett/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 14:56:21 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know in my heart there cannot be another Terry Pratchett. There are, and will be, greats and perhaps, in the fullness of time, maybe even greaters but there can never be another Pratchett. Every time I pick up a Discworld book I feel a pang knowing there will not be any more &amp;quot;first times&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drew Hayes is my current favorite for funny sci-fi/fantasy. He carries the torch of Pratchett with his diverse stories and humor woven into every book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;John Scalzi has fun and funny sci-fi with a lot of adventure.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Brandon Sanderson has a few laughs even in his denser works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A. Lee Martinez is probably as silly as Pratchett and has a strong dose of the underdog in his heroes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are lots of fun and funny books out there. But sometimes when I stare into the night sky I like to imagine riding along on the back of great a&amp;#39;tuin one more time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你拥有多少本你还没有读过的书呢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在Instagram上看到一个朋友的帖子，就想知道：你有多少本
你拥有多少本你还没有读完的书？

该帖子说她的书架上有80多本（！）书等待阅读。
这让我开始思考。我目前有8本书还没有读，但其中大部分
这些书中...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxrrau/how_many_books_do_you_own_that_you_havent_read_yet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxrrau/how_many_books_do_you_own_that_you_havent_read_yet/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:42:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have seen a post on Instagram of a friend, and wondered about it: how many books do you own that you havent yet read through?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The post said she had 80-something (!) books on her shelves that are waiting to be read, which got me thinking. I currently have 8 that i havent read, but most of those are from the same series and i bought them as a set. Is it a common thing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你会查看Goodreads的评分和评论来决定是否购买一本书吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[虽然如此，在过去没有互联网的时候，我们习惯于购买同一作者的书。
同一个作者的书，而且一次又一次。现在不需要了，我们可以跳过可疑的
坏书，只读好书。我想知道这种趋势是否
昔日的风气是否仍然盛行。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pxnojm/do_you_check_goodreads_ratings_and_reviews_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pxnojm/do_you_check_goodreads_ratings_and_reviews_to/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 13:00:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Granted that, In the past when there was no internet, we used to buy books from the same author again and again. It&amp;#39;s no longer needed and we can skip dubiously bad books and read only the good ones. Would like to know if this trend of yesteryears is still prevalent.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[首位美国本土桂冠诗人乔伊-哈乔开始第三个任期，发布回忆录]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxs91d/first_native_american_poet_laureate_joy_harjo/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxs91d/first_native_american_poet_laureate_joy_harjo/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 12:27:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么这么多奇幻书是系列而不是独立的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从《指环王》中了解到一个有趣的小故事，它是以单行本的形式写成的。
是一本1000页的书，但由于第二次世界大战和纸张短缺
被分成了三卷，从而成为我们今天所知的三部曲。这让我
思考我读过的多少本奇幻小说都是第一册......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxin5v/why_are_so_many_fantasy_books_a_series_rather/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxin5v/why_are_so_many_fantasy_books_a_series_rather/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 07:17:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;One fun fact of Trivia that I learned from Lord of the rings that it was written as a single 1000 page book but because of World War II and a shortage of paper was split into 3 volumes thus becoming the trilogy we know today.  That got me thinking about how many fantasy books i read that are book one of 3 or 5 or 10.  And sometimes I DNF them because it feels like the story is being padded out and I&amp;#39;m wondering if this is a problem in fantasy, if they would be better off as a single stand alone book (not all of course).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪本书或哪几本书开始了你的痴迷？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我相信，这可能是一个在这里已经被问得很多的问题。
这里。我一直不善于让自己阅读。这来自于某种程度上的
懒惰，但也是因为我从来没有找到一本能让我着迷的书。
我现在21岁了，觉得已经准备好让自己读书了，但我有...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/px63c6/which_book_or_books_started_your_obsession/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/px63c6/which_book_or_books_started_your_obsession/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 06:18:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am sure, that this is, probably, a question that has been asked plenty on here.
I have never been good at making myself read. This came from a somewhat high laziness, but also because I never was able to find a book that hooked me.
I am now 21 and feel ready to get myself into reading, but I have no idea which genre I like or where to start. So, which book or books got you hooked on reading?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否有批评喧嚣文化的书籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[或任何类似的东西。可能有关于过度劳累的社会的话题或主题。
资本主义等。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pxjdas/are_there_any_books_that_criticize_hustle_culture/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pxjdas/are_there_any_books_that_criticize_hustle_culture/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 05:13:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or anything similar. May have topics or themes about overworked societies, capitalism, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[书有时真的感觉像一个朋友，不是吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一生中大部分时间都很孤独，而书籍是我的避难所，比我能想象的还要多。
么多。我不知道如何，尽管我所读的书没有
提供相同的故事，甚至与我的个人包袱相似的故事，但我感到
与书中人物的亲近感。这就像听到一个朋友在谈论...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px1prp/book_really_does_feels_like_a_friend_sometimes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px1prp/book_really_does_feels_like_a_friend_sometimes/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 05:13:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been lonely most of my life, and books have been my refuge, more than I can imagine it would be. I don&amp;#39;t know how, even though the books I&amp;#39;m reading doesn&amp;#39;t offer the same story, or even similar story to my personal baggage, I felt closeness to its characters. It&amp;#39;s like hearing a friend talked deeply about their interesting, more passionate life, and hearing them talked about their sorrow too, feel strangely comforting. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Can anyone more knowledgeable explain why I feel this way? Has anyone feel the same? And what books offer the same feelings as mine to you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阅读的药用价值]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直都是一个贪婪的读者。当我被派往海外时，我有半打书放在行李箱底。
在我的行李袋底部有半打书，回来的时候，我的行李袋底部全部都是
我的鞋柜底部都是书......笑。不过，在我因公受伤后，阅读
变得不仅仅是一种有趣和放松的消遣方式。阅读有了...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxba0o/medicinal_value_of_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxba0o/medicinal_value_of_reading/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 02:13:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have always been a voracious reader.  When I deployed overseas I had a half dozen books in the bottom of my duffel bag, and came back with the entire bottom of my foot locker full…lol.  After I was injured on the job, though, reading became more than just a fun and relaxing pastime.  Reading took on the role of therapy for me.  I have fairly severe nerve damage and chronic pain, that pain meds only go so far to deal with.  I found, though, that getting lost in a good book goes a long way to getting me out of my head for awhile and makes the pain ease up a lot better than watching TV or most anything else does.  Has anyone else used reading as medicine as well as enjoyment?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[过去/童年的自己会如何看待现在的阅读习惯？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在想，自从我开始喜欢看书以来，我对书的品味发生了什么变化？
喜欢上它们。

如果我知道我10岁时的自己在26岁时还在自愿阅读并喜欢我所选择的许多书籍，我一定会大吃一惊。
今天，我自愿阅读并喜欢我选择的许多书。在那个年纪，我认为
只有无聊的老顽童才会读经典，和非小说类的书......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxbpf1/what_would_your_pastchildhood_self_think_of_your/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxbpf1/what_would_your_pastchildhood_self_think_of_your/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 00:31:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was thinking about how my taste in books has changed ever since I started enjoying them.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My 10-year-old self would be flabbergasted to know that, at age 26, I am voluntarily reading and &lt;em&gt;enjoying&lt;/em&gt; many of my choices today. At that age I thought only boring old geezers read Classics, and Non-Fiction was for stiff nerds with no imagination. Hell, I now occasionally pick up books on History, my most-loathed subject as a kid.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They’d also be disappointed with how little I care for Harry Potter now. I used to make it my personality, and had “must have read Harry Potter” near the top of my romantic partner requirements list lol. Jesus Christ.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, I think my teenage self would be impressed. I’ve challenged myself a lot to expand outside my comfort zone and read more difficult books. I am also much more secure &amp;amp; confident about reading whatever the hell I want &amp;amp; not caring if my Goodreads friends see me reading some “embarrassing” books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[菲利帕-格雷戈里既不是女权主义者、历史学家，也不是好作家]]></title><description><![CDATA[--尽管她喜欢称自己为三者。说实话，我从她的书中得到的是
说实话，我从她的书中得到的所有信息是：女人互相憎恨，女人的动机几乎完全是为了激情的浪漫，女人要么是贱货，要么是处女的缩影。
激情的浪漫，而女人要么是贱货，要么是处女的缩影。
善良的缩影（后者是中世纪的一种构造）。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px2k7s/philippa_gregory_is_neither_feminist_historian_or/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px2k7s/philippa_gregory_is_neither_feminist_historian_or/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 21:42:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;--even though she likes to call herself all three. Honestly, all I got from her books was that women hate each other, women are motivated almost solely by passionate romance, and women are either bitchy shrews or epitomes of virginal goodness (the latter being a construct right out of medieval times.) She even went on a BBC documentary (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p015vhp1&quot;&gt;https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p015vhp1&lt;/a&gt;) to repeat her &lt;em&gt;The Other Boleyn Girl&lt;/em&gt; assertion that Anne Boleyn tried to have sex with her brother, because she was &amp;quot;ambitious and ruthless enough for me to believe it&amp;quot; (one of many gendered double-standards that this Feminist™ seems to embrace without any sense of irony). A little bit of dramatization or creative filling-in of gaps in the historical record are permissible, but not when the author takes it up to an 11 and perpetuates sexist and historically reductionist narratives, all while repeatedly claiming the mantle of scholarly legitimacy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a pity that all her novels are being popularized in adaptations (White Princess, Spanish Princess, etc.) that are somehow even worse. At least the novel didn&amp;#39;t depict a fully-pregnant Catherine of Aragon doing something as stupid and reckless as charging straight into hand-to-hand combat with the Scots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我买了一本Grosset & Dunlap的Oliver Twist，以为自己买到了一个老版本，结果发现自己陷入了盗版书的历史。]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近，我买了一本由Grosset & Dunlap出版的二手《奥利弗-托斯特》，因为我喜欢精装版的设计。
因为我喜欢它的精装设计。我以为我买到了一个漂亮的特别版
当我看到推定的第一任主人的书面名字和日期
1928. 然后翻开书页，我看到封面上有一张照片......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px5qhw/got_my_hands_on_a_grosset_dunlap_oliver_twist/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px5qhw/got_my_hands_on_a_grosset_dunlap_oliver_twist/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 20:34:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently, I bought a secondhand Oliver Twist published by Grosset &amp;amp; Dunlap because I liked the hardcover design. I thought I scored a beautiful special edition when I saw the written name of the presumed first owner with the date 1928. Then turning the pages, I saw the frontispiece with a photograph from The Liebler Company cast, performing Oliver Twist in 1912. All throughout the book are charming black and white photographs of the cast from the play. This particular edition, as the publisher explained in the following page, was published because the play was so successful and because of Charles Dicken&amp;#39;s 100th birth anniversary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Curiosity piqued, I tried to find the copyright page but found none. Thinking it was ripped off, I tried searching online and ended up reading the history of Grosset &amp;amp; Dunlap. Turns out, they used to re-bind books, turning paperbacks into hardcovers. They also pirated and reprinted books, causing confusion when people thought they bought first edition book but was actually reprinted or mistaking a first edition book for a reprint. D&amp;amp;G did print original books, with Hardy Boys and Nancy Drew as the most notable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While reading this, I assumed that my copy of Oliver Twist is a re-bind and tried looking for the original imprint/publisher. But apparently, Grosset &amp;amp; Dunlap was also historically known for their photoplay editions, like a movie-tie in but with stills from the play or film. Very sought after by collectors. So my copy of Oliver Twist may not be pirated or a re-bind, at least.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grosset &amp;amp; Dunlap&amp;#39;s history was a fascinating read. It also brought me new knowledge about books in general. Lately, my run-ins with pirated books are usually illegal e-books, or cheaply printed copies when trying to buy online. I&amp;#39;ve never had an ounce of thought about [the history of] book piracy beyond blurred PDFs passed around thru emails, download links found in NSFW Tumblr posts, and  the badly-kept secret book groups on the internet lol&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, Grosset &amp;amp; Dunlap are now under Penguin Group.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TikTok的阅读复兴正在使旧书成为畅销品]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxbnbb/tiktoks_reading_renaissance_is_making_old_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pxbnbb/tiktoks_reading_renaissance_is_making_old_books/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 19:20:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是否误解了阿尔伯特-加缪的《异乡人》？]]></title><description><![CDATA[读完这本书后，我感到很困惑。默尔索这个人物
体现了荒诞主义的理想，也是加缪的许多哲学信仰的代言人。
哲学信仰的代言人。然而，我是否应该因此而宽恕他，并对他感到
尽管他犯了不道德的罪行，我是否应该原谅他，并对他产生怜悯之情？难道道德没有任何...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px7mue/am_i_misunderstanding_the_stranger_by_albert_camus/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px7mue/am_i_misunderstanding_the_stranger_by_albert_camus/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 17:17:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was left feeling confused after reading the book. Meursault is a character that embodies absurdist ideals, and is Camus&amp;#39; mouthpiece for many of his philosophical beliefs. However, am I supposed to therefore pardon him and feel pity for him in spite of his immoral crimes? Does morality not hold any meaning to Meursault and am I supposed to be ok with his murders or his help to Raymond? Am I missing something? It seems to me that the book is giving license to immorality, under the banner of nihilism. It is as though Camus is saying that since life is meaningless, therefore moral codes can be forsaken.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[像 "Sapiens "和 "A short history of nearly everything "这样的书--也许还有更多基于动物的书。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我读过尤瓦尔-诺亚-哈拉里的其他作品，也很不错。有哪些
其他的一些书？我对任何与人类或其他动物有关的东西都感兴趣。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/px2a9c/books_like_sapiens_and_a_short_history_of_nearly/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/px2a9c/books_like_sapiens_and_a_short_history_of_nearly/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:52:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve read the other ones by Yuval Noah Harari which were also great. What are some other ones? I&amp;#39;m interested in anything to do with humans or other animals&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你如何看待那些故意对读者隐瞒主要/观察员角色拥有的信息的书籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我说的不是推理书，即侦探试图破案和收集信息的地方。
收集信息。

我说的是那些推动行动的书籍，这些书籍以一个问题为开端，即
角色从一开始就知道的问题，但只有在结尾时才会向读者透露。
读者在最后才发现，通常是在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px68wi/how_do_you_feel_about_books_that_purposefully/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/px68wi/how_do_you_feel_about_books_that_purposefully/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 16:52:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not talking about mystery books, where a detective tries to solve a case and gather information. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m talking about books where the driving action kicks off with an issue that was known by the characters from the start, but which are only revealed to the readers at the end, usually at the climax. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, in &lt;em&gt;The God of Small Things&lt;/em&gt; by Arundhati Roy, the entire book deals with what happened to two siblings during their childhood to make to make one of them damaged as an adult. I absolutely loved that book, and it was amazing every page. I don&amp;#39;t remember being frustrated by the hidden knowledge. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, I just started &lt;em&gt;Lake of the Woods&lt;/em&gt; by Tim O&amp;#39;Brien. This is not really a spoiler, since it happens in the first ten pages - the &amp;quot;plot&amp;quot; starts off when someone writes a hit piece that tanks the main character&amp;#39;s political ambitions. I&amp;#39;m about 60 pages in, and it is becoming more clear that the book is going to jump around the hit piece for the rest of the book, likely without revealing its contents until the end. It&amp;#39;s already making me frustrated because I just want to know. Maybe my patience has gotten worse since reading &lt;em&gt;The God of Small Things.&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I was just interested in seeing what others thought. It&amp;#39;s a framing device that I could see leading to reader frustration, as the only reason for the mystery is an intentional plot device by the author. There is no built in explanation for why the reader wouldn&amp;#39;t know it. But, in the right hands, it can be a wonderful framing device that sucks you in and makes you feel like you are learning a forbidden secret that the characters won&amp;#39;t even acknowledge to themselves.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想感谢译者的辛勤工作]]></title><description><![CDATA[我来自一个几乎没有以我的母语出版的书籍的国家。
我对那些明显热爱原著的译者感到高兴。
他们的工作，特别是因为我主要是用英语阅读，以方便
读取材料。有时，这甚至会增加书的质量。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pww6nz/i_wanna_thank_translator_for_their_hard_work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pww6nz/i_wanna_thank_translator_for_their_hard_work/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 13:26:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Being from a country with little to no published books in my native language it makes me happy with translators that are clearly in love with the original book they are working on, specially because I mostly read in english for the ease of access of material. Sometimes it even adds up quality to the original book, specially when it was written in far different written system and specific cultures. Translator notes can add quite a bit of context that sometimes can&amp;#39;t be expressed through the use of english that would be lost to some readers. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It comes to mind good translations of Arabian Nights(the translations from multiple arabic sources, not the french one that was spread around here in south america). I can&amp;#39;t begin to imagine how life was around north africa and middle east in 2021, let alone hundreds of years ago. Context adds up so much value in such stories that it blows my mind. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also with languages that deviates from mine (I speak tupi[a native south american language], portuguese and english) so much that a direct translation proves itself almost impossible. Japanese is a good exemple of translation that requires lots of context because of its framework, so I am always pleased to read the implication of the use of kanji in setences.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the long post, I&amp;#39;m just an indigenous Brazilian trying to learn about other cultures.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;tldr; we should value good translations and translators are MVPs&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[围绕书籍的把关是如此翻天覆地的令人厌恶。读书社区通常是相当健康的，但似乎把关是一个太经常出现的问题。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我们都见过它。

"如果你没有读过（插入任何一本书，通常是经典之作（或甚至是作家）），你就不是一个真正的书迷！
你就不是一个真正的书迷！"

"如果你读过（插入流派，通常是青年或浪漫），你就不是一个真正的书迷
书）！")

"（插入类型，同样通常是青年或浪漫）是糟糕的，如果你读它，你就不是一个
不是一个...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwv51a/the_gatekeeping_around_books_is_so_flipping/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwv51a/the_gatekeeping_around_books_is_so_flipping/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 07:42:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;#39;ve all seen it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;If you haven&amp;#39;t read (insert any book, usually a classic (or even an author)) you&amp;#39;re not a real book fan!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;If you read (insert genre, usually YA or romance), you&amp;#39;re not a real fan of books)!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;(Insert genre, again usually YA or romance) is BAD and if you read it, you&amp;#39;re not a real fan of reading!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It grinds me gears. Even while on my 5 year hiatus from reading, I saw it. Because it&amp;#39;s way too common. Now that I&amp;#39;m getting back into it, I just see it too often. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Usually not stated as outright opinions, but reflected in insults or passive aggressiveness towards a genre/book/author and the people who read them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I guess the moral here is to please try to understand that books are for everyone, it&amp;#39;s not your place or authority to decide who is a &amp;quot;fan&amp;quot; or not. Just try to be less judgemental. But not just for books, for everything. Movies, games, food, careers, hobbies, fashion, etc. It doesn&amp;#39;t hurt you if a 35yo is using this Reddit and all they read is dystopian YA. I promise you&amp;#39;ll sleep better at night not worrying about these kinds of things.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: I&amp;#39;m pasting this response to a comment I received. It&amp;#39;s in regards to my motivation to making this post and I think it&amp;#39;s relevant. I wish I had included this in the post to begin with&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As far as saying it&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;my issue&amp;quot;, I get what you&amp;#39;re saying, but that&amp;#39;s not why I made the post. My overall moral of the post of not being judgemental (not limited to books) is one I think is important. Because people hating that I like a certain book or movie or whatever? I couldn&amp;#39;t care less. But gatekeeping mentalities do make their way into power. Whether it&amp;#39;s political or a workplace or even a Reddit community. And it&amp;#39;s on those places where voices are silenced and people are hurt in very real ways. Encouraging people to be more open minded is something worth investing in, imo of course. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also don&amp;#39;t live for other people. I couldn&amp;#39;t give less of a f*** what people think of how I dress, eat, live, read, game, etc. I do me, very unabashedly might I add. The reasons above are why I made the post. Not because I let myself be pushed and pulled by other&amp;#39;s onions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[把书作为礼物送给婴儿可以吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我并不是真正在婴儿身边长大的，我的家庭很小。但是现在我的
我的姻亲兄弟姐妹有了一个新的女婴，尽管住得很远，但我想成为一个很酷的孩子。
我想成为一个送书的酷阿姨。作为父母，在你的孩子出生后收到一本书作为礼物，是不是很烦人呢？
作为父母，在孩子不识字的情况下送书作为礼物是不是很烦？这是一本图片...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwpcbl/is_it_okay_to_give_an_infant_a_book_as_a_gift/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwpcbl/is_it_okay_to_give_an_infant_a_book_as_a_gift/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 22:22:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I did not really grow up around babies, my family was pretty small. But now my sib-in-laws by marriage have a new baby girl and despite living far away from them I want to be the cool aunt that sends books. Is it annoying as a parent to get a book as a gift when your child can&amp;#39;t read? It&amp;#39;s a picture book so she&amp;#39;ll grow into it soon, maybe I&amp;#39;m overthinking it? For what it&amp;#39;s worth I&amp;#39;m sending the mom a practical gift too but this book is specifically for the baby.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[u/goodreads-bot回来了!]]></title><description><![CDATA[对不起，各位。谷歌云关闭了这个机器人，因为他们的一个计费错误。
终端。我今天让机器人再次启动。对于暂时的中断，我很抱歉。我没有
才意识到!

u/goodreads [/u/goodreads] 机器人又活了一天!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pwo40w/ugoodreadsbot_is_back/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pwo40w/ugoodreadsbot_is_back/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 21:19:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry everyone. Google Cloud shut down the bot due to a billing error on their end. I got the bot started again today. Sorry for the temporary outage. I didn&amp;#39;t realize until today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/u/goodreads&quot;&gt;u/goodreads&lt;/a&gt; bot lives to see another day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[买家要小心。亚马逊正在用纸袋装运书籍，以防止运输中的损坏。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我等了一个星期才等到这套盒装书，却发现亚马逊把它装在一个没有包装的纸袋里。
纸袋里，没有包装，所以它在运输过程中被打了。

https://i.imgur.com/6tuARNK.jpeg

盒装的8个角都被损坏了，还有两个角也被损坏了。
外的书的角。我已经有了一个退货和更换...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwnjkp/buyer_beware_amazon_is_shipping_books_in_paper/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwnjkp/buyer_beware_amazon_is_shipping_books_in_paper/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 20:19:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I waited a week for this boxed set to arrive, only to find Amazon sent it in a paper bag with no packing so it got beat up in transit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/6tuARNK.jpeg&quot;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/6tuARNK.jpeg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All 8 corners of the boxed set are damaged along with the corners of the two outside books. I already have a return &amp;amp; replacement on the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the 2nd delivery in a week that&amp;#39;s shown up, beat to hell, in a paper envelope. I usually try to check for local business options, guess I&amp;#39;ll be ordering even less from Amazon if this is their new quality of shipping.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是M.L.Rio，《如果我们是恶棍》的作者和五个不同的穿风衣的书呆子。AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一名作家和演员，后来转为学者。我在大学时写了一本小说，不知怎么就卖掉了。
然后搬到英国，在伦敦国王学院和环球剧场获得了莎士比亚的硕士学位。
伦敦国王学院和环球剧院获得莎士比亚硕士学位。现在我回到了美国，IWWV已经出版。
以七种语言出版，并将推出特别精装本......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwiwsq/im_m_l_rio_author_of_if_we_were_villains_and_five/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwiwsq/im_m_l_rio_author_of_if_we_were_villains_and_five/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 19:17:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m an author and actor-turned-academic. I wrote a novel in college, somehow sold it, then moved to England to get a master’s degree in Shakespeare at King’s College London and the Globe. Now I’m back in the States, IWWV has been published in seven languages, and is coming out in a special hardback edition next month from Titan Books. I’m also a PhD candidate writing a dissertation on madness and mood disorder in early modern drama. Bom-bard me with curiosity (ban puns guaranteed).
Ocular proof: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/p/CULaTj6rQ1Q/&quot;&gt;https://www.instagram.com/p/CULaTj6rQ1Q/&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SureAsMel/status/1441145538221539330?s=20&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/SureAsMel/status/1441145538221539330?s=20&lt;/a&gt;
Find me on
Instagram: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.instagram.com/sureasmel/&quot;&gt;https://www.instagram.com/sureasmel/&lt;/a&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/SureAsMel&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/SureAsMel&lt;/a&gt;
My website: &lt;a href=&quot;https://mlrio.com/&quot;&gt;https://mlrio.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have to run, but thanks so much to everyone who participated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我对阅读有关葬礼和死亡仪式的社会学/人类学书籍感兴趣]]></title><description><![CDATA[最好是跨文化的，但不一定是这样。我更感兴趣的是
不同文化背景下的人们如何纪念他们心爱的死者]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pwdysx/im_interested_in_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pwdysx/im_interested_in_reading/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 18:46:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preferably across cultures, but it doesn’t have to be. I’m more interested in how people from different cultures honour their beloved dead&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[他认为，最好的书是那些告诉你你已经知道的东西。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我们开始之前，先提出公平的警告（因为这么多人对这个帖子有意见？
帖）。) 这是我第一次在这个网站上发帖。

在我看来，上面这句话完美地概括了《1984》成为经典的原因。这本书
这本书是漫画和现实的完美结合。当你开始阅读这本书时
你会想...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwg4rr/the_best_books_he_perceived_are_those_that_tell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwg4rr/the_best_books_he_perceived_are_those_that_tell/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 15:23:23 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fair warning before we start (since so many people have a problem with this post?): This is my first ever post on this site.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In my opinion, the above quote perfectly summarises why 1984 is a classic. The book is a perfect blend between caricature and reality. When you start this book you think to yourself: &lt;em&gt;This is a dystopian future we will never experience. Things will never be&lt;/em&gt; that &lt;em&gt;bad, right?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once you read Goldstein&amp;#39;s book, however, things start making a lot more sense and dread starts filling the reader&amp;#39;s mind. &lt;em&gt;This sounds like a magnified version of what the XYZ government is doing to the masses.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that is where the genius of Orwell and 1984 lies; in the identification of the role of media and indoctrination in totalitarian control over the masses so early on into the introduction of media into the society.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The book fascinated him, or more exactly it reassured him. In a sense it told him nothing that was new, but that was part of the attraction. It said what he would have said, if it had been possible for him to set his scattered thoughts in order. It was the product of a mind similar to his own. The best books, he perceived, are those that tell you what you know already.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One thing I have always believed in is that for as long as civilisations exist, there &lt;em&gt;will&lt;/em&gt; exist a medium, a tool, that will have the ability to control the minds of the masses. It is rather scary and at times (more often than not) this tool is used for bad rather than good, in a spread of misinformation rather than awareness. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Media will always be present, power will always reside with someone. The one thing we can do is understand the media and how the powerful make use of it to manipulate us.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[利比图书馆卡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我住在东南亚，非常想使用Libby，但我当地的图书馆提供的目录很小，而国外的很多图书馆有更多的书，我不知道该怎么办。
但我当地的图书馆提供的目录很小，而国外的很多图书馆有更多我感兴趣的书。
有兴趣读的书。有什么办法可以让我使用免费的国外图书馆卡吗？
卡？(我没钱，还是个学生)我可以用别人的图书馆卡吗？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwg7iv/libby_library_cards/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwg7iv/libby_library_cards/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 14:59:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I live in Southeast Asia and so desperately want to use Libby but my local library offers a small catalog and a lot of libraries abroad have more books I’m interested in reading. Is there a way I can use a &lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt; out of country library card? (im broke and still a student) Can I use someone else’s library card? And if there any other suggestions, do let me know!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sincerely, a broke student wanting to read more after a 5 year hiatus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[简-奥斯汀的书真的值得吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[现在，我从来没有注意到这一点，但我在浏览我的图书馆，我拥有的大多数书籍
我拥有的大部分书籍要么是高度幻想，要么是硬科幻，要么是沉重的非虚构作品和哲学。
600多页的陀思妥耶夫斯基和托尔斯泰的书。我不能相信我从来没有得到
任何东西来放松和休闲。所以简-奥斯汀的书会做...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwc8wb/are_jane_austen_books_really_worth_it/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pwc8wb/are_jane_austen_books_really_worth_it/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 12:36:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, I&amp;#39;ve never noticed this but I was browsing my library and most of the books I own are either high fantasy, hard scifi, heavy non-fictions and philosophies, 600+ pages of Dostoyevsky and Tolstoy books. I can&amp;#39;t believe I never got anything to just unwind and relax. So will Jane Austen books do that for me? Any other recommendations?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阅读《呼啸山庄》迫使我从一个很高的地方跳下来]]></title><description><![CDATA[难道只有我一个人不认为这本书是一个令人难以忍受的500多页长的
窥探和流言蜚语？不要误会我的意思，我喜欢经典，尤其是勃朗特姐妹的作品。
经典作品，尤其是勃朗特姐妹的作品。艾米莉-勃朗特的作品比她姐姐的很多作品都要出色。
她姐姐的很多作品，她的写作风格。

但这是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pw8wdz/reading_wuthering_heights_compelled_me_to_jump/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pw8wdz/reading_wuthering_heights_compelled_me_to_jump/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 07:20:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Am I the only one who does not see this book as the insufferable 500+ pages long snooping around and piece of gossip it is???!!! Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong I love the Classics, and especially the Bronte sister&amp;#39;s works. Emily Bronte has outshined a lot of her sister&amp;#39;s works with her writing style.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it is NOT a love story and I have no idea how and why Wuthering Heights makes it to every blog listing of books to read before you die!!!
Perhaps it is to push an already suicidal reader over the edge?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我需要更多的书]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以我现在处于阅读的低潮期，我需要一些书，马上。我最喜欢的类型是
历史小说和奇幻小说。我最喜欢的一些书是《轰隆隆》（The Boom
小偷》，《哈利-波特》系列，《最后的绿谷》，以及《饥饿游戏》系列。
我喜欢青春期的幻想，特别是歇斯底里的幻想。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pw6ene/i_need_more_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pw6ene/i_need_more_books/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 05:54:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I’m in a reading slump  and I need some books pronto. My favorite genres are historical fiction and fantasy. Some of my favorite books ever are The Boom Thief, Harry Potter series, The Last Green Valley, and the Hunger Games series. I LOVE YA fantasy, especially dystopian.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阅读阿加莎-克里斯蒂]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，我是阿莱克斯。今年夏天，我读了阿加莎-克里斯蒂的《后来没有了》。
它真的吸引了我，文笔很好，很容易理解。一些神秘的
书真的很混乱，一旦你读完了，你就不太明白
作者是如何解开谜团的，而不需要重新审视......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pw1hr2/reading_agatha_christie/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pw1hr2/reading_agatha_christie/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 01:08:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;#39;m Aleks. This summer I read  &amp;quot;And then there were none&amp;quot; by Agatha Christie. It really captivated me, the writing was great and easy to follow. Some mystery books are really confusing and once you finish them you don&amp;#39;t really understand how the author solved the mystery without revisiting previous pages but this didn&amp;#39;t happen to me with this book. Since I&amp;#39;m a really indecisive reader, I can&amp;#39;t pick a book for the life of me and I love mystery books I decided to start a little challenge. I decided to read every Agatha Christie novel, I found a blog that recommended a specific order to read the books and that&amp;#39;s what I&amp;#39;m following. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far I&amp;#39;ve read 7 books and I thought I&amp;#39;d share my thoughts about the books on here. I&amp;#39;ve always been a bit shy to share my opinions on different forms of media in case I missed some big point or didn&amp;#39;t understand something in the plot but I think this could be a great start. Also english is not my first language so excuse me if something is not clear enough or if my opinions are not perfectly articulated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since I&amp;#39;ve already read 5 books from the Hercule Poirot series I&amp;#39;m going to quickly sum up my thoughts on them in this post and from now on I&amp;#39;ll be writing an individual post for each book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mysterious Affair at Styles: 
I really enjoyed this one. I think it&amp;#39;s a great introduction to Poirot and Hastings and their dynamic together. Hercule unravels the mystery while Hastings guides you through it, trying to help his friend without, what it seems, much success. Though I enjoyed this book, I&amp;#39;m used to plot twists and thinking that nothing is what it seems in these kind of books so I kind of guessed who the murderer was before the big reveal but still it was worth the read. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The murder on the links: 
Now on the second book I&amp;#39;m already developing a love-annoyance relationship with Hastings. I don&amp;#39;t know if the whole point is making Poirot look even greater than he is or what but Hastings seems like the really dumb friend you add to spice up the main character. Still there are moments when I like him and think he makes the reading lighter. I liked this book less than the first one because of some questionable plot involving Hastings that made me mad. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poirot Investigates: 
I adored this book. It&amp;#39;s a collection of Poirot cases, they&amp;#39;re not long but each of them is interesting in their own way. I loved the fact that I read a &amp;quot;short&amp;quot; story but it felt like I read a whole novel in 15-20 minutes. But oh Hastings... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Big Four: 
This is probably my least favorite so far. Though I enjoy a good conspiracy theory, especially if it involves an organization that&amp;#39;s trying to control the world, I found it way too surreal and fantastic. Hastings seems a bit smarter in this one (in some points, in other he&amp;#39;s the same old dumb Hastings) but he still doesn&amp;#39;t know nor follow Poirot&amp;#39;s methods. Don&amp;#39;t tell anyone but in my mind Poirot and Hastings are really good friends... &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The murder of Roger Ackroyd: 
Hastings left and doctor Sheppard takes his place. I started this book knowing there was a big plot twist and having read &amp;quot;And there were none&amp;quot; before this one I guessed who was guilty halfway through it. Still I wasn&amp;#39;t disappointed. Agatha Christie had the ability to give you the whole case, every detail (even maps of the houses!!!) and you&amp;#39;d still be reading without realizing the small mistake committed by the killer. When you finish this book and Poirot finally points out what YOU missed you can&amp;#39;t help but chuckle. I guess what&amp;#39;s missing is the magnificence of Poirot&amp;#39;s &amp;quot;grey cells&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a general opinion, I like Poirot, he&amp;#39;s a realistic detective when it comes to his nature and though his lack of modesty might be a bit annoying sometimes I find it funny. Christie created a really unique and interesting character with him, I&amp;#39;d love to read a book where he&amp;#39;s the narrator. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I&amp;#39;ll end up being annoying with these posts because there are A LOT of books to read but if anyone follows this journey and reads the reviews just know that you&amp;#39;re amazing I love you &amp;lt;3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么事情会让你无论如何也要把一本书弄成DNF呢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[对我来说，是写作风格。我可以不看那种沉闷的或只是普通的邪恶的
角色、有足够漏洞的情节，以及懒惰的对话和互动。
互动。性爱场面让我恼火，但从未达到让我停止阅读的程度。
但是，如果写作风格不符合我的要求，我就会把它关掉。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvy9ib/what_is_the_one_thing_that_will_get_you_to_dnf_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvy9ib/what_is_the_one_thing_that_will_get_you_to_dnf_a/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 20:22:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For me, it&amp;#39;s the writing style. I can look past sort of dull or just plain evil characters, plots with enough holes to use as a fishnet, and lazy dialogue and interactions. Sex scenes irritate me, but never enough to make me stop reading. But if the writing style doesn&amp;#39;t click with me, I DNF that book so fast that I don&amp;#39;t know if it even counts as a DNF. My record was 10 pages in before I gave up because that particular author changed from past to present to past tense without warning, with no page breaks, and with the same character narrating everything, so time flow was super confusing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寻找一个摄政时代的浪漫故事，其中性和/或性吸引并不发挥主要作用。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好! 我读过简-奥斯汀的大部分作品，我认为它们绝对是
(我知道，这是一个惊喜 :D)，所以我一直在寻找一些
类似的东西。关于简-奥斯汀，我最喜欢的一点是，她的书是
不可否认的是，她的书是浪漫小说，但仍然不是性爱的。奥斯汀...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pvs8qd/looking_for_a_regency_era_romance_where_sex_andor/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pvs8qd/looking_for_a_regency_era_romance_where_sex_andor/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:22:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey all! I&amp;#39;ve read most of Jane Austen&amp;#39;s works and I think them absolutely brilliant (what a surprise, I know :D), so I&amp;#39;ve been looking for something similar. One of my favourite things about Jane Austen is that her books are undeniably romance novels, but still, they are not sex-obsessed. Austen remarks on the appearance of pretty much everybody, but they are aesthetic or factual remarks, not horny/overwhelmed with sexual attraction ones. I&amp;#39;m tired of horny people, and I am tired of reading about horny people. I have tried writers like Georgette Heyer and Julia Quinn but they did not quite hit the mark. But, I am definitely ready to try them again since I haven&amp;#39;t read all of their books (or gotten past the first few chapters) and there might be some of them which fit the bill. I&amp;#39;ve also checked out quite a few of goodreads/similiar recommended book lists, but most/all of the book covers have half-naked people, or the blurb/reviews have things like &amp;quot;instant sexual attraction&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;a scandalous night led to...&amp;quot;, which uh, hasn&amp;#39;t convinced me to try those books out. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To sum up- set in the regency era, main focus is romance/romance is a very important factor in the story, there is no sex, there are no characters being overwhelmed with sexual attraction, characters do not constantly think about sex/have sex dreams/hump pillows while smelling handkerchiefs that the other gave them, there are no heaving bosoms or straining breeches, no one is unbearably horny, sex is not a component of romance. Preferably no sexual tension at all, but I&amp;#39;m fine with tasteful sexual tension, for example &amp;quot;his hand clasped hers during the dance, and while she had danced a hundred such dances in her life, and had had her hand clasped a hundred times, it was different with Mr. Such-and-such&amp;quot; and that&amp;#39;s it, that&amp;#39;s where it stops. It does not continue with a heaving bosom. Wow this ended up the longest summary ever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TLDR; regency era romance, no sex, no one is horny!!!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[谢谢你关于《阿基里斯之歌》的无尽帖子]]></title><description><![CDATA[在过去两年中，我在这个分论坛上无数次看到这本书被提及和讨论。
在过去的两年中，我加入了这个分论坛，并最终有机会阅读它。
基于它所获得的赞誉，我对它寄予厚望，认为它将是一部了不起的作品
在过去的一年里，我一直希望能有机地找到它，要么...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvvdgp/thank_you_for_the_endless_posts_about_the_song_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvvdgp/thank_you_for_the_endless_posts_about_the_song_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:22:41 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve seen this book mentioned and discussed on this subreddit countless times over the last 2 years since I’ve joined and finally got a chance to read it. Based on the acclaim it received, I had high hopes it was going to be remarkable and for the last year I was hoping to find it organically either at a thrift store or in a lend-a-library, but when I saw it discounted at Costco I caved and bought it anyway. 
I couldn’t put it down and once I finished, had to sit with myself for a while to fully appreciate the beauty of what I just read. Never a dull page, incredibly written and I’m already wondering when I’ll read it again. Thank you all who posted and suggested it, I’ve read 25 books this year and The Song of Achilles just became my favorite.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[世界上最稀有的书籍现在通过梵蒂冈的使徒图书馆展出]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvufnn/the_worlds_rarest_books_now_on_display_through/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvufnn/the_worlds_rarest_books_now_on_display_through/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:41:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么我不能理解我读的任何书]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我在阅读一本书时，我发现我必须将文本翻阅数遍
来理解文本的内容，但即使如此，我仍然不清楚书中提到的是什么。
书中所提到的内容。我一般被认为是个聪明人。
然而，我在阅读理解方面一直有问题。它是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvqnk9/why_cant_i_comprehend_any_book_i_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvqnk9/why_cant_i_comprehend_any_book_i_read/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:57:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I am reading a book, I find that I have to go over the text several times to understand what the text is saying, but even then it still isn&amp;#39;t clear what is being mentioned in the book. I am generally considered a smart person, however I have always had issues with reading comprehension. It is the same way for me when I am given an audiobook. I do not know what is going on most of the time. The only book that I somehow ever managed to make it through was House of Leaves bY Mark Z Danielewski, so I am capable of it, i am sure. I have no issues understanding and comprehending text in other situations, because I text my friends all the time and am able to understand them. I also write a lot and have written a short story of 40,000 words. However, even Harry Potter seems impossible and daunting to get through. I just do not understand what is happening, even with an audiobook. This issue seems to be affectIng me in other areas, especially schoolwork where I am learning subjects such as biology which are very text-heavy. If anyone has any ideas what Is going on in my brain, let me know. Or at least please give me leads to someone who might.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is just frustrating because I know people that can easily go through a book a day and it comes as naturally to them as simply writing. 
It would help me immensely.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在中断了五年之后，刚刚重新开始阅读。这个月我已经读完了四本书。不敢相信我在高中毕业后曾停止阅读。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的待读清单也已经有47本书了。我认为阅读真的有助于
我的心理健康。我还开始了创意写作，也是为了好玩。我希望
我几年前就开始了。

题外话：今天有人告诉我，斯蒂芬-金的《它》这本书很糟糕，因为
它的电影也很糟糕。但她...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvmytl/just_got_back_into_reading_after_a_five_year/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pvmytl/just_got_back_into_reading_after_a_five_year/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 07:22:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My to-read list is also 47 books long already. I think reading has really helped my mental health. I also started creative writing for the fun of it too. I wish I had started years ago.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: someone told me today that Stephen King&amp;#39;s It the book was bad because It the movie was bad. But she hadn&amp;#39;t read it and I was like ?????? God I love that book though. Gotta get myself a nice hardback for it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading my incoherent post.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>