<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 04:35:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[工作使我无法阅读]]></title><description><![CDATA[我早上7点起床，下午6点回家--我有一份工作，我不能在工作中阅读。
工作。一旦我回到家，我就会从工作中放松半小时，但随后要做的是
做饭/打扫卫生、运动/训练--洗澡--准备第二天的东西--洗衣--吃饭等等。
第二天--洗衣服--吃饭等等。这给我留下了大约一...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ov49qz/work_keeps_me_from_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ov49qz/work_keeps_me_from_reading/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 19:33:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I get up at 7 AM I return home at 6 PM - I have a job where I cannot read at work. Once I return home I relax from work for half an hour but then have to do some cooking/cleaning some sports/training - showering - preparing stuff for the next day - laundry - dinner ect. This leaves me around one hour in the evening where I can read before I have to go to sleep. And I dont even watch TV. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sometimes I have even less time in the evening because I have to buy some groceries on the way home, meet with a friend, repair stuff, call friends/family ect &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Yet I hear from some people that they come home - drop everything and read for like 4-5 hours every evening before going to sleep. Like when do you do all the other stuff? I have to do most of the housework mentioned above or my apprtment would be a total mess. I &amp;quot;have to&amp;quot; meet up/keep in touch with family/friends or I would be a total loner. I simply cannot fathom to read for several hours after work because then I would have no time left for anything else and my life would be a total mess.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[特里-普拉切特爵士的女儿驳斥了 "可怕 "的说法，即如果作者在世，他将是一个变性人。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ovbni3/sir_terry_pratchetts_daughter_shuts_down/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ovbni3/sir_terry_pratchetts_daughter_shuts_down/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 18:51:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寻找一本书，感觉就像一个孤独的、下雨的、内省的、深夜开车穿过高速公路的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在寻找一本美丽、大气、沉浸式、个人化的书。
真正让你思考。美丽的散文，美丽的图像，美丽的独白，美丽的叙述者和故事。
美丽的独白，美丽的叙述者和人物。有一些东西，只是有那些
章节和段落，使你想合上书，......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ov69yr/looking_for_a_book_that_feels_like_a_lonely_rainy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ov69yr/looking_for_a_book_that_feels_like_a_lonely_rainy/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:13:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for a book that&amp;#39;s beautiful, atmospheric, immersive, personal, and that really makes you think. Beautiful prose, beautiful imagery, beautiful monologues, beautiful narrator and characters. Something that just has those chapters and those passages that make you want to close the book, stare at the ceiling, and really take in what you just read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All suggestions are appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寻找一本能在精神上摧毁我的书]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在寻找一本书，最好是恐怖或类似的，能让我重新思考我的整个人生。
我重新思考我的整个人生。我想找一本能完全吸引我，但又能让我想躺下，盯着天花板看的书。
也让我想躺下，盯着天花板哭。一些
令人不安，令人心碎，并将永远留在我心中。我是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ourjr4/looking_for_a_book_that_will_destroy_me_mentally/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ourjr4/looking_for_a_book_that_will_destroy_me_mentally/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 04:01:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for a book, preferably horror or something similar, that will make me rethink my entire life. I want something that completely captivates me but also makes me want to just lay down, stare at the ceiling and cry. Something disturbing, heart breaking, and will stick with me forever. I&amp;#39;m trying to get into reading more, only book I&amp;#39;ve been reading lately is American Psycho, which I do enjoy how brutal it is. I am most interested in war stories and stuff, and least interested in paranormal and ghost stories. Any suggestions are greatly appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["小王子》在83页中给我的感动比大多数书在500多页中所做的还要多。]]></title><description><![CDATA[这本书绝对漂亮，它是为儿童写的，但我认为它包含了成人也应该听到的教训。
蕴含着成年人也应该听到的教训。小王子所经历的冒险
谈到了爱、纽带、生活，并在孩子的眼中展示了 "成人 "的行为。
儿童眼中的 "成人 "行为。王子遇到了成年人，他们所做的事情在他们看来是荒谬的。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouyso9/the_little_prince_moved_me_more_in_its_83_pages/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouyso9/the_little_prince_moved_me_more_in_its_83_pages/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 03:32:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is absolutely beautiful, it’s written for children but I think it carries lessons adults should hear as well. The adventures the little prince go on talk about love, bonds, life, and shows “adult” behavior in the eyes of a child. The prince meets adults who do things that are absurd to him. For example: he meets a man who believes he owns the stars yet spends all his time counting them, for the sake of becoming richer so he can “buy more” stars. The prince simply wanders off after asking a few questions, commenting on how strange adults are. I won’t speak much more about the plot because I don’t want to just give my summary, but by the time I had finished the book I was in tears! Few books have moved me to tears the way the little prince has. It’s a very easy read and I cannot suggest it enough, whether you’re 9 or 90 there’s something to find in this book!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寻找新书阅读]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，我是Ciana，我有自闭症，我喜欢阅读，我正在寻找书籍建议。
我喜欢奇幻、恐怖、惊悚、神秘、真实犯罪、令人毛骨悚然的民间传说。
我也很喜欢《寻找阿拉斯加》这本书，它是一本好书，也是纸上谈兵。
城镇]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ourscc/looking_for_new_books_to_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ourscc/looking_for_new_books_to_read/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 01:56:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi I&amp;#39;m Ciana I have autism and I love to read I&amp;#39;m looking for book suggestions I prefer fantasy, horror, thrillers, mystery, true crime, creepy folk lore I could go on I also loved the book looking for Alaska it&amp;#39;s a good read as well as paper towns&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[神经舞者》仍然是令人震惊的赛博朋克作品]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/outgka/neuromancer_is_still_mindblowing_cyberpunk/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/outgka/neuromancer_is_still_mindblowing_cyberpunk/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 22:38:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[唯一已知的J.D.塞林格的声音录音将与偷走它的女人一起被火化。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ourjbz/the_only_known_recording_of_jd_salingers_voice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ourjbz/the_only_known_recording_of_jd_salingers_voice/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 21:09:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[苏珊娜-克拉克的《乔纳森-斯特兰奇和诺雷尔先生》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不久前读过这本书，我很喜欢它。我读的第一本作者的书是
皮拉内西，虽然我喜欢它，但我并没有像我希望的那样留下深刻印象，所以我
所以我对购买这本书犹豫不决。虽然我是一时兴起买的，但我还是很喜欢它。
立刻就喜欢上了。虽然它在这里和那里都有延伸，但我仍然喜欢...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouo4lm/jonathan_strange_and_mr_norrell_by_susanna_clarke/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouo4lm/jonathan_strange_and_mr_norrell_by_susanna_clarke/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 20:01:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read it a bit ago and I loved it.  The first book of the authors I read was Piranesi, though I liked it, I wasn&amp;#39;t all impressed the way I was hoping, so I was hesitant to buy this one.  Though I bought it on a whim and I enjoyed it immediately.  Though it stretched here and there, I still loved the whole thing, and I love the world building as well.  I just wanted to know other&amp;#39;s thoughts on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么流行的作家你只是没有真正的阅读欲望？]]></title><description><![CDATA[请不要追问我，但我只是没有兴趣去了解
斯蒂芬-金的书。不要误会我的意思，我并不反对，我甚至拥有《绿色里程》，并打算最终阅读它。
我甚至拥有《绿色里程》，并打算最终阅读它，但就目前而言，这种炒作对我来说几乎是令人反感的。
但就目前而言，炒作对我来说几乎是令人反感的。有没有人有类似的感觉，或者有其他的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouq40a/any_popular_author_you_just_dont_really_have_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouq40a/any_popular_author_you_just_dont_really_have_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 19:48:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please don’t come after me, but I just don’t have an interest to get into Stephen King books. Don’t get me wrong, I am not opposed to it and I even own The Green Mile and intend to read it eventually but as of now, the hype is almost off-putting to me. Anybody else feel similarly or with another author?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[暑期免费阅读--如果你被分配到较老的经典书籍作为暑期阅读的一部分，你可能可以从古腾堡计划中免费获得这些书籍。这里有一个100多本免费的通常分配的书籍清单。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouml14/free_summer_reading_if_you_are_assigned_older/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ouml14/free_summer_reading_if_you_are_assigned_older/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 19:23:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[完成了弗里德里希-尼采的《查拉图斯特拉》（Also sprach Zarathustra）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[上帝已经死了，他是被对我们人类的怜悯所杀。

我完全理解尼采对一切宗教的反感，我认为
这是他的主题，以摆脱当时存在的宗教胡言乱语
(而且现在仍然存在)。到目前为止，我只读了《反基督者》，那是对宗教的全面咆哮
宗教...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oufx73/finished_also_sprach_zarathustra_by_friedrich/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oufx73/finished_also_sprach_zarathustra_by_friedrich/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 17:06:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;God is dead and he was killed by pity for us humans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I totally appreciate the Nietzsches dislike for everything religious and I think it was his topic to get rid of the religious nonsense that existed back then (and still exists). I only read Antichrist so far, which is a full rant about religions where every religion is kind of rated and the nonsense exposed (except Buddhism, Buddhism is fine according to Nietzsche).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being this explicit against religions is astonishing, especially so since his books where written in the mid 19th centuries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also like the polemic, direct, cynical, provoking and sometimes funny style of Nietzsche. He wrote what he was thinking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Read it in the original german, and there where a lot more h letters in the german language back then. But this is not what made it hard to read. The philosophy is not direct in the book, but transmitted through some bible style text that you somewhat have to interpret yourself. I had to read most sentences twice to get any meaning out of it. But sometimes also that failed and I couldn&amp;#39;t extract any meaning for me and I continued. I think this book has to be read multiple times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I is famous for the &amp;#39;Übermensch&amp;#39; and the &amp;#39;Wille zu Macht&amp;#39;. The Übermensch is all over this book. The Will zur Macht is at best scratched and not really explained. I&amp;#39;m wondering actually why it is famous for that. I think he explained this concept in later books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &amp;#39;Übermensch&amp;#39; is a dangerous thought imho. Especially since he speaks of superfluous people that he hopes will die soon! Tough and unthinkable to write something like this by today standards. No wonder the Nazis liked this. I get there are lost people and people that seem to have no purpose at all, but questioning there right to live doesn&amp;#39;t seem to be right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I get from the Übermensch is that humankind should work on improving themselves (morally). To be better tomorrow than we are today (and there is a lot of room for improvement there to be honest). He also wrote that you cannot become the Übermensch, but your best chance is to &amp;#39;bear&amp;#39; the Übermensch. Meaning for me that we should teach our children too not make the racist, homophobic and whatnot mistakes we did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some notes and thoughts I took from parts of the book:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Tausend Ziele gab es bisher, denn tausend Völker gabe es. Nur die Fessel der tausend Nacken fehlt noch, es fehlt das Eine Ziel. Noch hat die Menschheit kein Ziel.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Aber sagt mir doch, meine Brüder: wenn der Menschheit das Ziel noch fehlt, fehlt da nicht auch - sie selber noch? -&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sorry for the original german, I&amp;#39;m unable to translate Nietzsche to proper english. But the summary is that humankind has no goal and therefore lacks humanity. This is very strong and made me think a lot. I agree that we have no goal at all. We are just exploiting each other without any goal, so that a small fraction of people become rich and live very well while the others live in poverty and bad situations. This is inhumane. But on the other hand, what would be the goal for humanity? Improve the situation for everybody and not for a fraction of people, maybe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is also one really great sentence about freedom:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Frei wovon? Was schiert das Zarathustra! Hell aber soll mir dein Auge künden: frei wozu?&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freedom for what? What do you do with your freedom? A good question that you better answer before you fight for freedom. It is easy to see something that is hindering your freedom. But what do you do if you get rid of it (if only hypothetical).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Something about praise:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Und auch das lernte ich unter ihnen: der Lobende stellt sich, als gäbe er zurück, in Wahrheit aber will er mehr beschenkt sein&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Praise is always egoistic and &amp;#39;hierarchic&amp;#39; and you have to be careful with that. Read a whole book about his once. Praise _always_ &amp;#39;belittles&amp;#39; the praised one (more or less, depending on the context).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He seems to be also obsessed with the &amp;#39;Schaffen&amp;#39; (to work or produce something) concept:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Wollen befreit: denn Wollen is Schaffen: so lehre ich. Und &lt;em&gt;nur&lt;/em&gt; zum Schaffen sollt ihr lernen&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Only learn something if you want to produce something with it. Whats the purpose of learning something If you don&amp;#39;t use it to produce something? Not sure about this. I you enjoy learning something without any purpose for pure egoist hedonism it still can be worthwhile imho. But it improves only yourself and is a dead end for improving humankind?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And something about the Wille zur Macht at last?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Euer Werk, euer Wille is euer »Nächster«: lasst euch keine falschen Werthe einreden!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be careful if others want to put there values upon you (which religions tend t do a &lt;em&gt;lot&lt;/em&gt;). Trust on your own egoistic willpower, it is your best &amp;#39;neighbour&amp;#39;. I agree.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I really laughed at the cynicism of Nietzsche at the end of the book. Since God is Dead and there is nobody to worship anymore they start worshiping the donkey in the room. Man, this was great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well you could write whole books about the interpretation of this book (and there are already whole books about this book) this are my main points I took out of it. I&amp;#39;m glad I read it, if only for the new thoughts mentioned above it sparked.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[指环王》（The Lord of the Rings]]></title><description><![CDATA[我目前正在重读《魔戒》；在电影出来之前，我读了好几遍。
但后来没有再读。目前正在读第四册的中间部分，即弗罗多、山姆和咕噜第一次进入伊蒂利安时。
咕噜第一次进入伊蒂利安。

天啊，多么伟大的写作和精彩的故事。每隔半小时左右，我就会想
我就对自己说，"这真是一个......"。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oulv9y/the_lord_of_the_rings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oulv9y/the_lord_of_the_rings/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 16:39:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am currently re-reading LOTR; I read it several times before the movies came out but have not since. Currently in the middle of book 4 when Frodo, Sam and Gollum first enter Ithilien. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Man, what great writing and wonderful storytelling. Every half hour or so I think to myself, &amp;quot;This is such a great part of the story coming up&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s been close to or over 20 years since I read this and it has been filled with great surprises, forgotten (and mostly better) differences from the movies and in general it&amp;#39;s been great.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know you will never see this, but thank you so much Dr. JRR Tolkien!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么书是被误解的犯罪？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我首先想到的是F*ght Club和1984。它是如此
看到好的文学作品被完全错误地对待，是非常令人沮丧的。

对《战斗俱乐部》的看法尤其令人沮丧，因为人们认为这本书正是在颂扬极端主义和有毒行为。
因为人们认为这本书正是在颂扬那种极端主义和有毒行为......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oulbva/what_book_is_criminally_misunderstood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oulbva/what_book_is_criminally_misunderstood/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 16:39:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first ones that come to mind to me are F*ght Club and 1984. It’s so frustrating to see good literature taken the complete wrong way. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The perception of F*ght Club is especially frustrating because people think the book is celebrating exactly the kind of extremism and toxic behavior it’s condemning. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;amp; I feel like people misunderstand 1984 by missing the nuances it has about the importance of language and just calling all changes in terms totalitarianism.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What’s a book that you think is misunderstood?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(Edited for grammar and clarity)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[范德梅尔的《龙涎香》是一部被误解的杰作。]]></title><description><![CDATA[范德梅尔是一位作家，最著名的作品是《湮灭》，它被拍成电影，由娜塔莉-波特曼主演。
由娜塔莉-波特曼主演。他早期的三部曲《龙涎香》（Ambergris）非常晦涩难懂，以至于在一年前被印制成书时，大部分内容都已绝版。
直到一年前，他的三部曲以总集的形式发行，才基本绝版。
总集。在几周内读完这三部曲后，我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ou6sbm/vandermeers_ambergris_is_a_misunderstood/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ou6sbm/vandermeers_ambergris_is_a_misunderstood/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 15:47:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vandermeer is an author best known for &lt;em&gt;Annihilation&lt;/em&gt;, which was made into movie starring Natalie Portman. His earlier trilogy, &lt;em&gt;Ambergris&lt;/em&gt;, is obscure enough that it was mostly out of print until a year ago when it was released in as an omnibus. After reading through the trilogy in a couple weeks, I am convinced it&amp;#39;s small following is due to a lack of marketing and readers constantly misunderstanding what they&amp;#39;re getting into when they come to it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vandermeer employs strange literary devices to describe the interactions of the civilians of the vivid, strange city of Ambergris. At the core, Vandermeer is writing pure literary works here. Stylistically he reads far more like McCarthy, Fitzgerald, and Hemingway than the typical fantasy fiction juggernauts. Content-wise, his stories are streamlined on characters, just like any literary work. The fantasy elements are included in deeply human ways that force the reader to grapple with the fate of millions and what it means to witness and understand history.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The books are sadly impossible to market. His later work found critical success with &lt;em&gt;Annihilation&lt;/em&gt;, which could be pigeonholed as a thriller for marketing. &lt;em&gt;Ambergris&lt;/em&gt; still sits in the background, mostly unread and avoided, which a real shame. You can classify it as weird fiction but that label will send away most of the readers who will truly love it, as you don&amp;#39;t really expect to see a mushroom-world in literary canon.  I&amp;#39;m fairly well-read and I was constantly amazed as Vandermeer showed me time and again things I never imagined in a book. His later work is more polished and marketable but this early trilogy arguably has more heart in it. I wonder if one day &lt;em&gt;Ambergris&lt;/em&gt; will finally pick up steam and be recognized for what it is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚刚读完玛德琳-米勒的《阿基里斯之歌》和《circe》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是否有希望找到与之相当的东西。编辑1：所以你们都
相信我没有希望...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ouhe7v/just_finished_song_of_achilles_and_circe_both_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ouhe7v/just_finished_song_of_achilles_and_circe_both_by/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 15:25:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is there any hope for me to find something quite like it.
Edit 1: so y&amp;#39;all believe that I have no hope...&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[科幻作家奥克塔维亚-巴特勒加入了未来学家的万神殿。数字艺术家Nettrice Gaskins新近委托创作的作品向这位作家的职业生涯致敬。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oujkb5/pioneering_scifi_writer_octavia_butler_joins_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oujkb5/pioneering_scifi_writer_octavia_butler_joins_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:31:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[巫婆的图书俱乐部]]></title><description><![CDATA[嗨，亲爱的！! 我只是想让社区知道，我正在主持一个
巫师读书会，将于8月1日开始。我希望我在这里分享的内容是可以的。
我只是觉得，如果有一些社区成员加入，那将是非常好的。
加入进来 这将是一个很大程度上自定进度的活动，而且非常低。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ouaf54/book_club_for_witchy_btches/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ouaf54/book_club_for_witchy_btches/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 05:59:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi sweetlings!! I just wanted to let the community know that I’m hosting a witchy book club that will begin on August 1st. I hope it’s ok that I’m sharing here—I just feel like it would be great to have some members from the community join in! It’s going to be largely self-paced, and very low pressure (much like our happy group here). Our August pick is “Toil and Trouble” by Augusten Burroughs. Check it out on instagram and twitter @ GrimoireBookClub, or at grimoirebookclub.com and sign up for the newsletter! Hope to see you there 💕 🔮✨📖&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我不能享受莎士比亚，这让我很难过]]></title><description><![CDATA[英语不是我的第一语言，虽然我的英语足够流利，可以顺利阅读绝大多数书籍。
虽然我的英语足够流利，可以顺利地阅读绝大多数书籍，但莎士比亚的语言对我来说是一个太高的障碍。
对我来说障碍太大。我读它，但在大多数句子之后，我不得不停下来，试图弄清楚它的意思。
我读它，但在大多数句子之后，我不得不停下来，试图弄清楚它的意思，这就扼杀了戏剧的流畅性。I...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ou1bm0/i_cant_enjoy_shakespeare_and_it_makes_me_sad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ou1bm0/i_cant_enjoy_shakespeare_and_it_makes_me_sad/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:42:40 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;English is not my first language, and although I&amp;#39;m fluent enough to read the vast majority of books without a problem, Shakespeare&amp;#39;s language is too high a barrier for me. I read it, but after most sentences I have to stop and try to figure out what it means, and it kills the flow of the play. I can&amp;#39;t enjoy it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a pity, because I understand enough to appreciate the elegance of the language, but not enough to be able to enjoy it. I don&amp;#39;t know if this is a problem for most native English speakers or not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[经过多年的缓慢阅读，我在大约三周的时间里读了9本书!]]></title><description><![CDATA[标题说明了一切!

像我们大多数人一样，我在童年时曾经吞噬书籍。没有办法
阻止我阅读我妈妈书架上的任何书。但成年后
我必须经常学习以跟上办公室的工作。
工作，而我只是没有精力......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ou8hr5/after_years_of_slow_reading_ive_read_9_books_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ou8hr5/after_years_of_slow_reading_ive_read_9_books_in/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:13:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Title says it all! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like most of us, I used to devour books when I was a child. There was no way of stopping me from reading anything I could find on my mom&amp;#39;s bookshelf. But adult life has gotten the better of me; I have to study a lot to keep up with office work, and I just didn&amp;#39;t have the energy to read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But as of late, I have re-kindled the momentum of reading books that I like and find quite enjoyable, both fiction as well as technical stuff!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Granted, there are 2x100 page books/short stories in there, which feels like cheating. But I don&amp;#39;t mind, as long as you don&amp;#39;t! I&amp;#39;ve overcome the laziness and I&amp;#39;ve been back at reading for a while. And I&amp;#39;m proud!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It all started because I wanted to finish the Dante and Colombia series by Sandrone Dazieri, so I re-read the second book in order to get into the third. And I just couldn&amp;#39;t stop. The first book is called Kill the Father, if anyone is interested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also threw a few science books in there that I knew I&amp;#39;d love, for good measure (had them collecting dust on my shelves):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kill the Angel (Dante and Colombia #2), Sandrone Dazieri.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Kill the King (Dante and Colombia #3), Sandrone Dazieri.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Lord of the Flies, William Golding. Re-read. One of my absolute favourites.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Of Mice and Men, John Steinbeck. Read it in one sitting on a 3h plane. I adored it so much!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A Brief History of Time, Stephen Hawking. Physics book #1.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Atom, Lawrence Krauss. Physics book #2. I had to take notes reading this to keep track of a few things. But I enjoyed myself enormously.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Theory of Everything, Stephen Hawking. Physics book #3. To my dismay, I realized upon reading that the conference&amp;#39;s this book is based on, are 95% copied from A Brief History of Time. Since it&amp;#39;s another 100 page read (just like Of Mice and Men), I read it anyways while sitting at a cozy bar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Orange Clockwork, Anthony Burguess. I have to admit, that I didn&amp;#39;t know that this book was written in a certain type of lingo the author came up with, the Nadsat speak, if I recall correctly, which I wasn&amp;#39;t prepared for at all. At the start it was very hard to understand, but luckily, the words were very repetitive and it seemed to me that the vocabulary was rather slim, and therefore, it felt easy to remember after a few pages. But I didn&amp;#39;t enjoy it as much as I wanted.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The Hitchhiker&amp;#39;s Guide to the Galaxy, Douglas Adams. I laughed out loud like a maniac while reading this; and I&amp;#39;m going to get the #2, The Restaurant at the End of the Universe, tomorrow! I adored reading this so much, I want them all! &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can easily see that I&amp;#39;m playing catch up with my years of having lost interest and practice in reading. There are so many books that I have left behind, and so many things to read from now, that it makes me feel giddy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What am I planning on reading now? I have a few things that I had waiting for me on my shelves, that I just didn&amp;#39;t get around to reading. I&amp;#39;m probably going to read the Harry Potter play first, because it&amp;#39;s easily to digest (I wouldn&amp;#39;t want to loose the momentum!), and I can see The Restaurant at the End of the Universe on the horizon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A longer read that is waiting for me on my shelves is 11/22/63 by Stephen King!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I feel proud of myself, and I want to keep the momentum going. I know work will be in the way of reading, but I successfully avoided sitting at the computer for a few weeks now, and I feel so comfortable reading with a coffee in hand, that I feel like I could do this forever.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What have you guys been reading of lately? Do you lose or gain interest in books easily? If you&amp;#39;ve ever lost interest in books as an adult, what has brought you back?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wish you all a wonderful weekend!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Edit: wording.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在求职面试中最不应该提起的书是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[有时雇主会问你最近是否读过什么书。也许他们这样做
衡量你的注意力的持续时间？从人际关系的角度来看，我认为这是一个
是了解一个人的好问题。这是我见到某人时问的第一件事。
但我怀疑雇主是否真的关心。

总之，我认为...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oua7tv/whats_the_worst_book_to_bring_up_in_a_job/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/oua7tv/whats_the_worst_book_to_bring_up_in_a_job/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 02:13:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes employers will ask you if you&amp;#39;ve read anything recently. Maybe they do this to gage your attention span? On an interpersonal level, I think this is a great question to get to know someone. Its the first thing I ask when I meet someone, but I doubt employers actually care.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyways, I think &amp;quot;American Psycho&amp;quot; would be the worst possible answer. For obvious reasons, one of which being that most people know it as a movie.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[谁能推荐一本像小说一样紧张的非小说类书籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我最近读了Adam Higginbotham写的《切尔诺贝利的午夜》，我完全被它吸引了。
吞噬了它。谁能推荐一本非小说类的书，能像小说一样创造出大量的
紧张的非小说？

我对物理学、宇宙学、哲学、人工智能感兴趣。
历史和这些东西。但我愿意接受...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ou3kil/can_someone_recommend_a_non_fiction_book_that_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ou3kil/can_someone_recommend_a_non_fiction_book_that_is/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 01:05:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i have read Midnight in Chernobyl by Adam Higginbotham lately and i absolutely devoured it. Can someone recommend a non fiction book that creates as much tension as a novel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;i am interested in physics, cosmology, philosophy, artificial intelligence, history and this kind of stuff. But i am open for everything&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[试图阅读浪漫小说时感到心都黑了，还有人吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾经读过爱情小说，也读过其他类型的书。由于生活中发生了很多事情
由于发生了很多生活上的事情，而且感觉对现实生活中的约会不感兴趣，我只是无法再回到阅读（或观看）浪漫小说的行列中。
回到阅读（或观看）爱情小说中。这感觉很不真诚，很俗气。
有一些我曾经喜欢的作者，我只是无法阅读他们的作品。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otvy67/feel_black_hearted_trying_to_read_romances/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otvy67/feel_black_hearted_trying_to_read_romances/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 16:12:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to read romances as well as other genres. Since a lot of life stuff has happened, and feeling not interested in dating in real life, I just can&amp;#39;t get back into reading (or watching) romances. It feels so disingenuous and cheesy. There are authors I used to love that I just can&amp;#39;t read their books anymore. Has anyone else experienced losing an interest in a whole genre after many years of love? Thanks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在什么时候会放弃阅读一本书？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我正在读《美国精神病学》，虽然我知道这将是一本艰难的书，但我没有准备好。
我没有准备好。这种写作风格对我没有任何吸引力。I
我理解为什么要这样写，但对贝特曼的公寓、他的衣服、对话的描述很乏味。
贝特曼的公寓、他的衣服、对话的描述很乏味，让人难以理解。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otv2st/at_what_point_do_i_quit_reading_a_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otv2st/at_what_point_do_i_quit_reading_a_book/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 12:09:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m reading American Psycho and while I knew it was going to be a tough read, I was not prepared for this. The writing style does not appeal to me whatsoever. I understand why it is written like this, but the tedious descriptions of Bateman&amp;#39;s apartment, his clothes, conversations are a slog to get through. At what point do I drop the book? I&amp;#39;m 50 pages in and I don&amp;#39;t think I can get through another 300 pages of this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寻找关于被谋杀/犯罪颠覆的舒适小城的书籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[我非常喜欢慢热型犯罪剧，关注一个小镇，以及一个谋杀或犯罪如何改变一切。
谋杀或犯罪可以改变一切。

我非常喜欢具有这种氛围的电视节目。伊斯特镇的母亲》、《杀戮》、《真命天子》、《真命天子》等。
杀戮》、《Broadchurch》、《真探》S1。

我对令人毛骨悚然的谋杀之谜不那么感兴趣，但想...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/otrxcc/looking_for_books_about_small_cozy_towns_flipped/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/otrxcc/looking_for_books_about_small_cozy_towns_flipped/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 11:24:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am huge into slow burn crime dramas that focus on a small town and how a murder or crime can change everything.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TV shows with this exact vibe that I&amp;#39;m a huge fan of: Mare of Easttown,  The Killing,  Broadchurch,  True Detective S1.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not so much interested in a gruesome murder mystery,  but want to see how a seemingly simple town/people can have quite diverse/secretive lives.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve started reading Mystic River,  but couldn&amp;#39;t get into it. Looking for more recommendations to grab my interest.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks in advance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[1Q84..... 我不知道我是否能继续下去。帮助!]]></title><description><![CDATA[多年来，有人告诉我，我会喜欢上村上春树，但不知何故，我一直没有去看。
我一直都被告知我会喜欢上村上春树，但不知何故，我一直都没能如愿以偿。我正在读我的第一本，1Q84。起初我非常
吸引，但现在对我来说，它只是一个缓慢的过程。不确定我是否有一个糟糕的
但它是重复的，简单的和干燥的。有时我可以...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otqjju/1q84_i_dont_know_if_i_can_keep_going_help/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otqjju/1q84_i_dont_know_if_i_can_keep_going_help/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 09:54:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve been told for ages that i would love haruki murakami, but somehow never quite got around to it. I’m on my first, 1Q84. At first i was extremely intrigued but man it’s just slogging for me now. 
Not sure if i have a bad English translation but it’s repetitive, simple and dry. Sometimes i can suspend my disbelief enough to consider I’m missing some nuance in translation but I’ve hit a wall. Roughly 40% through the book. Should i keep going?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Side note: finding the sexualisation of minors a bit overwhelming but as someone who likes anime/manga I’m not too surprised i guess.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love to read opinions about both topics. Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[是否曾有一句随机的话让你印象深刻，而这句话对你读的那本书并不重要？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的意思是说，不是励志的名言，而只是一句你至今仍记得的具体的台词。
几年后的今天，你还记得吗？

我的例子是《海底两万里》中的一句话，虽然我对这本书还记得很清楚，但我还没有重温这句话。
虽然我对这本书记得很清楚，但我已经有十多年没有读过这本书了，但我仍然
但我仍然有清晰的印象...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otm7ks/was_there_ever_a_random_quote_that_stuck_out_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otm7ks/was_there_ever_a_random_quote_that_stuck_out_to/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 08:43:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean like, not an inspirational quote, but just a specific line that you still remember to this day, years later?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My example would be from &lt;em&gt;20,000 Leagues Under The Sea&lt;/em&gt;, where, though I still remember the book fairly well, I haven’t read it in over a decade, but I still have crystal clear recollection of the line when they’re on the ship at the start and spot the “monster” and the Captain I believe it is is yelling for the gun to be fired and he yells a bunch of orders and finishes with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“And five bucks to the man who hits the infernal thing!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And for some reason that quote stuck with me, despite it not being a super important one or related at all to most of the story.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone else have any quotes like that?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我想喜欢科马克-麦卡锡。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的阅读范围相当广泛，并且喜欢我所读的大部分内容。从理论上讲
麦卡锡的方法和主题是我通常会被吸引的东西。
但我已经尝试过《大路》、《老无所依》和《所有漂亮的马》，但都没能读完50页左右，也没能读完。
但我曾尝试过《大路》、《老男人的国度》和《所有漂亮的马》，但都没能读完50页左右而没有......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otjtzp/id_like_to_like_cormac_mccarthy/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otjtzp/id_like_to_like_cormac_mccarthy/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 04:54:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I read quite widely, and enjoy the majority of what I read. Theoretically McCarthy’s approach and subject matter are something I would generally be drawn towards- but I’ve attempted The Road, No Country for Old Men, and All The Pretty Horses and haven’t been able to get past 50 pages or so without becoming bored and uninterested in the characters and story progression.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is your take on McCarthy? If you are a fan, why do you enjoy his works and how would you recommend approaching them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[女孩的沉默》改变了我对《阿基里斯之歌》的看法]]></title><description><![CDATA[TW:// 提及性侵犯问题

帕特-巴克的《女孩的沉默》和玛德琳-米勒的《阿基里斯之歌》。
都有相同的背景。它们都研究了阿基里斯在特洛伊战争中的作用。
他们的故事往往被忽视（尽管《阿基里斯之歌》开始于阿基里斯到......）。
在阿基里斯到达特洛伊之前。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otkow7/the_silence_of_girls_changed_my_perspective_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otkow7/the_silence_of_girls_changed_my_perspective_on/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 03:57:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TW:// mentions of Sexual Assault&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Silence of Girls by Pat Barker and The Song of Achilles by Madeline Miller both have the same setting. They both examine Achilles&amp;#39; role in the Trojan war, told by the people whose stories have been often overlooked (albeit SOA starts before Achilles makes it to Troy and The Silence of Girls begins ).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I read The Song of Achilles first, and found myself sympathizing for Patroclus and Achilles. They were gentle souls who in another universe, would have been soulmates. Patroclus depicts Achilles as headstrong, but caring. Stubborn, but loving. He depicts him as a man with a soul who is destined for greatness that destroys his chances at love. I couldn&amp;#39;t help but feel Patroclus&amp;#39; admiration for Achilles, and his frustration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I read The Silence of Girls, that perspective changed. Barker describes him as a cruel and apathetic man, who falls much more easily into the role of a conquerer than the story told in The Song of Achilles. Her brutal depiction of sexual violence that occurs in the camps is unflinching, something that is sometimes glossed over in SOA. By the end of the novel, I felt sick even thinking that I had empathized with such a character. When I tried to reread SOA to compare, I found I couldn&amp;#39;t get through it a second time, knowing how well Achilles was described.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else had a similar experience while reading the two books? Any other thoughts on the varying depictions of Achilles in the two novels? If one thing is for certain, the two completely different perspectives of the same character who has (essentially) the same plot and story in both novels, shows how talented Barker and Miller are at their craft.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[伊甸园之东。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不知道对这本书还能说些什么，但已经说过了。
有人说，"斯坦贝克的写作方式是，文字就像黄油一样流淌出来
和 "我不知道斯坦贝克有什么特点，但他的文字能让我立刻忘记周围的一切。
我不知道斯坦贝克是什么原因，但他的写作立刻让我忘记了我周围的一切。这些...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otfdxt/east_of_eden/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otfdxt/east_of_eden/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jul 2021 01:38:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don’t know what could be said about this book that hasn’t already been. Someone had stated that ‘Steinbeck writes in a way where the words just flow off the page like butter’ and ‘I don’t know what it is about Steinbeck but his writing instantly makes me forget about everything around me.’. These two resonate with me. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Being closer to 40 than I was yesterday, I feel like if I’d read this in my 20’s I’d have thoroughly enjoyed it, but certain themes would have been lost to me. Not that I’d have been confused, the subtleties might literally have not awakened in me the emotions that I’d feel now. Similarly, if I’d have read this in my 50s or 60s, I think I may recognize additional themes that might’ve eluded me upon reading in my 30s. It’s just that this book travels so deeply into a certain time and human condition that there must be enjoyment and enlightenment to be discovered at nearly any age, and each decade may house a secret to be unraveled. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A couple of the characters have such profound philosophies, and if feels so natural when they are conversing and questioning the world around them. For an author to conceive these characters, their train of thought, their ideals and motivations…it’s truly a wonder to me how rich in life and real they seem. And for them alone to have you nodding your head, or pondering their words is wonderful. The quotability held within the pages has no end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, I only know that I loved this novel. It may be the best I’ve read. But who am I…
If you have this on your list, dear reader, I’m excited for you and the road ahead.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[寻找可以帮助解决焦虑的书籍!]]></title><description><![CDATA[寻找可以帮助解决焦虑的书籍! 主要是针对社交焦虑症]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/otdiy4/looking_for_books_that_can_help_with_anxiety/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/otdiy4/looking_for_books_that_can_help_with_anxiety/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 21:32:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking for books that can help with anxiety! Mostly for social anxiety&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爱好者协会被勒令没收2003年从伊拉克偷运出来的罕见的吉尔伽美什石碑]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otc3o8/hobby_lobby_ordered_to_forfeit_rare_gilgamesh/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/otc3o8/hobby_lobby_ordered_to_forfeit_rare_gilgamesh/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 16:15:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有多嘴的习惯，不能保守任何秘密。有没有关于停止说话的书籍推荐？]]></title><description><![CDATA[有说得太多的习惯。有没有关于停止说话的书籍推荐？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ot5y5l/have_a_habit_of_talking_too_much_and_cant_keep/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/ot5y5l/have_a_habit_of_talking_too_much_and_cant_keep/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 14:35:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have a habit of talking too much. Any books recommendations on stop talking more&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[金-斯坦利-罗宾逊的《未来部》给了我前所未有的气候希望]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨晚，我读完了《未来部》，我个人认为它是我读过的对气候厄运感最好的解药。
是我读过的对气候厄运感觉最好的解药。

它绝不是对不久的将来的乐观或乌托邦式的想象（事实上。
该书以印度的致命热浪开篇，该热浪导致2000多万人死亡......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ossgss/kim_stanley_robinsons_the_ministry_for_the_future/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ossgss/kim_stanley_robinsons_the_ministry_for_the_future/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 14:03:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night, I finished &amp;quot;The Ministry for the Future&amp;quot;, and I personally found it to be the best antidote to feelings of climate doom I&amp;#39;ve ever read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s by no means an optimistic or utopian imagining of the near future (in fact, the book opens with &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;a deadly heatwave in India that kills 20+ million people&lt;/span&gt;). Instead, Robinson grapples with every imaginable solution we could (and might have to) leverage in the next 30ish years to try to save our biosphere from total devastation. Pumping water out from under Antarctic glaciers to slow them down, solar radiation management to provide temporary reprieve from warming, direct air carbon capture and sequestration, even shadow government operations to *&lt;strong&gt;ahem\&lt;/strong&gt;* &lt;em&gt;disincentivize&lt;/em&gt; carbon burners from doing what they do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are certainly chapters that slow down into the weeds of, for example, economic policy that was way over my head, but it was still interesting and incomprehensible enough that I felt like I was learning about something new. I still can&amp;#39;t tell you what quantitative easing is, but I know we might need to do it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;ve ever read anything else by KSR, you likely know he&amp;#39;s an open socialist, so you can probably guess what his imagined future wherein we attempt to survive the climate crisis looks like.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;re anything like me, constantly looking at the daily environmental news with abject horror as the situation grows worse, &amp;quot;faster than expected&amp;quot;, then I really encourage you to check this out. I&amp;#39;m feeling more hopeful for my future than ever... and isn&amp;#39;t that something science fiction is meant to do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚读了乌苏拉-K-勒奎因的《地海》前两本书，孩子们，我对此事有一些想法]]></title><description><![CDATA[是的，正如书名中所说。我目前正在看第三本书的中间部分
我也有所有其他的书。首先，如果你正在读这篇文章，但没有读过这本书，就不要说什么破坏性的话。
首先，如果你正在读这篇文章，但还没有读过这些书，就不要说什么剧透了。第一本《地海仙踪》并没有在我开始阅读时就抓住我的注意力。
我一开始读的时候，并没有抓住我的注意力，因为我觉得......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osuoaf/i_just_read_the_first_two_books_of_earthsea_by/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osuoaf/i_just_read_the_first_two_books_of_earthsea_by/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 03:35:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yeah, what it says in the title. I&amp;#39;m currently in the middle of the third book and I have all the rest of them too. First, no spoiler talk if you&amp;#39;re reading this post but haven&amp;#39;t read the books. The first, &lt;em&gt;A Wizard of Earthsea&lt;/em&gt;, didn&amp;#39;t grab my attention as soon as I started reading it, as I felt like the storytelling was a whole lot of telling and very little showing, but I quickly powered through until I was eventually engrossed in the story. What made it click is when I realised that this book would be really good to read out loud to someone else. On the other hand, the second book, &lt;em&gt;The Tombs of Atuan&lt;/em&gt;, grabbed my attention from the very start and I loved every single page of it. I won&amp;#39;t discuss the third yet because I&amp;#39;m not done reading it, but I really wanted to share my thoughts on the first two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From here on out, there be spoilers, may this be your warning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tale of Ged, Sparrowhawk, became interesting only after he summoned the shadow, in my opinion. Before that, it was a lot of setup, but little substance. Still, Ged&amp;#39;s character arc is well realised and he, as a character, grew on me rather fast after the incident. I really like how the conflict in this book rarely goes into combat, and even when it does it&amp;#39;s rather brief and is never the ultimate solution to whatever problem is at hand. I interpreted Ged&amp;#39;s conflict with his own shadow as representing his growth out of his juvenile arrogance, as at first, when faced with the consequences of it, he takes refuge from his shame in excessive humbleness, even giving up on his dreams, ambitions and talents, but ultimately the real solution isn&amp;#39;t to destroy the shadow that embodies his past arrogance, but to embrace it, recognising that it was a part of who he is and learn from the experience going forward. It&amp;#39;s not the most complex thing in the world, but I really enjoyed it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, the second book is where things get really good. Ged may be a very likeable character, but he&amp;#39;s not particularly complex or nuanced. But Tenar? I think Tenar is a great character, extremely well rounded and full of nuance, a lot of it unspoken, merely shown through her actions. Her tale gripped me from the very start and never let go until the book was over. Not all of her actions are good, but that&amp;#39;s not a bad thing because we get to see the psychological burden that doing those things placed on her. Also, we really get to explore the effect on her mind and feelings of the indoctrination that she got from a very young age by being grown in a literal cult of death. Seeing Ged again is very welcome, but Tenar is the absolute star of the show. The mystery and suspence in this book are top notch. Tenar gets to be a very strong and yet vulnerable character, who is prisoner of her circumstances but eventually breaks free by realising that she can exercise her own agency through compassion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thumbs up all around, especially considering the landscape of fantasy literature when she wrote these books. I can&amp;#39;t wait to read the rest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我认为《动物农场》是一本比《1984》更好的书]]></title><description><![CDATA[好吧，我知道很多人不喜欢 "这本书比那本书好 "这样的观点，因为每个人的兴趣不同。
因为每个人都可能有不同的兴趣，但我认为
动物农场》被低估了。

它是一个简短的寓言故事，可以在任何水平上阅读（我第一次读它是在初中），但这仍然是一个很好的例子。
我是在初中时读的），但这仍然...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ot022m/i_think_animal_farm_is_a_better_book_than_1984/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ot022m/i_think_animal_farm_is_a_better_book_than_1984/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 03:35:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Okay, so I know many don’t like opinions along the lines of “this book is better than that book” because everyone can have different interests, but I think Animal Farm is WAY underrated. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is a short, simple allegory that can be read at any level (I read it first in middle school), but that still holds deeper meaning when you understand more about the world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m sure it has to do with the fact it was a criticism of a past event rather than a warning about a possible future like 1984 is. But this is a must-read for any adult, especially in such a controversial political climate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[军方掠夺科幻小说的技术理念，但对该流派的社会评论视而不见]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osxou9/militaries_plunder_science_fiction_for_technology/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osxou9/militaries_plunder_science_fiction_for_technology/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jul 2021 01:59:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[波西-杰克逊》这本书适合成年人阅读吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我读到它们是为儿童准备的，但它们看起来确实很有趣。作为一个成年人
我是否会喜欢它们，或者它们会不会太幼稚了？它们看起来是幻想类书籍
而我喜欢幻想。

一共有多少本书，你推荐哪些？谷歌说有
30本，但波西不是主要的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/osqira/are_the_percy_jackson_books_suitable_for_an_adult/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/osqira/are_the_percy_jackson_books_suitable_for_an_adult/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 20:23:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve read that they’re for children but they do seem interesting. As an adult would I enjoy them or would they be too childish? They look to be fantasy books and I like fantasy. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How many books are there and which ones do you recommend? Google says there are 30 but that Percy is not the main character in all of them&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[读《阿基里斯之歌》，当一本书能够早早地告诉你结局，并且仍然是美丽和惊人的，这就是一本好书的标志。]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像你从头到尾都知道阿基里斯会死，即使你不知道，你也知道书中的预言。
你从一般的知识中了解到书中的预言。
我记得我读过的另一个系列就是这样的。他们说，这就是将要发生的事情
他在最后死了，但你仍然喜欢这个故事，并在他死的时候哭。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osh2hw/reading_song_of_achilles_when_a_book_can_tell_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osh2hw/reading_song_of_achilles_when_a_book_can_tell_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 20:01:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like you know the whole time Achilles is going to die, even if you didn’t know it from general knowledge you learn the prophecy in the book and I remember reading another series that did that. They were like this is what’s gonna happen he dies at the end but you still love the story and cry when he dies. Just *mwah perfection&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[乔治-RR-马丁写作中的致命弱点]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以有一个鲜为人知的系列，叫做《冰与火之歌》，需要。
我们被告知，只需要两本书就能完成。我没有兴趣了解
它是否会出版，而是猜测它为什么不能完成。
完成。

乔治-rr-马丁是一位伟大的作家。他还声称自己是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osb17a/george_rr_martins_achilles_heel_in_writing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osb17a/george_rr_martins_achilles_heel_in_writing/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:58:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So there&amp;#39;s this little known series called a song of ice and fire that needs, we&amp;#39;ve been told, only 2 books to accomplish. I&amp;#39;m not as interested in learning if it ever will be published but rather I am guessing as to why it can&amp;#39;t be finished.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;George rr martin is a great writer. He also claims he is a slow writer. And I disagree with that. From 1996 to 2000 he published the first 3 books, which are masterpieces. Then 5 years later book 4, then 6 years later book 5, and now book 6....TBD. the trouble happens to be, in my opinion that his writing style of planting seeds and watching them grow hurt him. He kept having branches sprout from the tree trunk of the central story and those branches started growing smaller branches. He should have been cutting off branches, not making new ones after book 3. &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t like to know where the story is going when I write&amp;quot; I love you George, but sometimes you need to know when you have enough story. And you had enough by book 3.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[没有Facebook的6个月，我从来没有在这么短的时间内读过这么多书😭。]]></title><description><![CDATA[每天晚上8点，我把我的手机放在另一个房间，阅读直到我睡着。
睡觉。到目前为止，我已经读完了。

编织甜草

阿里阿德涅

阿基里斯之歌

希尔思

熊镇

亚提克之怒

灵魂守护者

白玫瑰，黑森林

夜莺

灵魂之旅系列

盾牌女郎：在嚎叫声中...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osomvz/6_months_of_no_facebook_and_i_have_never_read_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osomvz/6_months_of_no_facebook_and_i_have_never_read_so/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:17:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every night at 8 pm I put my phone in another room and read until I am falling asleep. So far, I have read:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Braiding Sweetgrass&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ariadne&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Song of Achilles&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Circe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beartown&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Artic Fury&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soulkeeper&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;White Rose, Black Forest&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Nightingale &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Soulbound Series&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shieldmaiden: Under the Howling Moon&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Last Kingdom &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Bride &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I swear, I can read more but I was finishing up grad school and preparing for certifications (take it on Saturday wish me luck!). I finally am free from studying and now focusing on leisure reading! I wish I deleted my facebook earlier!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[限制我的屏幕时间，极大地改善了我的阅读。]]></title><description><![CDATA[直到六个月前，我已经很久没有读过一本完整的书了。这并不是说我
并非我不想读。我从小就是一个狂热的读者，但自从我16或17岁以后，我的阅读量就急剧下降。
或17岁后，我的阅读量急剧下降。

多年来，我尝试阅读别人推荐给我的书。我经常
试图阅读...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osnn19/limiting_my_screen_time_drastically_improved_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/osnn19/limiting_my_screen_time_drastically_improved_my/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 16:17:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up until six months ago I hadn’t read a full book in ages. It’s not that I didn’t want to. I’ve been an avid reader since I was a child but since I was 16 or 17 my reading just dramatically dropped off. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Over the years I tried reading books that were recommended to me. I would often try to read at night before bedtime, I would always be able to get through a page or two before my eyes would start to glaze over and I would get sleepy. I even switched tact to reading in the afternoon but kind of the same thing happened. One problem was obviously I was being recommended more adult books and hadn’t read more than teenage level novels in many years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started to limit my screen time on my phone about 6 months ago by putting limits and sticking to them. I slowly started to replace that screen time with other activities (not just reading). The effect after about a month of doing that was kind of magical. I don’t know if this is placebo effect but I started to make it through many more pages every day. And once I got caught up in a book I was able to look forward to reading it and it didn’t feel like a forced activity. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me it was a simple as just limiting my screen time and my attention span it whatever recovered enough to allow me to enjoy books again. I also feel much happier fulfilled and creative than I did before. I still use my phone and laptop plenty but reading again has brought a healthy balance back into my life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This may be kind of an obvious post but just wanted to share in case anyone else is having the same struggles with reading.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[非小说类的精华--历史、哲学、科学、改变生活！！！。]]></title><description><![CDATA[编辑：我希望得到一些关于女性、POC和WOC作家的建议，以及
角度的书籍（英文）。我想要一个
我想要一个多样化的阅读清单，而不是以欧洲/美国男性为主。

你好，我从来没有读过非小说类的书，而且我逐渐意识到，我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/osjlub/non_fiction_essentials_history_philosophy_science/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/osjlub/non_fiction_essentials_history_philosophy_science/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 15:30:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Edit: I would love some suggestions of female, POC and WOC authors, aswell as books (in English) from perspectives of other countries and cultures. Im after a diverse reading list, not predominately european/American males.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I have never read non-fiction and I am coming to the realisation that I am missing out on knowledge of so many things in the world but I don&amp;#39;t know where to start. Considering I only read page turning suspenseful fiction, I will be needing an ease into the world of non-fiction. I would love some suggestions that are EASY to read and have a narrative flow. Open to ANYTHING that will help me open up my eyes and mind to the world. What are some of your favourite books that inspired, educated or blew your mind? Think of me as a beginner here so I need engaging, easy flow, and refined subject matter! Any period in history of any part of the world, any form of science and any realm of philosophy I&amp;#39;m open to. Thankyou :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幻想：你的网关书是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[在一次关于幻想小说的谈话中，有人问了我一个很好的问题
小说。我觉得有必要与大家分享一下这个问题，并附上一点个人的叙述。
这个问题是："你进入奇幻小说流派的入门书是什么？"

我的答案是布莱恩-雅克的《红墙》/《茉莉花》，这并没有花费太多的心思。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os1mkb/fantasy_what_is_your_gateway_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os1mkb/fantasy_what_is_your_gateway_book/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 11:50:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Someone asked me an excellent question during a conversation about fantasy novels. I felt the need to share it along with a little personal narrative.&lt;br/&gt;
The question was &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;What was your gateway book into the fantasy genre?&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My answer of &lt;em&gt;Redwall&lt;/em&gt; / &lt;em&gt;Mossflower&lt;/em&gt; by Brian Jacques did not take much thought as it is one of the few memories that I can call on from the young age of 11. I did not care much for reading as nothing could hold my interest for very long. My middle school librarian, Mr. Francis, had asked me a few questions regarding my attractions and pointed me into the direction of &lt;em&gt;Redwall&lt;/em&gt;. The depiction of good and evil may have been simply laid out in these children&amp;#39;s books, but I believe that they are the foundation for all good fantasy stories. I was at the perfect age and must have been going through the right experiences to have these books take the honorary title of &amp;quot;Gatway Book&amp;quot;. &lt;em&gt;Redwall&lt;/em&gt; had lead me into some wonderful novels and series such as LOTR, HP, ASOIAF, KKC, and of course many more.&lt;br/&gt;
So thank you Jacques for creating Martin the Warrior to inspire in me stronger senses of perseverance and morality. Thank you also Mr. Francis for enduring the snickers and comments of a pre teen boy, and giving me the gift of reading. May you both rest easy wherever you are. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So my question to you is &lt;strong&gt;&amp;quot;What was your gateway book into the fantasy genre?&amp;quot;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[南京大屠杀》是我所读过的最残酷的书之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[这本书讲述了当时（1937年）中国首都的入侵情况。
南京，被日本皇室军队入侵。当时，日本人对他们在南京的有限空间感到失望。
他们对自己国家有限的空间感到失望，因为这些空间可用于
耕种和维持其不断增长的人口的空间有限而感到沮丧。对于这些和许多人来说...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ose52n/the_rape_of_nanking_is_one_of_the_most_brutal/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ose52n/the_rape_of_nanking_is_one_of_the_most_brutal/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 08:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The book is about the invasion of China&amp;#39;s capital city at the time (1937), Nanking, by the Japanese Imperial army. At the time, the Japanese grew frustrated with the limited amount of space they had in their country for farming and sustaining their growing population. For these and many other economic and political reasons, the Japanese decided to invade and annex part of China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Upon entering China, the Japanese burned and pillaged many small cities on the East on their way to Nanking located on the west. The Chinese army was not well prepared for this attack and kept getting pushed back. As the Japanese approached Nanking, many Chinese soldiers fled Nanking by boat through a river called the Yangtze just north of Nanking. There were a limited amount of boats and therefore many soldiers were left behind to fight or drowned by trying to swim across. The Chinese army not only left behind many of its men but poor Chinese citizens who could not afford to leave China.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then Japan took control of Nanking. What follows is the most brutal treatment of human beings that I have ever heard of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Torture/Killing*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a couple of the ways that the Japanese tortured and killed Chinese soldiers and citizens:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beheading killing contests. The Japanese would have competitions amongst each other on who could behead the most Chinese soldiers in a certain amount of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bayonetting. They used the bayonet (a knife that is attached to the muzzle of a rifle), to stab children, adults, and old individuals. There were some cases were pregnant women were disemboweled by bayonet so that the Japanese could bayonet their fetus. *ALSO* , the Japanese used dead Chinese individuals for bayonetting practice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mass incineration. A bunch of Chinese captives would be pushed into a pit, lit with gasoline, and burnt alive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eaten alive by dogs. They would bury Chinese individuals up to their waist and allow German shepherds to rip them to pieces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;One method was to bring many Chinese individuals to the top floor of a building, then set the bottom floors on fire, forcing them to jump off the building to their death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many people were thrown in the aforementioned river alive (which was frozen because it was December at the time of the invasion), where the Japanese would laugh at them and call it &amp;quot;fishing&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;One part of the book talks about how the Japanese had created several rows of prisoners in front of the river where the first row would get beheaded and the individual behind the one who just got beheaded had to push the other into the river. Then, the next individual would step up for their own beheading. This continued like a production line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;**Rapes*\&lt;/strong&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are a couple of the ways the Japanese brutalized the Chinese sexually (there was an estimated 20,000 - 80,000 women raped during and after the invasion of Nanking)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Japanese would rape girls as young as 8 and as old as 80. They would sometimes do it directly in the street and sometimes in front of the girls&amp;#39; families or husbands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They would force Chinese fathers to rape their daughters or for sons to rape their mothers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They would mutilate women&amp;#39;s breasts by cutting them or they would cut vaginas and shove large stick-like objects into them. There was a really disturbing story about how they would cut open young girls&amp;#39; vaginas in order to be able to penetrate them more easily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;They would gang rape many women or they would have them be passed around for many other men in the Japanese military to have a turn. There were stories of women being stored in certain buildings for the sole purpose of being raped multiple times a day by different men. Many of these women committed suicide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any woman who would deny a Japanese soldier&amp;#39;s sexual advance was instantly killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This disgusting event took the lives of over 300,000 Chinese soldiers/citizens and remains largely unspoken about in the West. This has to do with the economic/political interest the US has had with Japan ever since the cold war. In Japan, the government denies the atrocities to this day and distort history books that are taught to their young children. One of the quotes that really resonated with me in the book is that &amp;quot;to not acknowledge is to kill twice&amp;quot;. Say what you want about Germany, but they owned up to their mistakes and Nazi history is very emphasized in their educational system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book was EXTREMELY difficult to get through but really opened my eyes to the human capacity for evil and contextualized modern Japan-China relations. For these reasons, I am glad I have gotten through it and would recommend it to anyone who wants to learn more about one of the darkest events in human history (if you read the book, you will find that there is light in spite of the darkness with many different individuals (John Rabe &amp;amp; Robert Wilson of The Nanking Safety Zone) who protected and saved as many as 250,000 Chinese people).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[盗书者购买更多的书，以及其他不直观的盗书事实]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/orzc3e/book_pirates_buy_more_books_and_other_unintuitive/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/orzc3e/book_pirates_buy_more_books_and_other_unintuitive/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 05:53:29 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[关于抢劫的书籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[关于抢劫的书籍，有一个可爱的主人公或船员，对非小说的建议也可以接受。
非小说也可以接受。(也感谢你在我的许多其他请求之后作出答复。
的请求，谢谢你的回答）。)]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/osa3rh/books_about_heists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/osa3rh/books_about_heists/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 03:27:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Books about heists with a likable or protagonist or crew, suggestions for non fiction are also tolerated. (Also thank you for answering after my many other requests lol)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对尼尔-盖曼有什么看法？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就个人而言，我喜欢他的故事。我认为他写的东西真的很古怪，很有创意。
我特别喜欢他的漫画小说。

我刚刚拿起了《无名之地》，我几年前买了这本书，但从未读完。
当我重读它时，我注意到很多 "他有长发""她穿这个 "的说法。
"他做了那个" "她说...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os7c81/what_are_your_thoughts_on_neil_gaiman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os7c81/what_are_your_thoughts_on_neil_gaiman/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 02:46:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personally, I love his stories. I think he writes really quirky and creatively. I especially love his graphic novels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just picked back up Neverwhere, where I bought years ago and never finished. As I&amp;#39;m re-reading it I&amp;#39;m noticing a lot of &amp;quot;He had long hair&amp;quot; &amp;quot;she wore this&amp;quot; &amp;quot;He did that&amp;quot; &amp;quot;She said this&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Line after line and its irking me a bit. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Still in love with his work regardless. Thoughts?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚完成了《安娜-卡列尼娜》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我的生活已经达到了顶峰。我目睹了一些最真实的人物，在他们的复杂性和人类的可预测性方面，都是有史以来从头脑中产生的。
他们的复杂性和人类的可预测性，是有史以来从一个人的头脑中产生的。我几乎
我几乎感觉到我在阅读过程中真的活出了自己的人生；我经历了许多令我深思的事情。
我经历了如此之多的事情，让我深思，让我欣喜地微笑，让我哭泣......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os9grj/i_just_finished_anna_karenina/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os9grj/i_just_finished_anna_karenina/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Jul 2021 01:47:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;My life has peaked. I have witnessed some of the most real characters, in both their complexity and human predictability, to ever stem from a mind. I almost feel as though I have truly lived a life during my reading; I have experienced so much that has made me ponder, smile with glee, cry with sorrow, and simply feel satisfied with how easily I can understand the various characters (I could relate to each in their own way!), their struggles, and their place in society even though it was written so long ago—Tolstoy was a genius, a genius that could make you question and realize and think and feel more than you would be able to without his mind. None of his characters were without some unique insight into the spirit of the universe, the world, philosphy, psychology, Russian society, or the soul; and because all—at least the main characters—have pulled me alongside such a profound journey, a lasting impression of them on me is undoubtedly imbued inside my core, and will always be there. It’s also the perfect social commentary, and I can say with certainty that I understand the human condition to a greater extent than I ever have. Really, my life has been entrenched with such a new richness during the course of my reading—I cannot help but think that I have already reached my peak!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[什么书让你去。''他妈的... 这很好..."？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我不是一个大读者。我只是每年读几本书。4年前，我正在
逛当地的书店，没有书吸引我的注意。书店老板问
我说我一直喜欢哈利波特。
然后他向我推荐了帕特里克-罗斯福斯的《风之名》...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os6c9f/what_book_made_you_go_fuck_this_is_good/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/os6c9f/what_book_made_you_go_fuck_this_is_good/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jul 2021 21:40:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m not a big reader. I just read a few books every year. 4 years ago I was browsing my local bookstore and no book caught my eye. The bookstore owner asked what my favorite childhood book was and I said that I always loved Harry Potter. He then recommended The Name Of The Wind by Patrick Rothfuss saying that I will like that book since it&amp;#39;s Harry Potter for adults. (He didn&amp;#39;t mention that the series wasn&amp;#39;t finished yet...)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I vividly remember reading it with so much joy! Every chapter kept getting better and better. It was the first time in my life that a book actually gave me a &amp;#39;wow&amp;#39; moment. I just didn&amp;#39;t know a book could be that beautiful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s been awhile since I read a book like that. I&amp;#39;ve read some really good books but nothing spectacular.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever got that feeling and what book was it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>