<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Nov 2021 04:42:06 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[好吧，这听起来非常奇怪，但我正在寻找具有特定 "美学 "的书籍。]]></title><description><![CDATA[正如标题所言，我正在寻找某些类型的书；我想要的氛围是
我想感受的是类似于山寨美学的东西。我知道这听起来很疯狂，但
如果你在谷歌图片上查找 "cottagecore aesthetic"，会出现不同的图片。
蹦出植物、茶杯、漂亮的乡村房屋和其他东西......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pfbapx/okay_this_is_going_to_sound_really_strange_but_im/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pfbapx/okay_this_is_going_to_sound_really_strange_but_im/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 23:11:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the title states, I&amp;#39;m looking for certain kinds of book; the vibe that I want to feel is something like cottagecore aesthethic. I know it my sounds crazy but if you look up on google images &amp;quot;cottagecore aesthetic&amp;quot; different pictures will pop up with plants, tea cups, nice country houses and stuff like that. The only thing closest to these things are basically the chapters in The Lord of The Rings that revolves around The Shire and even some Elves places. I don&amp;#39;t know if the question is clear or not but I&amp;#39;m looking for books with these atmospheres, calming and relaxing books I guess, but with this kind of setting. Since english is not my first language I&amp;#39;ll understeand if I didn&amp;#39;t explain myself properly so I&amp;#39;ll try to be as clear as possible answering you if you&amp;#39;ll ask for any more clarification.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[丹-布朗的小说之间的相似之处]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经读完了丹-布朗的所有书籍。读完后，我想到
我想到，这些书有惊人的相似之处，甚至是那些非兰登的书。所以
让我们来讨论一下这些惊人的相似之处（请记住，也有例外）。
例外）...

 *死亡--有人死亡；可能是有人...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pf8wtc/the_similarities_between_the_novels_by_dan_brown/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pf8wtc/the_similarities_between_the_novels_by_dan_brown/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 22:25:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have completed reading all the books by Dan Brown. After the completion, it came to my mind that they are strikingly similar, even the non-Langdon ones. So let&amp;#39;s discuss about the striking similarities (keep in mind that there are exceptions) ...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Death - Someone dies; probably someone important/famous ( Ensei Tankado, Wailee Ming &amp;amp; Norah Mangor, Leonardo Vetra,  Jacques Saunière,  Bertrand Zobrist, Edmond Kirsch)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The main character is called and is asked to go somewhere.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The lady or the man (in the standalones) - is smart, confident, beautiful, bold and brave. (Sienna Brooks was the only &amp;#39;the lady&amp;#39; who wasn&amp;#39;t exactly with the good guys)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The agency - The agency is used by the antagonist to do the bad works ( Delta force, &amp;#39;Illuminati&amp;#39; Opus Dei, The Consortium, &amp;#39;The Palmarian Church&amp;#39;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Codes, Art, Riddles, &amp;#39;History&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Facts&amp;#39;, Religion &amp;amp; Technology&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The story narration is mostly done in two places/paths . The ending involves the joining of these paths. (Idk if guys r understanding what I meant, Eng isn&amp;#39;t my 1st lang)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The one person whom you can blindly trust, that is .. until you realise that he/she is the antagonist. ( Commander Trevor Strathmore,  William Pickering, Camerlengo Carlo Ventresca, Sir Leigh Teabing, Sienna Brooks, Winston, the only exception maybe Mal&amp;#39;akh)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The story has what I call &amp;#39;Hey, we  are/were  related/in a relationship&amp;#39; moment in the end. ( Ensei Tankado-Tokugen Numataka , Pope-Camerlengo Carlo Ventresca, Sophie Neveu-Marie Chauvel Saint-Clair &amp;amp; Brother, Peter Solomon-Mal&amp;#39;akh, Bertrand Zobrist-Sienna Brooks, The King of Spain-  Bishop Antonio Valdespino )&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The intimate scene in the end. (It doesn&amp;#39;t occur in the last three books)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The character shows hatred to his/her parent. (Rachel Sexton-Senator Sexton, Pope-Camerlengo Carlo Ventresca, Peter Solomon-Mal&amp;#39;akh). This is one of the less prominent similarities.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From all this I have created a general summary-&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main character (A) is called and informed of a problem/situation . He/she gets help from someone of the other gender (B) . There are some riddles referring to arcane art or literature. The antagonist uses an agency to carry out the deeds. A gets help from a trusted person (X). There is a lot of riddle solving. A realises that X is the bad guy. X gets caught. A spends some quality time with B. It is revealed that one of prominent character is related to another prominent character.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I would love to hear your opinions on my observations. Personally I find that the books have been becoming worse since &amp;#39;The Lost Symbol&amp;#39;, and have generally lost their originality.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我终于达到了100本书!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我有阅读障碍，但我非常喜欢阅读（我知道这很讽刺），所以读一本书要比正常情况下花很多时间。
我发现有时我很难集中注意力或完全记住我所读的内容。
我发现有时很难集中注意力或完全记住我所读的内容。然而，我每年都会试着做一次书的跟踪练习，我从来没有超过20本书，但我的阅读能力很强。
我从来没有超过20本书，但我终于达到了100本书，而且......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pfalmq/i_finally_reached_100_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pfalmq/i_finally_reached_100_books/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 21:23:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m dyslexic but I love reading so much (ironic I know)  so reading a book takes a lot longer than normal and I find it hard to focus or fully remember what i read sometimes. However I try to do a book track every year to practice and I never got more that 20 books but I finally reached 100 books and the year is still not finished yet. This is a massive achievement and I&amp;#39;m  just so happy about and I thought this was the best place to express it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The 100th book was  two can keep a secret by Karen Mcmanus. A modern day YA crime novel  the way she weaves the text from the perspective of her characters and keep you on tenorhooks the whole time. It chapters are all the outlook from the main characters and even though she wraps up her story at the end but somehow leaves something unresolved but not in a fursratrating way, more satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Highly recommended it to anyone who interested in crime or like books similar to Tanya french&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我开始和朋友们一起大声阅读书籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[去年，我开始和朋友们一起大声读书，我很喜欢。
它。我们通常只读几章，而不是整本书，因为那会让人觉得太累。
是太多了。虽然在大流行期间，我们确实设法一口气读完了《贝奥武夫》。
大流行病。我注意到了一些事情。

 * 让人给我读一本书...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pf5wn8/i_started_reading_books_out_loud_with_friends/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pf5wn8/i_started_reading_books_out_loud_with_friends/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 20:21:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past year, I started reading books out loud together with friends and I love it. We usually just read a few chapters, not the whole book because that would be too much. Although we did manage to read &amp;quot;Beowulf&amp;quot; in one go during the pandemic. Things I&amp;#39;ve noticed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having a book read to me stimulates different parts of my brain than me reading it. I&amp;#39;m able to visualise things easier and vividly, which enhances immersion. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s more passive and so less tiring, a bit like Audiobooks. But more engaging because you see the person and their expressions, and they can even &amp;quot;act out&amp;quot; the text. You&amp;#39;re also more inclined to pay attention/stay put than with Audiobooks (no temptation to pause).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It&amp;#39;s wholesome being in the same fictional world simultaneously with your friends and it&amp;#39;s a fun social activity to bring people together. Kind of like the old times when people gathered together to tell stories. It stirs something inside me reminiscent of my childhood. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, it&amp;#39;s more time-consuming and obviously it&amp;#39;s more like an event rather than being a replacement for solo reading, which I still prefer. Also, when I&amp;#39;m the one doing the reading I struggle to focus on the story for some reason. Overall, I think it&amp;#39;s fun and a nice way to share opinions with your friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阅读时间--根据你的个人阅读速度，估计你阅读任何书籍需要多长时间。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pfab6j/how_long_to_read_estimate_how_long_youll_take_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pfab6j/how_long_to_read_estimate_how_long_youll_take_to/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 18:47:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[廉价书籍怎么了？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我曾经能够在half.com、ebay或其他网站上找到1美元的旧书。
其他网站。运费是几美元，但很多时候书可以捆绑在一起
一个卖家--10本书15-18美元，类似这样的价格。半价书店
曾经在他们的商店里有一个1美元的清仓区，但那是......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/penabl/what_happened_to_cheap_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/penabl/what_happened_to_cheap_books/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 13:28:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to be able to find old paperbacks for $1 on sites like half.com, ebay, or others. Shipping would be a few dollars, but many times books could be bundled form one seller – 10 books for $15-18, something like that. Half Price Books used to have a $1 clearance section in their stores, but it was increased to $3 per book. I recently bought a hard bound non-fiction book that was a few years old and the best I could find used was $0.70 off the new price on Amazon. Am I looking in the wrong places, or have Amazon and resellers pushed all the prices up?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[完成《指环王》后，我感到很麻木]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚读完（和看完）《指环王》，现在我很难过。
我太喜欢它了，我不忍心和所有这些人物说再见。
说实话，我没有想到会对这本书投入如此多的感情。
说实话，我完全没有想到会对这本书有如此大的感情投入。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pej7u7/i_feel_numb_after_finishing_lord_of_the_rings/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pej7u7/i_feel_numb_after_finishing_lord_of_the_rings/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 10:25:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;well, i just finished reading (and watching) the lord of the rings and now i am sad. i love it so much and i can’t bear to say goodbye to all these characters that i journeyed with in what felt like years. to be honest, i did not expect to get this emotionally invested with this book at all. i thought i was just going to have a good time, have fun with the adventures, and then feel good after lol. but then it was nearing the end and all i could think about was “i don’t want this to end yet, I still want to go on adventures with these characters.” And then when I read the last line and finally finished it, I just stared at a blank wall after, feeling numb and sad and just ingesting all of it lmao. spent the whole day just thinking about everything that happened and getting melancholic after realizing that i will never get to read this book for the first time ever again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;this is the first time i am feeling like this with a book and it’s a feeling that i will cherish forever. i do not regret ever reading this book and honestly it’s one of the best things that’s happened in my life. just thought i would share this feeling because it’s a new feeling for me and i just loved this book so much. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;what are books that you unexpectedly loved and cherished?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我读了安迪-威尔的《圣母计划》，我可能再也不会读到这么棒的东西了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[作为一个阅读大量科幻文学作品的人，这可能是我迄今为止读过的最好的科学
的故事。

到目前为止，我读过的很多科幻作品都使用了科幻元素--飞船、太空服。
外星人来讲述情节驱动或人物驱动的故事。很少能找到
很少能找到有科学和发现的故事...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pf167k/i_read_andy_weirs_project_hail_mary_and_ill/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pf167k/i_read_andy_weirs_project_hail_mary_and_ill/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 09:33:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As someone who reads alot of sci-fi literature, this might be the best science story I&amp;#39;ve ever read till now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of sci-fi I&amp;#39;ve read till now uses sci-fi elements - spaceships, suits, aliens to tell plot driven or character driven stories. It&amp;#39;s rare to find stories with science and discovery at their center. And even if you can find one, they tend to be quite pessimistic and depressing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Project Hail Mary&amp;quot; is a perfect ode to science. It paints an optimistic view of the universe- that it&amp;#39;s not a cold and empty void, that humans and their simple ability to overanalyze the universe could save the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Real life science is hard, it takes years of research and pointless bureaucracy. But most people who pursue science do it for that bit at the end when you finally get the knowledge and understand the universe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Andy Weir has filtered that tiny bit out, and filled a whole book with it.
You just get a sheer joy from using boring, old physics to do monumental things, like saving the human race. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;ve watched the movies &amp;quot;Arrival&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Interstellar&amp;quot;, or played the game &amp;quot;Outer Wilds&amp;quot;, you&amp;#39;ll know what I mean.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么人们如此痴迷于角色并认同他们？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在所有小说中看到的最常见的批评是人们发现
他们无法 "喜欢 "或 "认同 "其中的任何人物。这一点
真的让我很困惑。我并不是说这是一个批评，但这有什么关系呢？
我也不是想笼统地说我的品味更好，而是在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pekya2/why_are_people_so_obsessed_with_character_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pekya2/why_are_people_so_obsessed_with_character_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 06:17:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common criticism I see on this sub of all fiction is that people found themselves unable to ‘like’ or ‘identify’ with any of the characters. This genuinely perplexes me. I don’t mean this as a critic but why does that matter? Nor am I trying to blanket say that my taste is better but in none of my favourite works of fiction would I say that I identify with the characters (except in a few specific examples, and then only briefly). I do like the character of Odysseus for his cunning and charisma but also acknowledge him to be a blood soaked trickster and not a particularly nice person. Crash by J.G. Ballard is one of my favourite novels but I don’t actually identify with people who are sexually aroused by car accidents. Orlando in Virginia Woolf’s novel of the same name is something of a spoilt and neglectful aristocrat entirely focused upon their own wants and whims and yet I love the book.
Why then do others feel they have to like and identify with characters?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[像《荆棘与玫瑰的法庭》，但......更糟糕？]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果以前有人问过这个问题，我很抱歉，但我拿起这个系列是为了有趣的
我拿起这个系列，作为一个有趣的快速逃离，然后就迷上了。现在，当我说更糟糕时......如果你知道我的意思，你
你知道我的意思。

每个人都把它说得很丑陋，也许我已经麻木了，但是......我希望有更多的内容？
我有点希望更多？我喜欢这种幻想...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/peu1yq/like_a_court_of_thorns_roses_but_worse/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/peu1yq/like_a_court_of_thorns_roses_but_worse/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 04:29:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m sorry if this has been asked before, but I picked up this series as a fun quick escape, and got hooked. Now when I say worse… if you know what I mean, you know what I mean. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone made it out to be so scandalous and maybe I’m desensitized but… I was kind of hoping for more? I love the fantasy element but could do with a little extra of that good good. 👀&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[奥威尔的思想在《动物农场》出版75年后仍然适用]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pewv8x/orwells_ideas_remain_relevant_75_years_after/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pewv8x/orwells_ideas_remain_relevant_75_years_after/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2021 04:29:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有什么有重大转折的惊悚书吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜欢她的眼睛后面，并在寻找类似的东西。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/peebq3/any_thriller_books_with_major_twists/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/peebq3/any_thriller_books_with_major_twists/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 17:37:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I loved behind her eyes and was looking for something similar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你喜欢的经典之作是什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[当我年轻的时候，我读了很多书。主要是YA，我读了《饥饿游戏》和《哈利?
波特》系列。然后我在20岁出头的时候停止了阅读。大约在
两年前，我想重新拾起阅读的习惯，于是搜查了我母亲的书柜。
书柜。我借来并阅读了《简-爱》、《呼啸山庄》......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pegpqh/what_do_you_enjoy_about_the_classics/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pegpqh/what_do_you_enjoy_about_the_classics/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 16:10:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was younger I read a lot. Mostly YA and I read the hungergames and Harry Potter series. Then I stopped reading somewhere around my early twenties.
Around two years ago I wanted to pick up the reading habit again and raided my mothers bookcase. I borrowed and read Jane eyre, wuthering heights and gone with the wind. These books got me hooked on books again&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was wondering what other people like about readimg older books  the classic. Stuff like that.
How did you get into them? Just curious.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[那些自豪地讨厌《麦田里的守望者》的人知道它是关于CSA的吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我刚刚读完《麦田里的守望者》，这是第一遍。我们都听说
喜欢这本小说是一个 "红旗"，当男人和年轻男孩喜欢这本小说时，人们似乎会说很多废话。
尤其是男人和年轻男孩喜欢这本小说时，人们似乎说了很多废话。我知道这本书引起了人们的共鸣
我知道这本书引起了一些真正的罪犯的共鸣，他们实施了可怕的暴力行为，所以我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/peiw7o/do_people_who_proudly_hate_on_catcher_in_the_rye/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/peiw7o/do_people_who_proudly_hate_on_catcher_in_the_rye/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 15:17:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just finished reading Catcher in the Rye for the first time. We’ve all heard that liking this novel is a “red flag” and folks seem to talk a lot of shit when men and young boys like this novel especially. I knew this book resonated with some real criminals who enacted awful acts of violence, so I was truly expecting the worst. I was completely shocked by the actual nature of the novel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As someone who works with teens/in youth services, I found Holden heartbreaking. He’s a teenager dealing with depression, isolation, and trauma, both from the loss of his brother and, it’s revealed, childhood sexual abuse/sexual assault. After he evades assault from Mr Antolini, he has a panic response and confesses to the reader: “that kind of stuff&amp;#39;s happened to me about twenty times since I was a kid. I can&amp;#39;t stand it.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I feel like all anybody ever speaks about when it comes to Catcher is how annoying/pretentious Holden is - but isn’t this very obviously a trauma response to unspeakable suffering? The novel’s approach to sexual violence doesn’t even begin and end with Holden - it permeates the novel, from Jane to the sex worker Holden meets to the sexual violence/aggression Holden knows his peers enact against other students and girls he knows. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a really weird “flex” that people think dunking on Holden or readers who identify with him is impressive. Do people realize that CSA survivors, especially boys who are far less likely to speak up about their abuse, may see themselves in Holden? Are they aware that finding Holden annoying for whining or being pretentious or jaded or depressed just perpetuates the idea that the only good victims of abuse are the noble, palatable ones (ie the ones that don’t actually exist outside of movies)? What do y’all think?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[今年上半年印刷书销售量飙升。"印刷品销售在2020年结束时比2019年增长了8.2%，这种强劲的表现持续到2021年，前六个月的单位比2020年的可比时期跃升了18.5%"]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pehone/print_book_sales_soar_in_years_first_half_print/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pehone/print_book_sales_soar_in_years_first_half_print/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 14:54:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[从来不知道阅读是我需要有意识地腾出时间的事情]]></title><description><![CDATA[我以前在大学时，一有时间就拿起书来读。
但现在我已经出来了，而且一直忙于找工作，我没有那么多时间。
我没有那么多时间，而我订购的书也只是堆在我的
桌子上。直到这时我才意识到，我没有像以前那样阅读，我...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pe8u32/never_knew_reading_is_something_i_need_to_make/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pe8u32/never_knew_reading_is_something_i_need_to_make/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 14:16:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to just pickup a book and read whenever I get time when I was in university but now that I&amp;#39;m out and been busy with job hunting and all, I don&amp;#39;t get that much time and the books that I have ordered is just piled up on my table. Only then I realised that I&amp;#39;m not reading like I used to and I need to find time to read them books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[动物农场》是一部长达30,000字的讽刺作品，继承了伊索的野兽寓言的传统，今年已经75岁。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ped1c6/animal_farm_a_30000word_satire_in_the_tradition/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/ped1c6/animal_farm_a_30000word_satire_in_the_tradition/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 11:43:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[乔治-奥威尔的故事比《一九八四》多得多]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/peades/theres_a_lot_more_to_george_orwell_than_nineteen/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/peades/theres_a_lot_more_to_george_orwell_than_nineteen/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 10:56:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一本会让我质疑现实的书。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经没有书可读了。喜欢那些让人彻夜难眠的书]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pdv13e/a_book_that_will_make_me_question_reality/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pdv13e/a_book_that_will_make_me_question_reality/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:52:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m running out of books to read. Love books that keep you up at night&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["ennui "只是无聊的同义词吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我经常看到这个词以类似于这样的方式使用。

> 好人花了多少时间与魔鬼作斗争，这很奇妙。如果他们
> 只需花同样多的精力去爱他们的同伴，魔鬼
> 就会死在他自己的倦怠轨道上
> 
> - 海伦-凯勒，《我生命的故事》。

所以，如果...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdsobl/is_ennui_just_a_synonym_for_boredom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdsobl/is_ennui_just_a_synonym_for_boredom/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:52:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I often see the word used in a way similar to this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It is wonderful how much time good people spend fighting the devil.  If they would only expend the same amount of energy loving their fellow men, the devil would die in his own tracks of ennui  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Hellen Keller, &lt;em&gt;The Story of My Life&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So if we were all nice to each other, the devil wouldn&amp;#39;t have anything to do and would thus be bored.  Isn&amp;#39;t that just plain &amp;#39;ole boredom?  The way I understood ennui is that it&amp;#39;s a specific type of boredom where there is an abundance of potential things to do but despite that, a feeling of boredom persists.   &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s look at a different example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;...as Domitian,&lt;br/&gt;
had wandered through a corridor lined with marble mirrors, looking&lt;br/&gt;
round with haggard eyes for the reflection of the dagger that was to&lt;br/&gt;
end his days, and sick with that ennui, that taedium vitae, that&lt;br/&gt;
comes on those to whom life denies nothing  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Oscar Wilde, &lt;em&gt;The Picture of Dorian Gray&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now this is more inline with my understanding of it.  It reads like a specific type of boredom.  Put another way, a prince could wake up in his palace, wander through his collection of exotic animals and sigh with ennui but on the other side of town the pauper boy picks up his stick that he&amp;#39;s played with for the last 721 days and is just... bored.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any word nerds want to weigh in on this one?   Is ennui just a synonym for boredom or is there more to it?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[真正写得好的谋杀悬疑/惊悚小说]]></title><description><![CDATA[我在寻找翻页的作品，同时也要写得好。我喜欢谋杀悬疑小说
但我发现许多（如果不是大多数）这类书籍都写得很差。
写得很差。

如果有任何关于情节驱动的谋杀推理小说或惊悚小说的推荐，同时也是
谋杀推理小说或惊悚小说，同时又能作为文学作品独立存在的，将是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pe280t/murder_mysteriesthrillers_that_are_actually_well/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pe280t/murder_mysteriesthrillers_that_are_actually_well/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2021 02:40:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m looking for page turners that are also well written. I love murder mysteries in particular, but have found that many (if not most) books in the genre are quite poorly written. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any recommendations for plot-driven murder mysteries or thrillers that also stand on their own as literature would be much appreciated. I’m looking mostly for semi-recent books and am not a fan of spy novels as a rule. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are my thoughts on some books I’ve read that might help with recommendations. Please note that these are just my opinions and good writing is subjective. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Girl with the Dragon Tattoo - Enjoyed this one with caveats. I wasn’t blown away by the writing and find the way Larssen writes about female characters and sexual assaults grating. That said, I think this would be one of the better picks in the genre if Larssen was able to write women well. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The Silent Patient - Found this engaging at points, but thought the writing was sometimes poor and didn’t find the plot plausible. I can suspend my disbelief to a point, but this was just a bit cringe in my opinion. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Magpie Murders - Decent writing, but characters weren’t well developed or engaging. Loved the creative structure of a book within a book, though. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Sharp Objects - Found the writing comically bad&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-2666 - Not really a murder mystery, but is possibly my favorite book of all time and happens to involve a serial killer. I love books like this that are kind of a mindfuck. Please do yourself the favor of reading this! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The Windup Bird Chronicle - A great example of literature that also involves a mystery. I don’t love how Murakami writes women, but he truly is a master of atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你对重读书籍有什么感觉？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜欢回头看我一年或两年甚至更长时间没有读过的书，因为
因为它真的能帮助我确定我的成长。它提醒我小说中的哪些部分是我发现的，因此我当时重视的是什么？
发现引人注目的部分，因此我当时重视的是什么，如果这有意义的话。我还
对这本书本身也有了更深的了解，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdxe8s/how_do_you_feel_about_rereading_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdxe8s/how_do_you_feel_about_rereading_books/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 20:58:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I like to go back to books I haven&amp;#39;t read for a year or two or even more because it really helps me identify my growth. It reminds me what parts of the novel I found striking, therefore what I valued at the time, if that makes sense. I also gain a deeper understanding of the book itself as well, versus the first read. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, I can&amp;#39;t help but feel like I&amp;#39;m &amp;quot;wasting my time&amp;quot; by not exposing myself to new material; there&amp;#39;s hundreds of books on my TBR list and here I am rereading something I&amp;#39;ve already read. Goodreads challenges also add to that race/ competitive feeling. Does anyone have the same thoughts, and how did you get over that feeling of &amp;quot;wasting your time&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[成人幻想系列？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在努力寻找好的/长篇的幻想系列，以便在完成我的TBRs后阅读。
后再读。我无意中发现的大部分都是青少年作品，我想从更成熟的人物角度来阅读。
我想从更成熟的角色角度来阅读。我很喜欢Mass, Harkness, Bardugo,
Aveyard和Tahir，只是举了一个过去系列的例子...。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pduq7d/adult_fantasy_series/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pduq7d/adult_fantasy_series/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:58:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been trying to find good/long fantasy series to read after I finish my TBRs on my bookshelf. Most of what I stumble upon is YA, and I&amp;#39;d like to read from more mature character perspective. I&amp;#39;ve enjoyed Mass, Harkness, Bardugo, Aveyard, and Tahir recently, just to give an example of past series I&amp;#39;ve enjoyed. Any suggestions welcome, thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哪些书应该是必读书目]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很好奇，人们认为哪些书应该属于必读书目。我们
我们都知道，大多数必读书目都是一针见血的，特别是对于青少年和成长中的受众来说。
增长的受众没有太多的经验；你会说什么书进入了你的核心，并对你产生了影响？
你会说什么书能触及你的核心并对你产生影响？

就我个人而言，是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdvzu2/what_books_should_be_required_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdvzu2/what_books_should_be_required_reading/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:46:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m curious to what books people think should fall under required reading.
We all know most required reading is hit and miss especially for adolescent and growing audiences without much experience; what book would you say got to your core and actually had an effect on you?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me personally it was ‘A Monster Calls’.  It had a fantastic story and illustrations to match, while also being extremely relatable to ideas and topics we all face in our lifetime.  It completely blew me away and I am constantly recommending it to my friends, and I think it would be very beneficial to a growing audience in schools&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我已经44岁了，我刚刚发现了有声书。我无法相信这些年来我一直在错过什么。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我已经很老了，我记得当有声书被称为磁带书的时候，它们在马路边的书店里被放在转盘上。
他们是在商场的书店里的旋转木马上。然后它们出现在
光盘。

我从来不认为它们有什么问题，或者它们不是 "真正的 "有声书。
读书"，我只是从来没有喜欢过它们。也许是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdz975/im_44_years_old_and_ive_just_discovered/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdz975/im_44_years_old_and_ive_just_discovered/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:25:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m old enough that I remember when audiobooks were called books on tape, and they were on a carousel in the bookstore at the mall. Then they appeared on compact disc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I never thought there was anything wrong with them, or that they weren&amp;#39;t &amp;quot;real reading&amp;quot;, I just never got into them. Maybe the selection back then was lacking, so it was mostly popular fiction, which isn&amp;#39;t what I usually read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;About five years ago I started working remote location industrial construction jobs and I got a tablet for my 18 hour commute. I got so many magazines from the library that I eventually had to cut my subscriptions in half, I just couldn&amp;#39;t read them all. The same app has audiobooks but I never bothered to check any out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t even know what eventually motivated me to do it, but this year I finally checked one out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life is transformed. Anytime I&amp;#39;m doing something that I used to listen to music for, it&amp;#39;s now audiobooks. If I&amp;#39;m in the kitchen (I live alone), I&amp;#39;ve got an audiobook on. If I go for a walk, I listen to a book. I almost wish I had a commute, so I could listen to more audiobooks. If I could be listening to a book but I&amp;#39;m not, I feel like I&amp;#39;m wasting my time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So far this year I&amp;#39;ve read two physical books but I&amp;#39;m closing in on ten audiobooks and I haven&amp;#39;t even been at it all year. It&amp;#39;s all been during time that I&amp;#39;ve been doing other things. I just feel like I&amp;#39;ve doubled productivity for a large portion of my life. I&amp;#39;ve got 13 more on my holds list and another 120 tagged for interest.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[战争与和平》的前200页是一个缓慢的过程，为该书成为有史以来最伟大的书做了准备。在这200页之后，这本书几乎让人无法放下。]]></title><description><![CDATA[大约一个月前，我读完了列夫-托尔斯泰的《战争与和平》，此前我曾在三个不同的场合试图进入该书。
之前，我曾在三个不同的场合试图进入这本书。这本书绝对令人难以置信，而且
它确实值得被认可为有史以来最伟大的书籍之一。
之一。然而，真正让我感到震惊的是，一旦我克服了这个问题，我就会发现，这本书的内容是如此丰富。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdym1j/the_first_200_pages_of_war_peace_are_a_slog_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdym1j/the_first_200_pages_of_war_peace_are_a_slog_that/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 18:25:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;About a month ago I finished War &amp;amp; Peace by Leo Tolstoy after trying to get into it on 3 separate occasions before. The book is absolutely incredible and genuinely does deserve the recognition it has as one of the greatest books of all time. What really did shock me however, was that once I got over that ~200 page hump, I just couldn&amp;#39;t put it down. I had tried and failed to get that far several times before, but once I got there, it was like I was transferred to an entirely new world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tolstoy has a very unique writing style that is very descriptive without being tedious. The way he described people&amp;#39;s appearances and auras, the way he described the dresses of all the women at the balls, the way he described the actions of everyone made everything feel more real than in any book I had ever read before. This is what makes the book the masterpiece it is, but also why the first ~200 pages are such a slog. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;War &amp;amp; Peace gives you no introduction to the world, the characters, or anything at all. When the book starts, you are just thrown into a dinner party for the Russian elite. The book throws dozens of names at you (many of which don&amp;#39;t actually matter) and it can be extremely overwhelming. However, this was literally the point of that scene. That scene is supposed to feel like you were invited to this party and were just being rapid fire introduced to everyone. You hear out of context arguments, you forget people&amp;#39;s names the moment you are introduced to them, and in general you feel a little like a stranger in this new place. But that is what makes everything feel so real. You meet these new people and overtime you grow to have your own opinions on them. You become emotionally attached to some, you hate others, but this growth is all organic in the same way you would make new friends at a party. As the story progresses, it feels like you are growing with the characters. Every time the perspective changes back to a character, it feels like you are coming to visit your friend and by the end of the book, you feel like you have been through hell and back with them. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When the book ended, I felt emotional because it was like I was saying goodbye to my friends. War &amp;amp; Peace was actually Tolstoy writing a prequel to another book that he never actually ended up finishing, so the characters actually feel like they have so much more of their lives left to live. War &amp;amp; Peace has so many loose plot threads that were clearly supposed to be explored in a sequel, but this just made the book feel so much more real. Those loose threads sort of get discussed in the 1st epilogue, but none of them feel out of place in the world. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you know Russian history, you can even make pretty good guesses of what will happen to the characters going forward. Pierre, for example, is clearly going to be a Decembrist, and his wife (who will remain unnamed for spoiler reasons) is clearly going to become one of the wives of the Decembrists who follows him into exile. The story is so well put together and based in reality to the point where you can know the plot of the non-existent sequel just by knowing Russian history.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[致那些破坏书籍结局和主要情节细节的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[愿你饼干中的巧克力片总是变成葡萄干。

愿那些到你房间和你谈话的人把门稍稍离开
虚掩着，让你不得不起身去关。

愿你的文章在你要点击一个链接时能多加载一点，以便
你点击一个广告...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdx9lq/to_the_people_who_spoil_endings_and_major_plot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdx9lq/to_the_people_who_spoil_endings_and_major_plot/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 17:07:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;May the chocolate chips in your cookies always turn out to be raisins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May the people who come to talk to you in your room leave the door slightly ajar, so that you have to get up and close it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your article load that extra little bit as you&amp;#39;re about to click a link so you click an ad instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May both sides of your pillow be warm.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you forever feel your cellphone vibrating in the pocket it&amp;#39;s not even in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you always get up from your computer with your headphones still attached.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your life be as pleasant as you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your chair produce a sound similar to a fart, but only once, such that you cannot reproduce it to prove that it was just the chair.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you have your laptop charge all night without noticing the chord isn&amp;#39;t plugged in the wall.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you always step in a wet spot after putting on fresh socks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your tea be too hot when you receive it, and too cold by the time you remember it&amp;#39;s there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your cookie always be slightly too large to fit inside your glass of milk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May the pin of the bathroom stall never reach the lock to close the door.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May you never be quite certain whether that pressure is a fart or poop.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May your spoon always slip and sink under the hot soup you eat.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;yours sincerely,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone you’ve spoiled books for.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿瑟-柯南-道尔爵士的《恐惧谷》被严重低估，可能是有史以来最好的神秘小说之一]]></title><description><![CDATA[没有福尔摩斯的后半部分有点不伦不类，现在回想起来会让人对道尔的政治经验不足感到害怕。
道尔的政治经验不足而感到不安。但在前半部分，你可以看到一个精彩的谋杀
但在前半部分，你却得到了一个精彩的谋杀谜团。虽然我认为《巴斯克维尔的猎犬》是一部优秀的小说，但我确实觉得这本书是一部优秀的小说。
优秀的小说，但我确实觉得这部小说更胜一筹。

它被批评为...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdtzxy/sir_arthur_conan_doyles_the_valley_of_fear_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdtzxy/sir_arthur_conan_doyles_the_valley_of_fear_is/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:48:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second half without Holmes is a little eh and in retrospect can make you wince with Doyle’s political inexperience . 
But you get a brilliant murder mystery in the first half. While I found the Hound of the Baskerville to be an excellent novel, I do feel this one is superior. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s criticized as a book that contradicts earlier books, but the contradiction was worth it to get the feline, sinuous villain that did not live up to the hype in previous works.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not sure why it’s not as recognized as it should be honestly.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[[马查多-德-阿西斯的《布拉什-库巴斯遗事》]--这个新译本是重新认识这本用 "欢快的笔和忧郁的墨 "写成的书的乐趣，或第一次发现它的完美机会。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdtsv7/the_posthumous_memoirs_of_brás_cubas_by_machado/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdtsv7/the_posthumous_memoirs_of_brás_cubas_by_machado/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 15:34:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[到目前为止，您的年度最佳读物!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我一直在回忆今年到目前为止我读过的书，试图挑选我最喜欢的书。
我的最爱。

虽然我喜欢其中的大多数，但有些书绝对是引人注目的。

达夫内-杜穆里埃的《丽贝卡》（所有时间的新宠）。

詹姆斯-鲍德温的《乔瓦尼的房间》（文笔非常好！）。

多里安的肖像》(The portrait of Dorian...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdswmw/your_top_reads_of_the_year_so_far/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdswmw/your_top_reads_of_the_year_so_far/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 13:52:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been reminiscing about the books I&amp;#39;ve read so far this year, trying to pick my favorites. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although I&amp;#39;ve enjoyed most of them, some definitely stood out:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rebecca&lt;/em&gt; by Daphné du Maurier (A new all time favorite)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Giovanni&amp;#39;s Room&lt;/em&gt; by James Baldwin (The writing is EXQUISITE!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The portrait of Dorian Gray&lt;/em&gt; by Oscar Wild (A must re read!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;How about you? What are you top reads of 2021 so far?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我和我的曾祖母读完了《悲惨世界》!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是Reddit的新成员，认为这是一个完美的故事，所以在这里分享
我的曾祖母在法国出生，部分时间在法国长大，十几岁时随家人移居到美国。
在她十几岁的时候和她的家人一起移居美国。当她长大后，阅读《Les
米斯》一直是她的头等大事，因为她有好几个朋友都是在法国长大的。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdnm9m/i_finished_reading_les_miserables_with_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdnm9m/i_finished_reading_les_miserables_with_my/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 29 Aug 2021 05:13:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m new to Reddit and thought this was the perfect story to share, so here goes!
My great-grandmother was born and partly raised in France before moving to America with her family in her teenage years. When she became older, reading Les Mis was always on the top of her bucket list as multiple of her friends were reading it and she wanted to read a novel that was based where she once lived. She finally got to it in her elderly years and was making great progress (she was about 400 pages in) when she had a sudden stroke and was rushed to the hospital, where she remained for some time. Once she was well enough to go home and live with a caretaker, I took it upon myself to help her finish what she had started and read Les Miserables to her on the phone whenever she was feeling well enough that day to listen. We finished reading it just yesterday, and I’m so happy that I could help her with a long term goal. She’s one of the strongest women I know and I’m so happy I could bond with her even more this way!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[刚读完ASOIAF的所有5本书，接下来我应该读什么？]]></title><description><![CDATA[阅读ASOIAF的所有5本书对我来说是一项艰巨的任务，但我真的很喜欢它们。
它们。我的阅读速度很慢，我经常只读几页就睡着了。
所以这花了我好几年时间。在我读完这些书之后，我又读了《七国骑士》。
七大王国的骑士》，我也非常喜欢。我现在正在寻找...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pdckxt/just_finished_reading_all_5_asoiaf_books_what/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pdckxt/just_finished_reading_all_5_asoiaf_books_what/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 23:52:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reading all 5 ASOIAF books was a monumental task for me, but I really enjoyed them.  I am a slow reader, and I often fall asleep after reading just a few pages, so this took me a couple years.  After I finished them, I read A Knight of the Seven Kingdoms which I also really enjoyed.  I am now looking for my next book.  Would like it to be a nice easy read, and something that is &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; in the medieval fantasy genre.  My interests are sci-fi, time travel, mystery, twist-endings.  Suggestions?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我希望有一本能让我傻笑的书。]]></title><description><![CDATA[它不一定是最好的写作，也不一定有那么多的意义，我只是
我只是希望有一些充满光明和欢乐的东西。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pdd84i/i_would_like_a_book_that_makes_me_giggle/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pdd84i/i_would_like_a_book_that_makes_me_giggle/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 22:21:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t have to be the best writing, or mean that much in the end, I just want something full of light and joy.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[巴西囚犯阅读书籍以缩短刑期]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdanpi/brazil_prisoners_reading_books_to_shorten_their/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdanpi/brazil_prisoners_reading_books_to_shorten_their/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 17:04:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我将不再阅读正在进行的系列中的任何内容。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我看到有人推荐了一本漫画书，作者不是别人，正是GRRM本人。这本
漫画叫《传奇》，非常好。它在某种程度上是《星球大战》和《权力的游戏》的结合。
的方式。我认为这是一个完整的系列，因为它开始于2012年，但它是
但从2018年开始，它处于停播状态，只完成了50%。任何书或系列...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdbmi8/i_will_no_longer_read_anything_in_an_ongoing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pdbmi8/i_will_no_longer_read_anything_in_an_ongoing/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 16:39:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I saw a recommendation of a comic book by none other than GRRM himself. The comic is called Saga and it&amp;#39;s very good. It&amp;#39;s star wars meets game of thrones in a way. Annd I thought it was a complete series since it started in 2012 but it&amp;#39;s on hiatus as of 2018 and only 50% complete. Any book or series for me will have to be completed before I begin. I just can&amp;#39;t have so many incomplete stories (kingkiller, gentlemen bastards, asoiaf,) and be left with the cliff hangers. Or am I wrong and hurting new authors for having their first book in a series be ignored because its only the beginning?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你是否曾被书中的一个小事件或细节吓了一跳？以一种真正让你重新思考问题的方式？]]></title><description><![CDATA[扎迪-史密斯的《白牙》在书的开头介绍了阿奇-琼斯。
出于某种原因，我真的被他的故事、他的生活（正如我们所知道的）抛到了脑后。
他的故事，他的生活，正如我们所知，是从45岁开始的。

故事的开头是他试图结束自己的生命，但却无法进行下去
因为......。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pd49b1/have_you_ever_been_taken_aback_by_a_minor_event/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pd49b1/have_you_ever_been_taken_aback_by_a_minor_event/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 15:33:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;White Teeth by Zadie Smith introduces Archie Jones in the beginning of the book and for some reason I was really thrown back for the fact that his story, his life as we know, it begins at the age of 45. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It begins with him trying to end his life, but couldn&amp;#39;t go through with it because of a the halal market owner shooing Archie and his car away from his store. Then quickly meets his future wife, a young Jamaican woman at an end of the world party with no apocalypse to justify it. The story plays a lot with time and history having characters of different ages and backgrounds at different periods in the 20th century. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having these two characters interact at very different periods of their lives having been intent on not living the next day was crazy for me to think about. It made me feel vastly better about the period of life I am and that I still have a lot of time to do the things I want to do. I was 21 when I read it (26 now) but I was having a lot of anxiety about falling behind in life. Being stuck in prison in the wake of a traumatic event will do that to you. My life was literally on hold, actually, worse than that. It was set back. I&amp;#39;m still working hard to get to where I want to be in life having been out 4 and a half years at this point. But, that concept in the beginning and throughout the book, makes me feel that I shouldn&amp;#39;t worry about it. Since, why do I have to be a certain age to do or be something? Life is chaotic and our impacts on it are often unforseen. Best not to stress it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love the book. It takes a look at the lives of it&amp;#39;s characters that is organic and very recognizable. The way Smith finds some humor in the difficult parts of life and the history that shapes it was very therapeutic to me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[阿富汗作家纳迪亚-哈希米第二次失去了她的祖国]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pd8fyt/an_afghan_author_nadia_hashimi_on_losing_her/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pd8fyt/an_afghan_author_nadia_hashimi_on_losing_her/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 14:27:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["类似Bridgerton "的书，但没有那么多的情色小说？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜欢朱莉娅-奎因的任何作品。我认为她的文字很美，而且
我喜欢她写人物的方式。我真的希望有更多像她那样的浪漫小说
像她那样的爱情小说，但没有所有血腥的细节。我不是在谈论一本假正经的YA
小说，我只是不想让人觉得我是在阅读完全......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pcxjv2/bridgertonlike_book_but_not_as_much_of_an_erotica/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pcxjv2/bridgertonlike_book_but_not_as_much_of_an_erotica/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 07:29:14 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I LOVE just about anything by Julia Quinn. I think her writing is beautiful and I love the way she writes her characters. I’m really wanting more romance novels like hers, but without all the gory details. I’m not talking about a prudish, YA novel, I just don’t want to feel like I’m reading total smut. Any recommendations ????&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最近放慢了我的阅读速度--它使事情变得更好了]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好!

我18岁时参加的一个大学预科班，由大学教授，有一个
速读课程。从那时起，13年过去了，我看到了这样的趋势
我看到速读的趋势急剧上升，并多次尝试学习速读。

然而，最近我有一个感悟，我有...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcqh6a/recently_slowed_down_my_reading_and_its_changed/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcqh6a/recently_slowed_down_my_reading_and_its_changed/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 05:28:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A college prep class, taught by the university, that I took when I was 18 had a speed reading course.  Since then, 13 years have passed, I’ve seen the trend of speed reading skyrocket and have tried multiple times to learn speed reading.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, recently I had a realization that I had read an entire book and felt like I only really comprehended half of what I had read.  So I decided to slow down my reading and really enjoy every page instead of treating my reading like a sprint I would treat it more like a marathon.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What I’ve come to realize is that my reading comprehension goes up when I slow down my reading and read at a pace that’s comfortable for me.  I also feel like I get a lot more enjoyment out of my reading as well as I’m not attempting to rush through it.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else had this experience?  Is there a reason that this could be the case?  What does the research say?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By the way, some people could be really great speed readers and that could be your preferred style!  That’s ok too.  I just want to remind people that going against trends or against the grain is ok if it works for you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[哇哦。阅读实际上是一种乐趣，它拯救了我的生活。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我从小就不喜欢读书。被迫阅读是非常痛苦的。而且
当我阅读时，我很难理解所读的内容。它
我花了很长时间才读完一本书，因为我太容易失去注意力了。
因为我经常失去注意力，不得不重读一些段落。

我目前正在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pd2g8k/wow_reading_is_actually_fun_and_it_saved_my_life/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pd2g8k/wow_reading_is_actually_fun_and_it_saved_my_life/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 05:14:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I never liked reading growing up. And being forced to read was excruciating. And when I did read, I had a lot of difficulty comprehending what was being read. It would take me forever to finish a book because I would lose attention too frequently and have to reread passages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m currently going through a traumatic breakup among other major life changes and always told myself that when I have more free time to try reading again. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved to a new place - alone for the first time in a long time and I had trouble being alone with my thoughts and being terrified (still am but less so) with moments of silence of having my thoughts race around in my head.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I filled that time with reading. And maybe perhaps it’s because I’m still in such a profound emotional and vulnerable state that anything can elicit great mood changes but the past two books I’ve read really resonated me and have sparked some sort of rediscovery that I feel has changed my core personality to be a better person and understanding my self worth and my faults.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I now look forward to reading. I can actually laugh and cry and feel emotion through words! I CAN FINALLY SAY “THE BOOK WAS SO MUCH BETTER THAN THE MOVIE”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I even decided to get rid of my tv and I now spend a lot of my time reading instead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought a nice bookshelf and I am so excited to start filling it up with books I’ve read, and it serving as a visual aid in all the journeys I’ve gone through these books and the stories I can share with other people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The two books that changed my life:
1. The Brief Wondrous Life of Oscar Wao - was hard to get into at first but I really like the style of writing specifically the authors Prose. 
2. Tuesdays with Morrie. - very uplifting and really made me think my outlook on certain things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[(血色子午线》剧透）我知道在湖泊中的孩子发生了什么事]]></title><description><![CDATA[我知道，因为麦卡锡告诉我们。霍尔登把孩子 "抱在怀里，顶着他的
巨大而可怕的肉体"。血色子午线》的秘密在于：它正是
它就是它所呈现的样子。没有任何神秘之处。经过多次阅读，我已经知道
答案就在书中。

我们知道什么是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcw8et/blood_meridian_spoilers_i_know_what_happened_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcw8et/blood_meridian_spoilers_i_know_what_happened_to/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 03:34:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know because McCarthy tells us. Holden takes the kid &amp;quot;in his arms against his immense and terrible flesh.&amp;quot; The secret of Blood Meridian is this: it is exactly what it appears to be. There is no mystery. After many readings, I&amp;#39;ve learned that the answers are on the page.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do we know about the Judge? He is freakishly huge and immensely strong. We see him crush a man&amp;#39;s skull between his massive hands. We see him lift an immense iron meteorite and throw it 11 feet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is how the kid died. He was enveloped utterly by this... thing. And &lt;strong&gt;crushed&lt;/strong&gt;. That was Holden&amp;#39;s will, to consume and envelope this apostate wholly, like the darkness McCarthy is so preoccupied by.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Judge took the kid into his flesh, and crushed him entirely. Imagine the scene in those jakes. A body reduced to a mutilated horror of blood and bone, barely human in shape. A pile of gore, brains exploded through the skull, torso crushed and misshapen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The witnesses wouldn&amp;#39;t be able to comprehend what they were seeing. &amp;quot;Oh my god&amp;quot; would be the only appropriate response. One witness asks &amp;quot;what is it?&amp;quot; They cannot be certain that the remains are even human.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is commonly believed that the killing was sexual in nature due to Holden&amp;#39;s nakedness. Yet he is frequently naked throughout the novel. It is not inherently sexual. Holden is a child murderer and pederast, but there is no indication that he would rape a grown man.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Holden&amp;#39;s nakedness is Biblical. &lt;strong&gt;A thing naked is a thing revealed&lt;/strong&gt;. The Judge is unveiled in those jakes, and swallows the kid (now the man) into his flesh, leaving some unrecognizable, bloodied mass of flesh and shattered bone lying on the floor of that outhouse.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我正在寻找最令人沮丧的书]]></title><description><![CDATA[我需要一本能让我质疑自己生活的书。一些压抑的、有
很多关于人类行为的思考。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pctl92/im_looking_for_the_most_depressing_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pctl92/im_looking_for_the_most_depressing_book/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 03:17:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I need a book that will make me question my life. Something depressing, with a lot of thoughts about human behaviors ig?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[一个你无法进入的书的类型。]]></title><description><![CDATA[你是否曾有过这样一种书的类型，你就是无法进入，无论你尝试多少次，都无法进入。
次。它可能是恐怖、犯罪、科幻的任何东西。

对我来说，它必须是任何种类的幻想。我只是无法接受十本书的系列和
我只是无法接受十本书的系列和数千页的篇幅，以及众多名字古怪的人物......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcnnwy/a_book_genre_you_just_couldnt_get_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcnnwy/a_book_genre_you_just_couldnt_get_into/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 02:41:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Have you ever had a book genre you just couldn’t get into, no matter how many times you tried. It could be horror, crime, sci fi anything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For me it’s got to be any kind of fantasy. I just couldn’t get with the ten book series and the thousands of pages and the numerous characters with odd names you had to keep track off. Not to mention the many subplots. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But what about you guys?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你会把未读的书和已读的书分开保存吗？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很快就要重新整理我的书架了，我正在考虑不同的整理方式。
组织方式。

目前我把未读的书放在一个单独的书架上，我想知道这有多
这很常见。

你通常是把已读和未读的书混在一起，还是把未读的书
还是把未读的书分开，只把它们放到你的书架上？]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcww5t/do_you_keep_your_unread_books_separate_from_those/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcww5t/do_you_keep_your_unread_books_separate_from_those/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 02:15:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll be reorganising my shelves soon and I’m thinking about different styles of organisation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently I keep a separate shelf for unread books and I was wondering how common that was. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you usually mix your read and unread books, or do you keep unread books separate and only add them to your ‘regular’ shelf once you finish them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[晚了54年，多萝西-帕克终于得到了一块墓碑]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcokf9/54_years_late_dorothy_parker_finally_gets_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcokf9/54_years_late_dorothy_parker_finally_gets_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 22:50:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[武藏]]></title><description><![CDATA[这本书真的很好。我没有很多人喜欢同类型的书，也没有人读过这本书。
书或像我一样阅读，或至少开始阅读。我已经看了一半了
书。他开始学习生活，似乎他正在接受越来越多的
越来越多地了解他周围的环境。我喜欢这本书的发展方向....]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pclqul/musashi/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pclqul/musashi/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:56:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book is really good. I don’t have many folks that into the same type of books or read like I do or at least started to. I am about half way through the book. He is starting to learn to live and it seems like he is taking in more and more of his surroundings. I like where this book is going. Thanks for reading this.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有神经分裂者角色的书？]]></title><description><![CDATA[因此，正如标题所示，我正在寻找一本其中一个（或多个）角色有注意力缺陷/多动症/自闭症等的书。
角色有注意力缺失症/多动症/自闭症等。我不久前被诊断出患有ADD
前，我只是想看看有哪些形式的代表。
并看看其他人是如何体验的。
我更喜欢虚构的书，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pcn5d8/book_with_neurodivergent_character/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/pcn5d8/book_with_neurodivergent_character/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 21:17:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, as the title suggests, I am looking for a book where one (or more) of the characters has ADD/ADHD/Autism, etc. I got diagnosed with ADD a little while ago, and I kinda just want to see what forms of representation are out there, and see how other people experience it.&lt;br/&gt;
I prefer fictional books, but non-fiction is also welcome.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我刚刚完成了斯蒂芬-金的《站立》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[哦。我的。天啊。这是我读过的第一部SK作品，让我告诉你，它不会是
不会是最后一部。这本书让我一直处在座位的边缘。
为书中的人物欢呼雀跃，并在书的结尾处潸然泪下。这一章
当斯图躺在峡谷里，准备去找他的时候。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcpmrg/i_just_finished_the_stand_by_stephen_king/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcpmrg/i_just_finished_the_stand_by_stephen_king/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 17:54:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh. My. God. This is the first SK work I have ever read, and let me tell you, it won’t be the last. This book had me on the edge of my seat the entire time, cheering for the characters and flat out crying by the end of it. The chapter near the end when Stu is laying in the ravine, getting ready to die, I had to keep my eyes from jumping ahead, just hoping with all of my heart that Tom was going to find him. The description of their journey back to Boulder was just so heartwarming. I am definitely having the “after finishing a really good book” depression lol. Please tell me I’m not the only one who gets this feeling after finishing an amazing read. What did you think of this book and what are your favorite Stephen King works?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么有些人需要与一个角色发生关系，才能发现他们是令人信服的？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我见过有人以他们无法与主人公产生共鸣为借口批评书籍。
主角。有时我看到人们在看完一本书后就完全停止了。
因为同样的原因。我明白，其中一个因素是通过一个与自己相似的人物在这个虚构的世界里生活。
虚构的世界中，通过一个与你思想相似的人物来生活，但是......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcmqvj/why_do_some_people_need_to_relate_to_a_character/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcmqvj/why_do_some_people_need_to_relate_to_a_character/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 14:30:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve seen people criticize books with the excuse that they couldn&amp;#39;t relate to the protagonist. Sometimes ive seen people completely stop midway through a book for that same reason. I get that one element is to live vicariously in this fictional world through a character of similar mind to you, but is that the only way to enjoy a book? Is that the main draw? There are times when ive read books where i cant relate to any of the characters but the characters (whilst completely crazy and the opposite of me) are fascinating. Sometimes the draw for the book isnt necessarily the characters themselves but a more broader picture of how all the different pieces in the plot come together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I honestly think those who only look for &amp;#39;likeable&amp;#39; characters or characters they can relate to are narrowing their selection and missing out on a lot of great books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[为什么这么多Goodreads评论只是简单地回顾书籍，而没有评论？]]></title><description><![CDATA[就像标题所说的那样。这种情况在不太受欢迎的书中似乎很猖獗，它
这让我非常生气。就像，伙计，我刚读完整本书，就来听
别人对它的想法。是什么促使人们留下 "评论 "呢？
例如，我刚刚读完《西藏七年》，并且...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcjfec/why_are_so_many_goodreads_reviews_simply_recaps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/pcjfec/why_are_so_many_goodreads_reviews_simply_recaps/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2021 13:41:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just like the title says. This seems to be rampant for less popular books and it enrages me to no end. Like, dude, I just read the whole book and came to hear someone else&amp;#39;s thoughts on it. What even motivates people to leave &amp;#39;reviews&amp;#39; like this (for example I just finished &amp;#39;7 years in Tibet&amp;#39; and realized that half the reviews were devoid of all substance and the other half were just &amp;#39;so then this happened in the book&amp;#39;)?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyway, that&amp;#39;s my rant. Does anyone have other good sites for book reviews where I won&amp;#39;t simply be bombarded with SparkNotes? Thanks in advance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>