<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Buzzing 读书]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览读书，荐书相关的讨论]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 01:15:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[zh-Hant]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[關於二戰後日本的書籍的推薦 🇯🇵]]></title><description><![CDATA[尋求與日本歷史有關的書籍的推薦。
第二次世界大戰結束後。如重建，在冷戰中的作用
在冷戰中的作用，政治氣候，等等。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o3l34n/recommendations_on_books_written_about_postwwii/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o3l34n/recommendations_on_books_written_about_postwwii/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 21:57:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeking recommendations on books pertaining to Japanese history immediately following the conclusion of the Second World War. Such as re-construction, role in the Cold War, political climate, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[閱讀是一種天賦]]></title><description><![CDATA[當我還是個孩子時，我是一個狂熱的讀者，主要是因爲我的父親是。當他
死後，我無法長時間坐在書前，無法完全沉浸其中。爲什麼呢，我也不知道。

最近我拿起了《哈利-波特》這本書，這是我小時候和他一起讀的書。
小時候讀的。我開始意識到書是多麼美妙，迷失在...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3n1sa/reading_is_a_gift/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3n1sa/reading_is_a_gift/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 20:32:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I was a kid I was an avid reader, primarily because my dad was. When he died I couldn’t sit with a book long enough to fully dive in. Why, I don’t know.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I picked up the Harry Potter books, it was what I read with him as a kid. I began to realise how wonderful books are, getting lost in a little world and feeling empathy and compassion for other people. I have always had unhealthy coping mechanisms and now I refuse to dabble in drink or drugs because I need a clear mind to read! It’s wonderful. It’s a gift I’m grateful he introduced me to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[威廉-霍奇森的 "邊疆之家"]]></title><description><![CDATA[這本書自始至終都有一種緩慢的、令人不安的怪異感，而到了最後，一切都突然崩潰了。
突然在結尾處，一切都戲劇性地坍塌了。這是一本非常沉重的書，但
很值得一讀。詩歌很美，霍奇森的寫作風格很好。
鮮明的。只是想把它扔出去!

要麼接受，要麼離開...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3blzj/house_on_the_borderland_by_william_hodgson/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3blzj/house_on_the_borderland_by_william_hodgson/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:54:05 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This book has a slow-going unsettling weirdness to it all throughout, and suddenly at the end everything collapses theatrically. A very heavy book, but well worth the read. The poetry is beautiful and Hodgson&amp;#39;s writing style is distinguishable. Just wanted to throw it out there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take it or leave it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我在閱讀《火星人》時感到非常愉快]]></title><description><![CDATA[自從我看了《火星人》這部電影后，我就一直想讀這本書。
最後我讀了它。我不得不說，這是我讀過的最有趣的一本書。
因爲我喜歡天文學、美國國家航空航天局和所有與太空有關的東西。

當然，書中的一些情節似乎很牽強，比如......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3jrvy/i_had_an_absolute_blast_reading_the_martian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3jrvy/i_had_an_absolute_blast_reading_the_martian/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 18:29:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had been thinking about reading The Martian ever since I watched the movie and finally I read it. And I have to say, this is the most fun I&amp;#39;ve had reading a book &amp;#39;cause I&amp;#39;m into astronomy, NASA and all things space related.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Granted some of the scenarios in the book seem far-fetched like the reason the astronauts had non frozen potatoes on Mars with them. But hey, I had fun while reading it so it doesn&amp;#39;t really matter to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book made me laugh out loud multiple times. Andy Weir&amp;#39;s wit is amazing. Also I&amp;#39;ve seen some people complain about how Mark just effortlessly solves any problem that comes up. But I don&amp;#39;t think it&amp;#39;s effortless &amp;#39;cause we get to know what he did through logs so imo he won&amp;#39;t put the entire process of thinking and whatnot in the log. He tells us precisely how he solved the problem and what difficulties he had to face along with compromises that had to be made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What was your experience reading The Martian? 
PS: I&amp;#39;m now halfway through On Earth We&amp;#39;re Briefly Gorgeous by Ocean Vuong and I&amp;#39;m absolutely loving it and his way of writing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[沙丘》重新點燃了我對閱讀的熱愛]]></title><description><![CDATA[一個多月前，我和一些朋友一起參觀了主街的一家書店。
在主街上的一家剛剛開業的書店。我不一定想去那裏，但是我
但我還是跟他們進去了。我沒有看到什麼太有趣的東西，這是自高中以來的情況。
從高中開始就是這樣，那時候我覺得我的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3inkb/dune_reignited_my_love_for_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3inkb/dune_reignited_my_love_for_reading/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 17:12:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A little over a month ago, I was with some friends and we visited a book store on Main Street that had just opened. I didn&amp;#39;t necessarily wanna go there, but I went in with them regardless. I didn&amp;#39;t see anything too interesting, which had been the case since high school, which is when I felt my passion for reading dwindle off until it eventually died. But I did notice something in there, promotional area for the series of Dune. I had heard of it, especially since they are making a movie about it, but I had no idea what it was about. I looked it up, saw it was a science fiction series from the 1960s and thought &amp;quot;Might as well&amp;quot; in regards to trying it out. A month and 600 pages later, the passion is back. I now find myself making a list of books I want to read, which I haven&amp;#39;t done since middle school.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are there any books that reignited your love for reading as an adult?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尋找一個維多利亞時代的神祕故事，但比夏洛克更冒昧。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我喜歡夏洛克，我對一些有情緒的、神祕的、以維多利亞時代爲主題的文學感興趣。
文學作品，我不介意它比道爾的寫作更冒昧一些。這裏正在
我認爲這本書非常合適。謝謝你!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o34oic/looking_for_a_victorian_mystery_but_more_risqué/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o34oic/looking_for_a_victorian_mystery_but_more_risqué/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 14:44:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I loved Sherlock and I’m interested in some moody, mystery, Victorian themed lit, I don’t mind if it’s a little more risqué than Doyle’s writing. It’s raining here and I think this would fit perfectly. Merci!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[只是我用 "華氏451 "做的一些書畫作品]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3f56p/just_some_book_art_i_made_with_fahrenheit_451/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3f56p/just_some_book_art_i_made_with_fahrenheit_451/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 14:21:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[火星人]]></title><description><![CDATA[我很高興終於要開始這個項目了！！。任何認識我的人都知道
我對太空和NASA很着迷，爲了看火箭會熬夜到凌晨3點。
或國際空間站的太空漫步。而且我非常想念我的電視丈夫戈多-史蒂文斯。
所以這將是一個值得歡迎的分散注意力的機會

劇情簡介：六天前，...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o3e1n9/the_martian/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o3e1n9/the_martian/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 13:51:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m so excited to FINALLY be starting this one!! Anyone who knows me knows that I&amp;#39;m obsessed with space and NASA and will stay up until 3am to watch a rocket launch or ISS space walk. And I desperately miss my tv husband, Gordo Stevens, so this will be a welcome distraction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SYNOPSIS: Six days ago, astronaut Mark Watney became one of the first people to walk on Mars. Now, he&amp;#39;s sure he&amp;#39;ll be the first person to die there. After a dust storm nearly kills him and forces his crew to evacuate while thinking him dead, Mark finds himself stranded and completely alone with no way to even signal Earth that he&amp;#39;s alive and even if he could get word out, his supplies would be gone long before a rescue could arrive. Chances are, though, he won&amp;#39;t have time to starve to death. The damaged machinery, unforgiving environment, or plain-old &amp;quot;human error&amp;quot; are much more likely to kill him first. But Mark isn&amp;#39;t ready to give up yet. Drawing on his ingenuity, his engineering skills and a relentless, dogged refusal to quit-he steadfastly confronts one seemingly insurmountable obstacle after the next. Will his resourcefulness be enough to overcome the impossible odds against him?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尋找類似《禁閉島》的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[有趣的、快節奏的、有扣人心絃的故事線和巨大的情節轉折的東西。
巨大的情節轉折]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o39cni/looking_for_a_book_like_shutter_island/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o39cni/looking_for_a_book_like_shutter_island/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 13:10:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something that is interesting and fast paced with a gripping story line and massive plot twist&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[時空之輪》賞析（請勿劇透]]></title><description><![CDATA[嘿，夥計們，我只是想在剛剛開始《世界之眼》的時候插上一腳。
我得說，與其他人所說的第一個故事很慢相反
或其他什麼... 我真的很喜歡它。

我過去曾嘗試閱讀J.R.R.托爾金的作品，也曾嘗試閱讀GoT的作品。
真的，真的很喜歡...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3btuo/wheel_of_time_appreciation_please_no_spoilers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o3btuo/wheel_of_time_appreciation_please_no_spoilers/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 12:37:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, I just wanted to chime in having just started Eye of the World and I gotta say, contrary to what everyone else said about the first story being slow or whatever... I&amp;#39;m really loving it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have tried to read both J.R.R. Tolkien in the past as well as GoT and I really, really am enjoying this kind of writing. It&amp;#39;s descriptive but not overwhelmingly so with such a huge focus on language and it throws in lore but it doesn&amp;#39;t inundate you with so much intrigue and mystery that you don&amp;#39;t know what&amp;#39;s going on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m only on chapter 8 but I already feel very invested in this story. I&amp;#39;m really looking forward to this series and I&amp;#39;m super glad I didn&amp;#39;t decide not to pick it up because of it&amp;#39;s length, the &amp;quot;slog&amp;quot; halfway through, or the general disdain aimed at the first couple books.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你喜歡哪些與你的意識形態/信仰不同甚至相反的書籍？]]></title><description><![CDATA[對我來說，我想提出，除其他外，瑪麗蓮-羅賓遜的《吉利德》。我是
我對宗教歷史和神學感興趣，而
這部小說與深刻而充滿活力的真正的信仰感和與基督教的個人聯繫密不可分。
個人與基督教的聯繫。這也是一個...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o33dip/what_are_some_books_you_love_with/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o33dip/what_are_some_books_you_love_with/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 05:43:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For me I would put forth, among others, Marilynne Robinson&amp;#39;s &lt;em&gt;Gilead&lt;/em&gt;. I&amp;#39;m interested in religious history and theology from a historical perspective while this novel is inextricable from a deep and vibrant sense of genuine faith and a personal connection to  Christianity. It&amp;#39;s also one of the most thought-provoking, stirring, and beautifully written novels I&amp;#39;ve ever read in my life.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What are some novels that you either disagreed with or were extremely disconnected from in themes but you regard as great?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我重讀了一本我在高中時討厭的書，並愛上了它。]]></title><description><![CDATA[在我十年級的英語課上，我們被分配到雷-布拉德伯裏的《Farenheiht 451》。
課堂上，我們被安排閱讀雷-布萊德伯裏的《法倫希特451》。我記得我並不完全喜歡它。我也不喜歡讀威廉-戈爾丁的《蠅王》。
那年我也不喜歡讀威廉-戈爾丁的《蒼蠅王》）。)

我現在30歲了。我決定重讀這本書，看看我是否仍然不喜歡它，或者是否是
是我的問題...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o2sk6z/i_reread_a_book_i_hated_in_high_school_and_fell/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o2sk6z/i_reread_a_book_i_hated_in_high_school_and_fell/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 19:58:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We were assigned “Farenheiht 451” by Ray Bradbury in my 10th grade English class. I remember not enjoying it all. (I also did not enjoy reading “Lord of the Flies” by William Golding that year either)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m 30 now. I decided to reread it to see if I still did not enjoy it, or if it was a case of me being 16. I just finished it, and I was surprised how much I enjoyed it. I do not think that 16 year old me appreciated it, but 30 year old me whose working on her PhD in history definitely does. I am really glad that I took a chance on it and reread it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever reread books from high school that you did not like and ended up enjoying the second time?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[在自我幫助、自我發展、抗焦慮等方面有哪些好書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個非常焦慮、懶惰的人，我想變得更加自信，不那麼依賴社交媒體，並且更有效率。
對社交媒體的依賴，並提高工作效率。我想過一種更有意義的生活。
我已經20多歲了。我想少喝酒，等等。你有什麼文學作品嗎？
可以對我產生積極的影響嗎？

謝謝!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o2ota3/what_are_the_best_books_on_self_help_self/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o2ota3/what_are_the_best_books_on_self_help_self/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 18:33:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m a really anxious, lazy person who’d like to be more confident, less reliant on social media and more productive. I want to live a more meaningful life now that I’m in my 20s. I want to drink less, etc. Do you have any literature recommendations that could influence me positively  ? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[以其尖銳的判斷和對新聞業無情的看法而聞名的《紐約客》的長期作家珍妮特-馬爾科姆已經去世。她今年86歲。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o21pcw/janet_malcolm_a_longtime_writer_for_the_new/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o21pcw/janet_malcolm_a_longtime_writer_for_the_new/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 14:13:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[讓我們討論一下哈里特-雅各布斯是如何通過她的寫作挑戰她那個時代的親奴隸制理想的。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o2j854/lets_discuss_how_harriet_jacobs_challenged_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o2j854/lets_discuss_how_harriet_jacobs_challenged_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 11:18:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[最令人不安的恐怖書籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[有哪些最令人不安的恐怖故事。我正在尋找
那些能誘發噩夢的書，但不是斯蒂芬-金的書。謝謝
任何有建議的人。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o268a9/most_disturbing_horror_books/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o268a9/most_disturbing_horror_books/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 02:21:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;What are some of the most disturbing horror stories out there. I&amp;#39;m looking for books that are nightmare inducing, but aren&amp;#39;t Stephen King books. Thanks to anyone who has suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[幫我找一本《懲罰》的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是一個每週圖書播客的聯合主持人，我們從2017年開始做這個播客，我正在尋找
尋找一種非常特殊的書。通常情況下，我們閱讀經典、暢銷書等。
但在我們的聖誕節目中，我們會給對方買一本特別的書。我們試圖找到一本
書來懲罰其他傢伙。聖誕節是特別的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o1xik6/help_my_find_a_punishment_book/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o1xik6/help_my_find_a_punishment_book/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 17:52:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I co-host a weekly book podcast that we&amp;#39;ve been doing since 2017 and I&amp;#39;m looking for a very specific kind of book.  Normally we read classics, bestsellers, etc but for our Christmas episode we buy each other a special book.  We try to find a book to punish the other guys with.  Christmastime is special and not just anything will do.  We try to find something that&amp;#39;s fairly well-known but also as weird, off-putting, unsettling, offensive and/or terrible as we can find.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Out past books have been&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bear&lt;/em&gt; by Marian Engel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ass Goblins of Auschwitz&lt;/em&gt; by Cameron Pierce&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cows&lt;/em&gt; by Matthew Stokoe&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Life in the Fat Lane&lt;/em&gt; by Cherie Bennett&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pounded in the Butt by my own Butt&lt;/em&gt; by Chuck Tingle&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Dianetics&lt;/em&gt; by L. Ron Hubbard&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The holidays are a while away but this is an important decision and I need time to think about the absolute worst thing I can find that will also be fun to make fun of and make for an episode people might want to listen to.  Any help would be greatly appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[英國圖書館和博物館聯合起來，從私人買家手中拯救 "驚人的 "失落圖書館]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1tlv9/uk_libraries_and_museums_unite_to_save/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1tlv9/uk_libraries_and_museums_unite_to_save/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 11:48:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[消失的勺子》：一本令人愉快的驚喜之書]]></title><description><![CDATA[我剛剛讀完薩姆-基恩的《消失的勺子和其他真實》。
消失的勺子和其他關於瘋狂、愛情以及從元素週期表看世界歷史的真實故事。
元素週期表中的瘋狂、愛情和世界歷史的真實故事（這個書名很拗口），我想與你們分享我是多麼喜歡這本書。
我很喜歡這本書。

我是一時興起在巴恩斯書店買的這本書。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1njl9/the_disappearing_spoon_a_delightful_surprise_of_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1njl9/the_disappearing_spoon_a_delightful_surprise_of_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 11:17:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have just finished reading Sam Kean&amp;#39;s The Disappearing Spoon and Other True Tales of Madness, Love, and the History of the World from the Periodic Table of the Elements (a mouthful of a title) and I would like to share with you how much I enjoyed the book. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I bought this book on a whim at a Barnes and Noble because I did terribly this semester due to school being online. I told my friend who was with me &amp;quot;I don&amp;#39;t wanna pick a science book because that&amp;#39;s nerdy but I did horrible this semester and I want to learn SOMETHING, even if it wasn&amp;#39;t from school.&amp;quot; But this book was way more enjoyable than school, as you will see. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book is a non-fiction science/history book. It is divided into chapters which focus on different elements of the periodic table and the stories behind the elements themselves, their discoverers, or maybe just their quirks and features. The authors writing style is less academic and more informal, but that does not subtract from how good of a learning source this book is. There are times in which you have to read over paragraphs again to understand what was being said about some particular topics, but for the most part, this book had me reading on and on wondering what would be revealed next about the scientists involved in discovering the elements (K .Fajans got a Nobel Prize revoked because he told a newspaper he was going to win one before the Nobel Committee made it official) or the elements themselves (there are only a few ounces of Astatine in the whole planet). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book is great because it is not extensive about one very particular topic, but it bounces around in a coherent way. It has a myriad of stories that stuck with me perfect for when I want to sound smart around people I just met (aluminium was so hard to extract at one point, it was worth more than gold).  Speaking of gold, one time a whole village was torn down because there was gold in its concrete, pavement, and foundations. Back to the book, reading it I never felt like &amp;quot;damn I&amp;#39;ve read enough about this, I wish he&amp;#39;d move on,&amp;quot; the stories were perfectly concise and interesting, and the best part is I felt good about myself reading this because I was actually learning stuff, as I only ever read fiction. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d recommend this book to anyone who is into obscure stories and facts and anyone who wants to learn a few cool things about the periodic table. This book is more lighthearted than academic so do not worry about not knowing much already about chemistry or physics, as it is explained quite nicely. Anyway, this is my first time doing a write up on a book since middle school, and I just wanted to show anyone looking for something to read a cool book :).  Also, if you have read the book I&amp;#39;d love to hear what you think about it! Have a good night/morning/evening/day!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛剛讀完 "萬福瑪利亞計劃"。]]></title><description><![CDATA[哇。只是哇。這本書絕對令人驚訝。幽默是真實的，情節
是引人注目的，而且人物是可親的。

這絕對是我在很長一段時間內閱讀過的最有趣的書之一。故事中出現的各種衝突
故事中出現的各種衝突都是如此令人着迷。

結局讓我感到驚訝...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1lhnz/just_finished_reading_project_hail_mary/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1lhnz/just_finished_reading_project_hail_mary/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 07:29:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow. Just wow. This book was absolutely amazing. The humor was genuine, the plot was compelling and the characters were relatable.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It definitely was one of the most fun I have had reading in a long time. The various conflicts that arise in the story are all so enthralling. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The ending surprised me and that&amp;#39;s not a bad thing. I think Andy Weir did a wonderful job and I cannot wait to read his next novel&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also loved the use of flashbacks as a storytelling device and I think it may be the best sci fi I have read in a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[傑森-雷諾茲以 "令人驚歎的 "兩面性贏得卡內基獎章]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1jw7w/jason_reynolds_wins_carnegie_medal_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1jw7w/jason_reynolds_wins_carnegie_medal_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 03:38:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你希望每個人都能讀什麼書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我屬於一個規模極小的讀書會（實際上只有我們兩個人），我們正在尋找一本不屬於我們通常喜歡的書。
我們正在尋找一本不屬於我們通常傾向於的書，也就是
幻想。我們一直試圖在某種程度上改變我們所讀的書。到目前爲止，我們已經讀了。

國王之路，桑德森（5/5）。

美國衆神》，蓋曼（2/5

劍...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o1gs82/what_book_do_you_wish_everyone_would_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o1gs82/what_book_do_you_wish_everyone_would_read/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 03:38:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I belong to an extremely small book club (literally just two of us) and we are looking for a book that is out of what we usually gravitate towards, which is fantasy. We&amp;#39;ve tried to vary the books we read somewhat. So far we&amp;#39;ve read: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Way of Kings, Sanderson (5/5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;American Gods, Gaiman (2/5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sword of Kaigen, Wang (3.5/5)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pirate Latitudes, Crichton (2.5/5) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wind up Bird Chronicle (4.5/5) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fahrenheit 451, Bradbury (4/5) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Futurological Congress, Lem (currently reading, good so far) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Final Empire, Sanderson (currently reading, good so far)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So in general, we&amp;#39;ve enjoyed most of what we&amp;#39;ve read (probably an unpopular rating given to American Gods!). &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is your favourite fiction book that you wished everyone would read? What should we read next?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我真的很欣賞那些熱衷於談論他們讀過的書的人。]]></title><description><![CDATA[最近我開始更多的閱讀，雖然我個人認爲閱讀活動並不那麼令人愉快
活動很愉快，但社交部分卻很精彩。我喜歡談論書籍和
故事。就像和偉大的談書人一樣，人們可以再次迷失在書中。無論是
談論情節，談論人物，有時它是...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o16ch8/i_really_appreciate_people_who_eagerly_talks/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o16ch8/i_really_appreciate_people_who_eagerly_talks/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 03:08:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recently I started reading more and while I personally don&amp;#39;t find the reading activity so enjoyable the social part is wonderful. I &lt;em&gt;love&lt;/em&gt; talking about books &amp;amp; stories. Like with great book talkers one can get lost in the book again. Be it talking about the plot, about the characters, sometimes it&amp;#39;s like you are gossiping about these made up characters. &amp;quot;Can you believe James did that? - oh I just read that, I knoooow, how dare he!?&amp;quot; Sharing books, overanalyzing them, plucking small unimportant snippets and going &amp;quot;oh that is such a great moment, totally spoke to me in a profound way!&amp;quot; Basically just having fun talking about these made up universes we find in books. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am so grateful to all those that talk about stories without timidity. Books are just so fun when shared.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[尋找像《星際》和《地心引力》這樣的書]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是科幻小說的新手，正在尋找一些以太空爲背景的懸疑科幻小說。
有驚悚或恐怖元素的太空科幻書。最好是沒有任何浪漫
子劇情。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o1cum2/looking_for_books_like_interstellar_and_gravity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o1cum2/looking_for_books_like_interstellar_and_gravity/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:13:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m new to the sci fi genre and am looking for some suspenseful sci fi books set in space that have thriller or horror elements. Preferably without any romantic subplots.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[記得在當地圖書館查詢書店的情況]]></title><description><![CDATA[昨天和孩子們去了圖書館。有我媽媽陪着我們，所以這一次我
實際上是去逛了一下里面的書店。最後買了6本書。4本是
手工製作和 "怎麼做 "的手冊。其他兩本是《安娜-卡列尼娜》和《巴斯克維爾的獵犬》。
Baskervilles。所有6本書的費用是多少？$5.50

告訴我最好的交易...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1c4bw/remember_to_check_your_local_library_for_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o1c4bw/remember_to_check_your_local_library_for_a/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 00:13:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Went to the library with the kids yesterday. Had my mom with us, so for once I actually got to browse the bookshop inside. Ended up with 6 books. 4 are crafting and “how to” manuals. Other two are Anna Karenina and The Hound of the Baskervilles. The cost for all 6? $5.50 &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tell me about the best deal you’ve gotten on a book?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[布魯姆日快樂! 我幾乎讀完了《尤利西斯》，我很喜歡它! 是否有其他的書迷喜歡這本瘋狂的書？]]></title><description><![CDATA[今年我一直在讀 "硬 "書（《白鯨》、《堂吉訶德》）。
並決定解決《尤利西斯》。我聽說它是最難讀的書之一。
所以我想這將是一個有趣的挑戰。我在網上找到了一份指南
這本書實際上是我最喜歡的書...。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o157xl/happy_bloomsday_im_almost_finished_with_ulysses/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o157xl/happy_bloomsday_im_almost_finished_with_ulysses/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 19:52:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been on a kick of reading &amp;quot;hard&amp;quot; books this year (Moby Dick, Don Quixote), and decided to tackle Ulysses. I&amp;#39;d heard it&amp;#39;s one of the toughest books to read, so I figured it would be an interesting challenge. I found a guide online to help me through it, and it&amp;#39;s actually been my favorite book I&amp;#39;ve read so far this year! I&amp;#39;m in the penultimate chapter, and should finish in the next day or two.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m wildly impressed by Joyce. He had an incredible grasp of language and history, and could write astonishingly beautiful prose. Language and style are like different hats he tries on for the various chapters; it&amp;#39;s fun to watch him play in the language. His characters (Bloom in particular) are also so real and fully formed. He isn&amp;#39;t afraid to gaze hard at the flaws of his characters (and they&amp;#39;re deeply flawed), but that makes their redeeming qualities even sweeter and more precious. The book doesn&amp;#39;t have much in the way of plot. It&amp;#39;s more like real life. You&amp;#39;re along for a journey without a clear beginning or end, but it ultimately is beautiful and meaningful despite its apparent formlessness. I&amp;#39;ve found this to be an absolutely profound experience, and I&amp;#39;d recommend it to anyone willing to rethink what a book can/should be.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是泰瑞-邁爾斯。我喜歡寫作。兔子是真的。AMA!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我製作電影、播客、音樂、書籍和任何他們願意讓我做的東西。我撰寫並執導了由詹妮弗-比爾斯、唐納德-薩瑟蘭、克里斯蒂安-薩瑟蘭、馬蒂爾-卡斯特羅、馬蒂爾-卡斯特羅等主演的電影。
執導了由珍妮弗-比爾斯、唐納德-薩瑟蘭、克里斯蒂安-斯萊特和
"石冷 "史蒂夫-奧斯汀。我創建了公共廣播聯盟
[http://www.publicradioalliance.com/]，其特點是播客：...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o189ry/im_terry_miles_i_love_writing_rabbits_is_real_ama/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o189ry/im_terry_miles_i_love_writing_rabbits_is_real_ama/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 19:43:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I make movies, podcasts, music, books and whatever they&amp;#39;ll let me. I wrote and directed movies starring Jennifer Beals, Donald Sutherland, Christian Slater and &amp;quot;Stone Cold&amp;quot; Steve Austin. I created &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.publicradioalliance.com/&quot;&gt;The Public Radio Alliance&lt;/a&gt; which features the podcasts: &lt;a href=&quot;http://tanispodcast.com/&quot;&gt;TANIS&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://rabbitspodcast.com/&quot;&gt;RABBITS&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://thelastmoviepod.com/&quot;&gt;The Last Movie&lt;/a&gt;. I also co-created &lt;a href=&quot;http://theblacktapespodcast.com/&quot;&gt;The Black Tapes Podcast&lt;/a&gt;. My first novel, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/604640/rabbits-by-terry-miles/&quot;&gt;Rabbits&lt;/a&gt;, released last week and I&amp;#39;m damn excited to talk about it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/pbve2fw96a571.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/pbve2fw96a571.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA["Ocean Vuong的《在地球上，我們短暫的華麗》是我遇到過的最美麗的散文作品]]></title><description><![CDATA[作爲Cindy Pham（Booktuber）亞洲閱讀馬拉松的一部分，我拿起了《OEWBG》，我被震撼了。
我被嚇了一跳。這本書的框架是寫給作者不識字的母親的一封信。
他並沒有直截了當地提到書中敘述者的名字，而是用了一個童年的綽號：OEWBG。
他沒有直截了當地提到書中敘述者的名字，而是用小時候的綽號：小狗。

書中還穿插了一些其他的故事。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o11c4v/on_earth_were_briefly_gorgeous_by_ocean_vuong_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o11c4v/on_earth_were_briefly_gorgeous_by_ocean_vuong_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 16:45:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of Cindy Pham&amp;#39;s (booktuber) Asian Readathon I picked up &amp;#39;OEWBG&amp;#39; and I was blown away. The book is framed as a letter addressed to the author&amp;#39;s mother who is illiterate.He doesn&amp;#39;t outright refer to the narrator of the book by his name but by a childhood nickname : Little Dog. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It weaves in and out of different points in the author&amp;#39;s lives and those of his mother and grandmother. He talks about experiences that revolve around his race and sexuality. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;His language is very poetic and it&amp;#39;s evident when the paragraphs merge so many themes and imagery together that one finds it hard to understand what he&amp;#39;s trying to convey. But sometimes it&amp;#39;s not about the meaning, it&amp;#39;s the emotions that the words evoke.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No word of his is wasted, they all contain themes interconnected throughout the book. His metaphors and language touches your soul. Just look at this quote for example :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;He loves me, he loves me not, we are taught to say as we tear the flower away from it&amp;#39;s flowerness. To arrive at love, then, is to arrive through obliteration&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If that doesn&amp;#39;t convince you then an excerpt from the book which was published in the New Yorker might :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/culture/personal-history/a-letter-to-my-mother-that-she-will-never-read/amp&quot;&gt;On Earth We&amp;#39;re Briefly Gorgeous - Ocean Vuong&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[美國廣播公司試圖掩蓋對詹姆斯-鮑德溫的採訪。四十年後的今天，它仍然與我們息息相關。]]></title><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o166c9/abc_tried_to_bury_this_james_baldwin_interview/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o166c9/abc_tried_to_bury_this_james_baldwin_interview/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 15:41:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[老男人/年輕女人關係的無盡列車]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好--啊，我在r/books[/r/books]上發的第一篇帖子，而且是一篇咆哮！這是我的第一次。

所以我剛剛讀了《紙上魔術師》。這是一個很好的想法，寫得不是很好。
但說實話，我對這個19歲、剛從學校畢業的女孩感到不滿。
女孩，"愛上 "了她30多歲的導師，最後...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o12l28/the_endless_train_of_older_manyounger_woman/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o12l28/the_endless_train_of_older_manyounger_woman/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:43:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello everyone - ah, my first post on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/books&quot;&gt;r/books&lt;/a&gt; and it&amp;#39;s a rant!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So I just read &amp;#39;The Paper Magician&amp;#39;. It was a good idea, not amazingly well written, but honestly the gripe is with the 19 year old, fresh out of school, girl, &amp;quot;falling in love&amp;quot; with her 30+ year old mentor, the end of the book and teaser for the second book implying it would be reciprocated. And I remembered reading a &amp;quot;Newbury and Hobbes&amp;quot; book a friend lent me and running into more or less the same trope and being skeeved out by it then too - the whole &amp;#39;bright young woman falls for older mentor&amp;#39; business.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Why is this such a prevalent theme, especially, it seems, in fantasy? Maybe I&amp;#39;m just reading the wrong books. I appreciate these are relatively pulpy titles. You almost-never seem to find either genuine teacher/pupil relationships, M/F friendships or heck, an old(er) woman having an adventure in general, without some weird age-mismatched romance being shoehorned in. Am I alone in finding that sort of addition really - unpleasant? I felt genuinely dirty putting down &amp;#39;The Paper Magician&amp;#39; - this girl has known this man not even 6 months, he&amp;#39;s had endless more experience than her and it&amp;#39;s treated like a sweet romance? There was genuinely no need for the romance at all. I&amp;#39;d believe she wanted to save her teacher because she liked and respected him &lt;em&gt;as a teacher and mentor&lt;/em&gt;, not because she&amp;#39;s *suddenly in lurve*. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Maybe I&amp;#39;m too old for what is essentially a YA book, but being 35+ myself doesn&amp;#39;t mean I don&amp;#39;t want to read about magic and also - where are the women heroes my own age that I can relate to? Older men are magical heroes all over the place but they have to be paired with a younger smart-but-wide-eyed woman to Teach His Skills To and of course, fall in love. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I appreciate the real world bleeds into these books and of course, older women are usually considered less attractive and/or busy having babies to have adventures (...mild /s, but also some truth in it...), but it&amp;#39;s &lt;em&gt;fantasy&lt;/em&gt;, come on, writers, live a little? Is there not a target audience of middle aged, non-child-having (...or even HAVING-children women who can do more than one thing in their life at a time or have invested in a child-carrying backpack) women who want an adventure? Not even a romance. Just a story with an older magical heroine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Are there any books I&amp;#39;m missing to disabuse me of this feeling that this is the only book around? Am I alone in feeling genuinely squicked by massive age-gap romance in what&amp;#39;s not even, primarily, a romance novel?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll be amused if this is downvoted to all heck since it&amp;#39;s my first post and heyyyyy, maybe I am a bitter old woman. ;) But anyone feel the same in any way?!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eh, I&amp;#39;ve got &amp;#39;The Priory of the Orange Tree&amp;#39; on my list next so maybe that&amp;#39;ll cheer me up. ;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Erin Morgenstern的《無星海》，鬥爭是真實的]]></title><description><![CDATA[這本書我正好讀完了50%，我真的在努力保持着
讀的動力。

這本書的散文很美（儘管可能有點重描述），故事的前提是非常令人興奮的。
故事的前提是如此令人興奮，但似乎沒有什麼進展。主要人物
是乏味的，而且沒有什麼有效的......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0w4l5/starless_sea_by_erin_morgenstern_the_struggle_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0w4l5/starless_sea_by_erin_morgenstern_the_struggle_is/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 06:43:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am exactly 50% through this book and I am really fighting to keep up the motivation to read it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The prose is beautiful (if perhaps a little description heavy) and the premise of the story is so exciting, but seems to be going nowhere. The main character is DULL and has very little valid motivation at this point in the story. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else read it, is it worth getting through the back half?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我的書包從我的車裏被偷走了。]]></title><description><![CDATA[值得慶幸的是，袋子裏沒有什麼實質性的金錢價值。但是
裏面的書對我來說是非常重要的。但我未婚妻的《誓言使者》（Oathbringer），這本書很受人喜愛，而且我正在努力完成它。
誓言使者》，這是一本深受喜愛的書，也是我正在努力學習的一本書。
的書，就在那個袋子裏。對一個人來說，這本書幾乎一文不值。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0vjj4/my_book_bag_was_stolen_out_of_my_car/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0vjj4/my_book_bag_was_stolen_out_of_my_car/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 05:44:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, there was nothing of substantial monetary value in the bag. But the books that were in it were incredibly important to me. But my fiancée’s copy of Oathbringer, a book which is well loved and one that I was working my way through, was in that bag. Nearly worthless to someone putting in the effort to steal, but invaluable to me. People are cruel.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[有沒有人對我們永遠無法讀完所有的書感到非常難過？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我只是很難過。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o0v8k7/anyone_just_really_sad_that_we_will_never_be_able/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o0v8k7/anyone_just_really_sad_that_we_will_never_be_able/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 04:32:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;i am just sad.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你在哪些書中真正看到過自己？]]></title><description><![CDATA[作爲一個長期的讀者，直到最近在閱讀薩默塞特-毛姆的《剃刀邊緣》時
毛姆的《剃刀邊緣》時，我才真正看到自己在書中的形象。這真是一個
偶然發現的令人驚訝和歡迎的事情。其中一個人物的想法、感受、生活中的位置，甚至是他自己的想法。
感受，在生活中的位置，甚至他在事件中的經歷......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0lexd/in_what_books_have_you_truly_seen_yourself/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0lexd/in_what_books_have_you_truly_seen_yourself/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 04:32:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a longtime reader, only recently while reading “The Razor’s Edge” by Somerset Maugham have I truly seen who I am reflected in the pages. 
This was such a surprising and welcome thing to stumble across. One of the character’s thoughts, feelings, place in life and even his experiences in the events of the novel are all things I can relate to and truly have experienced. It’s as if it’s my life story as well. 
Has anyone else had this profound phenomenon happen to them?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我希望對樹木、花卉和岩石有基本瞭解。]]></title><description><![CDATA[順帶了解一下，現在不希望深入大自然。

一年多前我搬到了PNW，那裏非常漂亮，到處都是森林，有很多美景。
森林和如此多的美景。我想知道這些樹種的名稱
和花的名字，因爲我在進行小型徒步旅行。我也喜歡岩石。

我沒有時間...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o0kv5h/i_would_like_to_have_a_basic_knowledge_of_trees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o0kv5h/i_would_like_to_have_a_basic_knowledge_of_trees/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 02:52:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A passing understanding, not looking to go deep into nature right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I moved to the PNW a little over a year ago, and it&amp;#39;s gorgeous, filled with forests and so much beauty. I would like to know the names of the tree species and flowers as I take my mini-hikes. I love rocks too.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;#39;t have time to take a class in these subjects right now, and I have three other pursuits that I really need to buckle down on, so... I would like three simple picture-style books on the subject.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Best would be a photo with a few simply written facts, almost like a child&amp;#39;s book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m sure these books exists but I can&amp;#39;t find them on Amazon, and the book stores in my city aren&amp;#39;t really open yet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you in advance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[咆哮式書評 "艾迪-拉魯的隱形生活"]]></title><description><![CDATA[我昨天看完了這本書，仍然非常生氣，以至於我不得不
寫一篇咆哮式的書評來宣泄一下。這本書有一個很好的前提。
多麼好的一個故事的想法啊! 這就是爲什麼我很生氣，作者做得如此
糟糕的工作。從寫作到情節，再到...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0l5ft/ranting_book_review_of_the_invisible_life_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0l5ft/ranting_book_review_of_the_invisible_life_of/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 01:09:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I finished this book yesterday and am still so angry about it that I just had to write a ranting book review for catharsis. This book had such a great premise. What a good idea for a story! Which is why I&amp;#39;m so angry that the author did such a poor job. Everything from the writing to the plot to the characters was terrible. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The writing - Interesting at first, but she&amp;#39;s just not a good enough writer to pull off the style she was trying to write in. I think she was going for poetic and modern, but it came off as a college student trying to write in an interesting way and failing. You know those IG posts where the caption is full of &amp;quot;deep&amp;quot; descriptions, sentence fragments, and new paragraphs that are only a sentence long? That was this book. Oh, and she used the same description for every character over and over. Lucien is wolfish. Addie has freckles like a constellation. Every man in the book has curls falling over his forehead. FIND A DIFFERENT WAY OF DESCRIBING PEOPLE. Also, she kept hammering the same trope of, &amp;quot;Addie didn&amp;#39;t know about this yet, but she would.&amp;quot; As in, &amp;quot;Addie didn&amp;#39;t know Italian yet, but she would,&amp;quot; or, &amp;quot;Addie didn&amp;#39;t know about Luc&amp;#39;s moods yet, but she would.&amp;quot; This isn&amp;#39;t interesting! This is not a story!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;The characters were super boring. Addie, the main character, was boring. Nothing interesting about her at all. Its a shame that a woman who turns immortal has no interests, imagination, or drive. Her mortal love interest was equally uninteresting. The two of them would walk around uninterestingly, apart and together. Its was very...uninteresting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Plot - there was no plot. Actually, I take that back. In a book that&amp;#39;s 350 pages long, there was plot in maybe 40 pages. The beginning set up what should have been a really, really good story. Then nothing happened for 300 PAGES. The last 30 pages contained the rest of the plot. They were the most interesting by far, but still turned out to be boring because she hadn&amp;#39;t developed relationships, people, plot, anything. I didn&amp;#39;t care about anyone by then and forced myself to skim the last 30 pages, which is where everything actually happened. There was so much promise held in those 30 pages. Its such a freaking shame. You got a glimpse what this could have been had a talented storyteller written it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A good editor would have told her to take the first 20 and last 50 and write an entire new book just fleshing that out. Instead, you get 300 pages of Addie walking around and Luc appearing. They then have the same conversation over and over. Every time the timeline went to a moment in the past, you knew she was going to be walking around and that Luc would appear after a page and you knew exactly what they were going to talk about. This happened at least 25 times. No character development. No development in their relationship. No moving the plot forward. Just the same thing over. and over. and over. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;TL;DR - The writing, plot, and characters in this book were terrible, which is a shame for such a great premise. This story in a different author&amp;#39;s hands would have been so, so great. I&amp;#39;m so mad a better author wasn&amp;#39;t able to write it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[7月份/r/books讀書俱樂部的選擇是Fredrik Backman的《焦慮的人》。]]></title><description><![CDATA[如果你在尋找上個月的公告主題，可以在
在這裏找到
[https://old.reddit.com/r/books/comments/nf76bm/the_rbooks_book_club_selection_for_june_is/]。

在7月份，我們將閱讀弗雷德裏克-巴克曼的《焦慮的人》。
每週都會有一...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0cgsf/the_rbooks_book_club_selection_for_july_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0cgsf/the_rbooks_book_club_selection_for_july_is/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 19:23:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;If you are looking for the announcement thread for the previous month, it may be found&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://old.reddit.com/r/books/comments/nf76bm/the_rbooks_book_club_selection_for_june_is/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;here&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the month of July, we will be reading &lt;strong&gt;Anxious People&lt;/strong&gt; by Fredrik Backman. Each week there will be a discussion thread and when we are done, Fredrik himself will be joining us for an AMA&lt;strong&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/49127718-anxious-people&quot;&gt;Goodreads&lt;/a&gt; (feel free to skip if you prefer to know nothing going into the book):&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Looking at real estate isn&amp;#39;t usually a life-or-death situation, but an apartment open house becomes just that when a failed bank robber bursts in and takes a group of strangers hostage. [...]  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Each of them carries a lifetime of grievances, hurts, secrets, and passions that are ready to boil over. None of them is entirely who they appear to be. And all of them—the bank robber included—desperately crave some sort of rescue. As the authorities and the media surround the premises, these reluctant allies will reveal surprising truths about themselves and set in a motion a chain of events so unexpected that even they can hardly explain what happens next. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;!Content Warning! (potential spoilers) - &lt;span class=&quot;md-spoiler-text&quot;&gt;Suicide&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You may find the dates of, and links to, the discussion threads below in the sticky comment on this post. You are welcome to read at your own pace. Don&amp;#39;t worry about joining later on in the month. Usually it is pretty easy to catch up and you are always welcome to join the discussions a little later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you would like to view any past book club selection or want to see how things work, you may find the complete archive &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/books/wiki/bookclub&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those of you that are viewing reddit on the redesigned desktop version you will see an option on this post to &amp;#39;follow&amp;#39;. If you &amp;#39;follow&amp;#39; the book club post you will receive a notification when a new post, a discussion thread for book club, is added to the collection. It is still being tested, so it may not be perfect, but perhaps it will make it easier to join the discussions when they go up.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yaa Gyasi的《Homegoing》是如此美麗的一本書。]]></title><description><![CDATA[這是一部由雅-加西寫的歷史小說，同時也是一部美麗和悲傷的小說。
小說。隨着每一頁的翻動，我發現自己被送回了過去，看着每個人物的生活如何展開
看着每個人物的生活如何展開--彷彿他們都在活着。
他們都是活生生的人物，而我則是一個不老的人，而且......]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0gk56/homegoing_by_yaa_gyasi_was_such_a_beautiful_read/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0gk56/homegoing_by_yaa_gyasi_was_such_a_beautiful_read/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 19:05:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A historical novel written by Yaa Gyasi, it was simultaneously beautiful and sad novel. With the turn of each pages, I found myself transported back in time and watched how the lives of each character unfolded- as if they were all living, breathing characters while I was the one who was ageless, and was traveling through time. Despite not sharing the same history, I felt an unimaginable connection with each of the characters of the book. I I never read anything like this before. I never read the same book twice, but maybe I will read this book again. Homegoing was one of the best books I read this year!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sharing because I thought everyone should this book at least once in their life. I am certainly going to recommend this book to all my friends.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於巴勒斯坦的書籍]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好，我正在尋找涵蓋巴勒斯坦發生的事情背後的歷史背景的書籍。
的書，以及最近發生的事情。謝謝
衷心感謝!]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o0cyt2/books_on_palestine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/o0cyt2/books_on_palestine/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 16:40:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello community, I am looking for books that cover the historical context behind what is happening in Palestine as well as what happened more recently. Thanks in advance!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[還有誰？：更多但更短的書的章節比更少但更長的章節更容易讓人迷上一本書（至少對我來說是這樣）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[有一些書有很多章節，但每一章只有大約
1-9頁長。還有一些書的章節較少，但它們可以持續到
長達30多頁。

這肯定有一些心理學上的解釋，但對我來說，我發現那些有很多章節的書
那些有很多章節的書讓我覺得...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0fnki/anyone_else_more_but_shorter_book_chapters_make/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0fnki/anyone_else_more_but_shorter_book_chapters_make/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 15:57:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some books with a looooot of chapters but each chapter&amp;#39;s just around 1-9 pages long. Then there are some books with fewer chapters but they can go on to be 30+ pages long.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There must be some psychological explanation for this but for me I find that the ones with a lot of chapters make books easier to go through, losing time saying &amp;quot;just one more chapter&amp;quot; again and again and again compared to when reading a looooong chapter and growing tired of anticipating the next chapter. (I don&amp;#39;t stop reading in the middle of chapters, I just can&amp;#39;t)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;d enjoy reading an 600-page novel with 80 chapters more than a 200-page one with just 5 chapters (considering the quality is on par).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Anyone feel me? 😅&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[關於《當呼吸變成空氣》的非正式書評（因爲我真的需要把這件事說出來）。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我真的不知道該從何說起。保羅-卡拉尼提，我是把你作爲一個
神經外科醫生、神經科學家、丈夫、父親，還是癌症患者？I
我認爲這就是卡拉尼提的魅力所在，無論你如何努力，一個人
標題都不足以抓住他的本質。

我拿起這個...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0ae2g/an_informal_book_review_on_when_breath_becomes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/o0ae2g/an_informal_book_review_on_when_breath_becomes/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 11:51:51 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I truly don&amp;#39;t know where to start. Paul Kalanithi, do I speak of you as a neurosurgeon, a neuroscientist, a husband, a father, or a cancer patient? I think that&amp;#39;s the beauty of who Kalanithi was, no matter how hard you tried, one title wouldn&amp;#39;t be enough to capture his essence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I picked up this book as a medical student, but put it down as a human being, remaining in the depths between life and death. I was inconsiderate, to say the least. The way I started reading this book reminded me of the way some medical students deal with cadavers; slicing and tearing them open with a thirst for knowledge, but forgetting that these were people: living and breathing, just like them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I skimmed through the pages of the book, stopping whenever my eyes settled on a new medical term. &amp;quot;Neurocardiogenic Syncope,&amp;quot; I whispered, hastily closing the book to search up the term. It was not until Part II: Cease Not Till Death, that I came to terms with an unsettling notion: I was reading the words of a man who had died. Paul Kalanithi was a man who had fought so hard to understand mortality, and as he mentions in his book, what better way to understand something than to experience it first-hand. It was then when I began to read the book as someone that would have to face their own death one day, and many more before that. Death is inevitable, cruel, but also, necessary.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paul Kalanithi has managed to shift my entire perspective on medicine, doctor-patient relationships, and life. When people asked me why I chose to become a doctor, my reply would revolve around science, but very rarely, did I mention people. Don&amp;#39;t get me wrong, there is nothing more I want to do than help people, but I never consciously made that my first priority. Having finished this book, and it leaving me with a strong sense of grounding, I can proudly say that I have found the real reason I chose medicine. Here&amp;#39;s how Paul Kalanithi phrased it, &amp;quot;Emma [Kalanithi&amp;#39;s oncologist] hadn&amp;#39;t given me back my old identity. She&amp;#39;d protected my ability to forge a new one.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Treating patients is not always about a biological cure, because even when patients are cured, the memories and emotions remain. Thus, what differentiates doctors like Emma and Paul from all the others, is that their patients were able to go on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ll go on,&amp;quot; Paul Kalathini whispered, dragging himself out of his bed. He had a whole plan ahead of him; he wanted to become a neurosurgeoun-neuroscientist. He spent all his life focused on this plan. Yet, when faced with the possibility of death, he adopted a new persona. He became a father and a writer (my favourite writer).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Paul Kalanithi, I can only hope for an ounce of your bravery, determination, intelligence, and strength, and hope that your beautiful daughter, Cady, gets so much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will never be forgotten, certainly not by me. Thank you for all that you&amp;#39;ve done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before I go, I promise to read your book after every year of medical school. So, until next year, Dr. Kalanithi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Note: I’m sorry if this is messy and full of errors, I’m not ashamed to admit I wrote this while crying. I would love to hear all of your experiences with the book.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[剛剛完成 "萬福瑪利亞計劃"。真是一次愉快的旅程[劇透]]]></title><description><![CDATA[首先，我要說的是，我喜歡《火星人》，無論是書還是改編的電影。
這本書在很多方面都有類似的感覺，我很喜歡。我感受到的
情感過山車比我預期的要多，特別是在最後。
我對這個故事的前提是完全盲目的，而且是如此的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nzvatn/just_finished_project_hail_mary_what_an_enjoyable/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nzvatn/just_finished_project_hail_mary_what_an_enjoyable/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 05:46:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, I’ll say that I loved The Martian, both the book and the adapted movie.  This book has a similar feel in a lot of ways, which I liked. I felt the emotional roller coaster more than I was expecting, especially towards the end. I went into this story completely blind to the premise and am so glad I did. I wasn’t expecting him to make contact with aliens and loved his dynamic with Rocky. The last chapter hit me right in the feels.  Was excited to see that he got a new set of students in the end.  Fun fact, both The Martian (movie) and this new book ended with hands raised… found that cool.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[如果我是閱讀新手，而且不善於閱讀，我應該閱讀 "名著 "嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。我最近開始接觸閱讀，但我很難保持專注
我需要一段時間才能讀完一本書。我不覺得自己對一本書有什麼興趣
我認爲我應該感興趣。正因爲如此，我在考慮閱讀人們認爲的
認爲是最好的文學作品，如《堂吉訶德》（或如此...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzl2se/should_i_read_masterpieces_if_im_new_to_reading/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzl2se/should_i_read_masterpieces_if_im_new_to_reading/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 02:25:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all. I recently started getting into reading but I struggle to keep my focus and it takes me a while to finish a book. I don&amp;#39;t feel as interested in a book as I think I should. Bc of this I was thinking of reading what people would consider some of the best literature such as don quixote (or so I&amp;#39;ve heard). However, I&amp;#39;m worried that bc I&amp;#39;m not an avid reader or any good at reading I won&amp;#39;t appreciate the book as much. What would you recommend i do?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[謝謝大家!]]></title><description><![CDATA[我想說的是，自從加入這個分論壇後，我的閱讀清單的質量有了很大提高。
我的閱讀清單的質量有了很大的提高，因此，我的閱讀樂趣也得到了提高。
閱讀的樂趣。我從自己的請求中得到了一些很好的建議，以及
我從自己的請求中得到了一些很好的建議，同時也看到了其他人的請求。這是一個很好的團體。對於所有的...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzvg08/thanks_all/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzvg08/thanks_all/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 21:41:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a quick note to say that since joining this subreddit the quality of my reading list has greatly improved, and because of that so has my pleasure in reading. I&amp;#39;ve gotten some wonderful suggestions from my own request and as well as looking at other&amp;#39;s requests. This is a good group. For all of you who take the time to share the joy you&amp;#39;ve found in a book, thank you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[爲什麼每一本從敵人到戀人的書都比P&P愚蠢？]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是《傲慢與偏見》的終生粉絲，但我最近才發現
"從敵人到戀人 "是愛情小說中一個非常常見的套路。

顯然，我很高興，因爲我認爲我肯定會發現一個
一個永無止境的娛樂仙境。

但是，在谷歌上搜索了 "最好的敵人到情人 "的名單之後，我發現了一個新的問題。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzpmhs/why_is_every_enemiestolovers_book_stupid_compared/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzpmhs/why_is_every_enemiestolovers_book_stupid_compared/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 20:49:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m a lifelong Pride &amp;amp; Prejudice fan, but I only recently found out that &amp;quot;enemies to lovers&amp;quot; is a really common trope in romance novels. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously I was delighted, because I thought that I was sure to discover a wonderland of never-ending entertainment. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But after googling lists of “best enemies to lovers” novels and trying out a few, I am surprised to find how… dumb they are? &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now I am NO literary snob believe me, I love trashy novels! But like… these books are so blah, stilted, or just… not clever. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Like, is it rocket science? Is it really that hard to write a clever slow-burner like p&amp;amp;amp;p was?  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I tried “you deserve each other” by Sarah Hogle and actually returned it 40 percent through. Really good premise but no clever dialogue whatsoever. No chemistry. No buildup. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone seems to recommend “the hating game” by sally thorne but I listened to the first chapter and already it sounds dumb. Like “We sit here with our chins on our hands and stare into each other’s eyes.” And “My previous passwords have all been variations on how much I hate Joshua.” Like girl, get a life. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(This isn&amp;#39;t a rule, but I&amp;#39;d prefer the story to not have characters that solely exist to waste paper until Miss Protagonist and Mr. Hunk discover their thin veneer of “hatred” has just been generic-brand flirting all along.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please give me your suggestions for clever haters-turned-lovers books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I don’t care what time period it’s from &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;needs witty characters &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;male/female romance &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;maybe mixed with another genre? &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m not looking for porny sexy stuff but I don’t mind it if the story is good &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;slow burn is good &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I’m not looking to compare or replace p&amp;amp;amp;p I just used it as an example of a book that did the haters to lovers thing really well.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我是勞倫斯-賴特，普利策獎得主，《隆起的塔》和《十月底》的作者，在此談論我的新書《瘟疫年》。科維德時代的美國。你可以問我任何問題。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我是勞倫斯-賴特，《紐約客》的工作人員，劇作家，編劇。
也是普利策獎獲得者，已經出版了11本非虛構作品。
他已經出版了11本非虛構類書籍，包括《隱祕之塔》。
[https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/194238/the-looming-tower-movie-tie-in-by-lawrence-wright/]。
去...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nzq4iw/im_lawrence_wright_pulitzer_prizewinning_author/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nzq4iw/im_lawrence_wright_pulitzer_prizewinning_author/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 18:33:20 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m Lawrence Wright, staff writer for The New Yorker, playwright, screenwriter, and a Pulitzer Prize–winning author who has released eleven books of non-fiction, including &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/194238/the-looming-tower-movie-tie-in-by-lawrence-wright/&quot;&gt;The Looming Tower&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/212925/going-clear-by-lawrence-wright/&quot;&gt;Going Clear&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/561612/god-save-texas-by-lawrence-wright/&quot;&gt;God Save Texas&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last April, I released a novel, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/624363/the-end-of-october-by-lawrence-wright/&quot;&gt;The End of October&lt;/a&gt;, in which I gave a fictionalized account of a devastating disease sweeping across the globe. The manuscript was completed and delivered before COVID-19 hit the scene. Then, at the end of last year, I penned an article for The New Yorker about the actual pandemic we were facing, entitled &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2021/01/04/the-plague-year&quot;&gt;The Plague Year&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot;. Now, as of last week, my book of the same title is out in the world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/678999/the-plague-year-by-lawrence-wright/&quot;&gt;The Plague Year&lt;/a&gt;, I look at 2020 from the initial outbreak of COVID-19 to the storming of the U.S. Capitol to the extraordinary vaccine rollout, touching on medical, economic, political, and social ramifications of the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking forward to discussing my work with you—past and present—as well as any questions you might have about my research or findings. Ask me anything!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof: 
&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/hwqt7z4dclx61.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/hwqt7z4dclx61.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[具有有趣情節的亞洲標題？任何類型的都可以！☺️]]></title><description><![CDATA[書友們好！我想在今年購買更多的亞洲書籍。我想在今年購買更多的亞洲書籍。嗯，亞洲人或
非亞裔作者都很不錯。我只是想多讀一些書，並收集一些
該類型的書。

一些來自亞洲作家的書籍推薦，你可以閱讀。

 1. Pachinko》--李敏珍
 2. 奇蹟溪》--金安琪
 3....]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzk9cj/asian_titles_with_interesting_plot_any_genre_will/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzk9cj/asian_titles_with_interesting_plot_any_genre_will/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 18:01:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello book community! I want to buy more Asian titles this year. Well, asian or non-asian authors are pretty cool. I just like to read more and collect from that genre/type. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some book recommendations from Asian authors you can read: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pachinko - Min Jin Lee&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Miracle Creek - Angie Kim &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Strange Weather in Tokyo - Hiromi Kawakami &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Little fires everywhere - Celeste Ng &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are all good!! ❤️✨&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[我買了一本美國書的英國版本，它有很大的不同。]]></title><description><![CDATA[我以前也買過美國書的英國版本，通常唯一不同的是
是標點符號的不同。但這本書的實際內容是
不同。它是《好女孩，壞血液》，是《好女孩的謀殺指南》的續集。
的續集。我首先注意到的是 "mum "而不是 "mom"，但後來...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nznd06/i_bought_the_uk_version_of_an_american_book_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/books/comments/nznd06/i_bought_the_uk_version_of_an_american_book_and/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 16:41:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve bought UK versions of American books before, and usually the only thing different is the punctuation. This one though, the actual content of the book is different. It’s Good Girl, Bad Blood which is the sequel to A Good Girl’s Guide to Murder. I first noticed “mum” instead of “mom”, but then also “999”, “solicitor”, “A-levels”, etc. So finally I caved and bought an American copy from Target and it’s even more different than I thought. Whole paragraphs replaced! The name of the town changed!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Has anyone else seen this before? I thought this was so bizarre.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[你能給我推薦一本吸引人的書，把我從閱讀的困境中解救出來嗎？]]></title><description><![CDATA[大家好。

雖然我通常是一個狂熱的讀者，但這幾個月來我一直處於低迷狀態，而最近的幾本書
我試圖拿起的幾本書都沒有吸引我。

我真的很想看一本非公式化的驚悚小說，希望能有一本帶有神祕感的書能吸引我。
會吸引我。但我希望能有 "下一個Gone... "之外的東西。]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzdty5/can_you_suggest_me_a_pageturner_to_knock_me_out/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nzdty5/can_you_suggest_me_a_pageturner_to_knock_me_out/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 09:05:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi all, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Though usually an avid reader, I’ve been in a funk for a few months and the last few books I’ve tried to pick up just haven’t grabbed me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m really craving a non-formulaic thriller, hopefully one with a mystery that will hook me. But I’m hoping for something outside of “the next Gone Girl” generic thrillers that are a dime a dozen these days.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks so much!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[像《搭車指南》、《德克-詹特利》、《光盤世界》這樣的書...]]></title><description><![CDATA[所以，我基本上已經準備好了D.A.和T.P.的所有作品。
完成了斯蒂芬-金和查克-帕拉紐克的長期馬拉松比賽（非常暗淡），我需要一些有趣和輕鬆的東西來擺脫個人的低迷。
我需要一些有趣的、輕鬆的東西來擺脫個人的頹廢狀態。
我喜歡所有這些書都是不敬業的，我想要一些...]]></description><link>https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nz2370/books_like_hitchhikers_guide_dirk_gently_disc/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://books.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/booksuggestions/comments/nz2370/books_like_hitchhikers_guide_dirk_gently_disc/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2021 08:39:48 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I&amp;#39;ve ready basically everything by D.A. And T. P. But most recently I finished a long marathon of Stephen King and Chuck Palahniuk (very bleak), and I need something fun and light to pull out of a bit of a personal downward spiral. I love all of these books are irreverent, and I want something funny, witty, but with some depth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately I&amp;#39;m not a fan of Christopher Moore, so not that set. Hope this helps, and thanks for the recommendations in advance. I can&amp;#39;t believe how helpful this group has been for me!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>